<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage id="19341" parentID="11978" level="2" writerID="106" creatorID="94" nodeType="1059" template="16" sortOrder="14" createDate="2013-10-29T16:12:26" updateDate="2019-07-01T17:00:00" nodeName="What Is New" urlName="what-is-new" writerName="content" creatorName="xunfan" path="-1,11978,19341" isDoc="">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
         <div class="section-component">
            <div class="more-detail">
            	 <h1>Important Notice</h1>
				 <h3>July 2019</h3>
					 <ul>
					 	<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-July-webapps-python-update"><span>7/1</span>Linux kernel TCP SACK denial of service vulnerability<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
									<section>
										<p>Newly disclosed security vulnerabilities (<a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-11477">CVE-2019-11477</a>, <a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-11478">CVE-2019-11478</a>, <a href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2019-11479">CVE-2019-11479</a>) may cause the Linux operating system to the risk of "denial of service (DoS)". For customers running IaaS Linux virtual machines, please contact the providers of Linux distributions for guidance. For customers using Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) and HDInsight, please refer to the following documents:</p>
										<ul>
											<li>Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS): <a href="https://github.com/Azure/AKS/issues/1065">https://github.com/Azure/AKS/issues/1065</a></li>
											<li>HDInsight: <a href="https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/security-advisory-on-linux-kernel-tcp-vulnerabilities-for-hdinsight-clusters/">https://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/updates/security-advisory-on-linux-kernel-tcp-vulnerabilities-for-hdinsight-clusters/</a></li>
										</ul>
										<p>See <a href="https://portal.msrc.microsoft.com/zh-cn/security-guidance/advisory/ADV190020">Microsoft Security Notice 190020</a> for more information.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
							</li>
					 </ul>
				 <h3>January 2019</h3>
				 		<ul>
						 	<li>
								<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-january-webapps-python-update"><span>1/14</span>Azure App Services have updated Python 3.4.1 to 3.6.6<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
									<section>
										<p>To solve the known security issue in Python 3.4.1, we have updated all App Services running Python 3.4.1. Original Python 3.4.1 has been updated to Python 3.6.6.</p>
										<p>We suggest you to run a test for App Services and update the code, to ensure your websites fully compatible with the new version of Python.</p>
										<p>If you need to force App Services to run the old version of Python for special reasons, please refer to our GitHub announcement: <a href="https://github.com/Azure/app-service-announcements/issues/144">https://github.com/Azure/app-service-announcements/issues/144</a></p>
									</section>
								</div>
							</li>
				       </ul>
				 <h3>December 2018</h3>
				 		<ul>

						 	<li>
								<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-december-cognitive-service-emotion-api-retirement"><span>12/28</span>Azure Cognitive Services Emotion API will be deprecated - Please migrate to Face API by February 15, 2019<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
									<section>
										<p>Our <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/home/features/cognitive-services/face/">Face API</a> has now been officially released. It can detect emotions displayed on human faces in your applications. As the existing Emotion API features have been fully replaced by the Face API, we will deprecate Emotion API on <strong> February 15, 2019</strong>.</p>
										<p>To continue using Emotion API, please migrate to Face API by the stated date. We encourage you to make the switch as soon as possible to take advantage of Face API, which includes richer facial recognition features, service level agreements, and full Azure support.</p>
										<p>Please <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/cognitive-services/face/">migrate to Face API</a> by February 15, 2019, to prevent any service disruption to your applications and fully utilize emotion recognition features.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
							</li>
					   		<li>
								<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-december-IoThub-operations-monitoring-retirement"><span>12/18</span>Diagnostic settings in Azure IoT Hub (IoT Hub) to replace operations monitoring, please migrate by March 10, 2019</a>
									<section>
										<p>Diagnostic settings in Azure Monitor provide a single, simplified monitoring and logging experience. Azure Monitor and Azure IoT Hub are fully integrated, which can help you to keep your IoT solutions running in a healthy state. As diagnostic settings have replaced operations monitoring in Azure IoT Hub, the operations monitoring will be deprecated on March 10, 2019.</p>
										<p>To continue to collect logs on Azure IoT Hub without disruption, please <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/iot-hub/iot-hub-migrate-to-diagnostics-settings">migrate to diagnostic settings</a> by March 10, 2019, at which time operations monitoring will be completely removed from the Hub and the support for it will end.</p>
										<p>Learn about <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/iot-hub/iot-hub-monitor-resource-health">details of using diagnostic settings to monitor the operations and health of Hub</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
							</li>
				       </ul>

				 <h3>November 2018</h3>
				       <ul>
					   		<li>
								<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november-mysqldatabase"><span>11/30</span>We are ending the MySQL Database on Azure service on December 1, 2019. This will be replaced by the Azure Database for MySQL service.</a>
									<section>
										<p>Azure Database for MySQL provides fully managed, enterprise-level MySQL database as a service. With Azure Database for MySQL:</p>
										<ul>
											<li>Customers can easily migrate to the cloud, using languages and frameworks of their choice.</li>
											<li>Customers get built-in high availability and dynamic scaling, helping them easily adjust to changes in their demands.</li>
											<li>Customers will benefit from the unparalleled security and compliance, including <a href="https://www.azure.cn/support/azure-ip-advantage/">Azure IP Advantage</a>.</li>
										</ul>
										<p>All these services come with a flexible pricing model so customers can choose resources for their workloads with no hidden cost. To find out more about Azure Database for MySQL, please see the <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/home/features/mysql/">Product Function</a> page and <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/pricing/details/mysql">Price Details</a> page.</p>
										<p>If you are an existing customer:</p>
										<ul>
										<li>You will be automatically migrated to the new service before the end of life of the existing service.</li>
										<li>User business continuity is supported. When your server(s) has been scheduled for migration, we estimate the total downtime for migration per server to be less than 10 minutes in most cases. However, the exact downtime depends on the size and change rate of your existing MySQL Database on Azure instances.</li>
										<li>Migration will begin on Feb 15th, 2019.</li>
										<li>Special pricing will be lost when scaled to a different service tier or if server is deleted.</li>
										<li>You will continue to pay the same price post migration. Detailed information about the SKU mapping between the old service and the new service will be published before end of December 2018.</li>
										<li>There is no action necessary for now. At a minimum, 30 days prior to your scheduled migration, you will receive additional notifications including the exact timeline for your migration.</li>
										</ul>
										<p>If you are a new customer:</p>
										<ul>
										<li>You will not be accepted on the “MySQL Database on Azure” service as of the date of this announcement</li>
										</ul>
										<p>Please refer to <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/support/faq#implementationAndMaintenance">MySQL Database on Azure Migration FAQs</a> for the most common questions related to this migration</p>
									</section>
								</div>
							</li>
					       	<li>
								<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november-support-plans"><span>11/16</span>Azure Support Plan Notification</a>
									<section>
										<p>We will be offering our new support plan from December 15. To deliver better experiences with Azure, we will continue to offer technical support services free-of-charge for enterprises. Customers who signed up for 21Vianet's Online Service Standard Agreement (OSSA) within the period of validity of your Azure agreement will get the “Developer” Support Plan. Customers who signed up for 21Vianet's Online Service Premier Agreement (OSPA) within the period of validity of your Azure agreement will get the “Standard” Support Plan. If you run business-critical workloads on Azure and would like to access services to satisfy the below needs, you may choose the paid “enterprise-tier” Premier Support Plan. Please contact your account manager for more details concerning purchase and use of “enterprise-tier” support plans.</p>
										<ul>
											<li>Designated service delivery manager committed to improve your Azure experience.</li>
											<li>Highest priority reactive support to help ensure business continuity of your services.</li>
										</ul>
										<p>Please click<a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/support/plans/">here</a> for more details of support plans.</p>
										<p>In addition, adjusted phone service hours are from 9am to 9pm, Monday-Sunday since Dec 1st, 2018. For frequently asked questions on Azure, we recommend you get answers to your questions fast through <a href="https://support.azure.cn/zh-cn/support/support-azure/">Online Customer Service</a> or WeChat Official Accounts (Azure Cloud Technical Support).</p>
									</section>
								</div>
							</li>
				       </ul>
            	 <h3>October 2018</h3>
				       <ul>
					       	<li>
								<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-october-privacy-statement"><span>10/31</span>We have updated our Privacy Statement for Online Services</a>
									<section>
										<p>Your privacy is of critical importance to us. We strive to protect your personal information. Therefore, we have updated our Privacy Statement and would like to share the updates with you. The updates takes effect as from today.</p>
										<p>In particular, we have combined the Privacy Statements of Azure and Office 365 and made adjustments as shown below:</p>
										<p>1. Enhanced your rights to your personal information</p>
										<ul>
											<li>Further strengthened your control over your personal information, including your right to know, right to choose, right of revocation and right to amend.</li>
											<li>Clarified the principles such as storage constraints so as to ensure information will be deleted immediately following the end of the lifecycle or your personal information will be anonymized and etc.</li>
											<li>Introduced our protection mechanism for your personal information, including protection for the personal information of minors.</li>
											<li>Clarified that we would obtain your consent in advance with regards to the use of your personal information for purposes not covered by this privacy policy.</li>
										</ul>
										<p>2. A more transparent approach in introducing how your personal data would be processed</p>
										<ul>
											<li>Clarified the boundaries of “personal information” and “sensitive personal information” and explained to you the scenarios that might involve “personal information” when 21Vianet Online Services collects and uses your information.</li>
											<li>Covered a series of scenarios with regards to our collection of personal information. For example, we would collect your personal information through the process of real-name authentication when you use 21Vianet Online Services. In addition, we would also collect your personal information through websites and marketing activities.</li>
											<li>Introduced how we would share your personal information, including sharing with external subjects.</li>
										</ul>
										<p>We encourage you to read the full Privacy Statement and understand the updates we made. If you have any questions or thoughts, please contact us through<a href="https://www.azure.cn/support/contact/"> Azure support</a>.</p>
										<p>Read<a id="service-fabric_year_2018-october_support-privacy-statement" href="/support/legal/privacy-statement/">full Privacy Statement</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
							</li>
				       </ul>
				<h3>August 2018</h3>
            	 <ul>
            	 	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div><a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-august-linux">Risk Warning: Linux denial of service vulnerability</a><section>
								<p>8/15: Another security vulnerability called “FragmentSmack” (<a href="https://www.kb.cert.org/vuls/id/641765">CVE-2018-5391</a>) also leads to denial of service (DoS) of Linux operating system. We have taken proper protective measures to ensure Microsoft cloud platform’s customers (Azure and Microsoft 365) free from the affection of this vulnerability. You do not need to take any immediate protective actions. However, as a best practice, we still recommend that you regularly consult each Linux distribution provider to install the latest updates for Linux Virtual Machines running on the Azure platform. You can consult each Linux distribution provider for more information on Linux security vulnerabilities.</p>
								<p>8/7: We noticed that a newly disclosed security vulnerability (<a target="_blank" href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-5390">CVE-2018-5390</a>) may cause the Linux operating system to temporarily fall into a “Denial of Service (DoS)” state. Virtual Machines running the Linux operating system may be vulnerable to this attack, but Azure hosting platform will not be affected. We are currently working with numerous Linux distribution providers to help them address this security issue. Please contact each Linux distribution provider for guidance on how to address the <a target="_blank"  href="https://cve.mitre.org/cgi-bin/cvename.cgi?name=CVE-2018-5390">CVE-2018-5390</a> security vulnerability. For more information on this vulnerability, please visit the Vulnerability Notes Database at <a target="_blank" href="https://www.kb.cert.org/vuls/id/962459">https://www.kb.cert.org/vuls/id/962459</a>.</p>
								<p>We will continue to update this security notice as the case progresses.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
            	 </ul>
            	 <h3>July 2018</h3>
            	 <ul>
            	 	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div><a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july-php-minor"><span>7/16</span>PHP minor version + Xdebug update notifications</a><section>
								<p>In August 2018, Azure App Services will stack update PHP to the latest version. For information about changes in the latest version, please see the change logs on the PHP website.</p>
								<table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
			                        <tr>
			                            <th align="left"><strong>PHP Versions</strong></th>
			                            <th align="left"><strong>Change Logs</strong></th>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>7.1.19</td>
			                            <td><a target="_blank" href="http://www.php.net/ChangeLog-7.php#7.1.19" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_php#7.1.19">http://www.php.net/ChangeLog-7.php#7.1.19</a></td>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>7.2.7</td>
			                            <td><a target="_blank" href="http://www.php.net/ChangeLog-7.php#7.2.7" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_php#7.2.7">http://www.php.net/ChangeLog-7.php#7.2.7</a></td>
			                        </tr>
			                    </table>
			                    <p>We will also update the Xdebug binary files, which will include adding Xdebug support for PHP versions 7.1 and 7.2.</p>
			                    <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
			                        <tr>
			                            <th align="left"><strong>PHP Versions</strong></th>
			                            <th align="left"><strong>Xdebug Path</strong></th>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>5.6</td>
			                            <td>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.5.5\php_5.6\php_xdebug-2.5.5-5.6-vc11-nts.dll</td>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>7.0 x86</td>
			                            <td>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.6.0\php_7.0\php_xdebug-2.6.0-7.0-vc14-nts.dll</td>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>7.0 x64</td>
			                            <td>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.6.0\php_7.0\php_xdebug-2.6.0-7.0-vc14-nts-x86_64.dll</td>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>7.1 x86 (new)</td>
			                            <td>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.6.0\php_7.1\php_xdebug-2.6.0-7.1-vc14-nts.dll</td>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>7.1 x64 (new)</td>
			                            <td>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.6.0\php_7.1\php_xdebug-2.6.0-7.1-vc14-nts-x86_64.dll</td>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>7.2 x86 (new)</td>
			                            <td>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.6.0\php_7.2\php_xdebug-2.6.0-7.2-vc15-nts.dll</td>
			                        </tr>
			                        <tr>
			                            <td>7.2 x64 (new)</td>
			                            <td>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.6.0\php_7.2\php_xdebug-2.6.0-7.2-vc15-nts-x86_64.dll</td>
			                        </tr>
			                    </table>
			                    <p>Please note that the paths for xdebug.dll will be updated to the paths in the image above. We will delete the old xdebug.dll paths, including:</p>
			                    <p>Xdebug paths to be deleted:</p>
			                    <p>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.4.0\php_5.4\php_xdebug-2.4.0-5.4-vc9-nts.dll</p>
			                    <p>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.4.0\php_5.5\php_xdebug-2.4.0-5.5-vc11-nts.dll</p>
			                    <p>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.4.0\php_5.6\php_xdebug-2.4.0-5.6-vc11-nts.dll</p>
			                    <p>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.4.0\php_7.0\php_xdebug-2.4.0-7.0-vc14-nts-x86_64.dll</p>
			                    <p>D:\devtools\xdebug\2.4.0\php_7.0\php_xdebug-2.4.0-7.0-vc14-nts.dll</p>
			                    <p>For more information about how to use the right version of Xdebug for your version of PHP, see the <a target="_blank" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_ms-blog-troubleshooting-php-performance-in-microsoft-azure-web-sites-with-xdebug" href="//blogs.msdn.microsoft.com/waws/2014/04/04/troubleshooting-php-performance-in-microsoft-azure-web-sites-with-xdebug/">Xdebug Blog</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
            	 </ul>
            	
                <h1>Product Update</h1>
                <a href="#" id="new_control_bexpend" class="folded-link"><em>Expand All</em></a>
                <h3>July 2019</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-july-time-series-insights"><span>7/2</span>Azure Time Series Insights has now been officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Time Series Insights is a managed analytics and visualization service that democratizes the Internet of Things (IoT) by making it simple to explore and analyze your IoT time series data. It lets you quickly validate your IoT solution and avoid downtime to mission-critical devices by helping you discover hidden trends, spot anomalies, and conduct root-cause analyses in near real-time. It also offers up to 400 days of real-time analytics and storage of time series data, helping organizations to spot and understand longer-term trends in their IoT data. It provides powerful data exploration and telemetry tools to help you improve operational analysis.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/time-series-insights/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-features-time-series-insights">Azure Time Series Insights Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/time-series-insights/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-pricing-time-series-insights">Azure Time Series Insights Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/time-series-insights/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-docs-time-series-insights">Azure Time Series Insights Documentation</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-july-expressroute"><span>7/1</span>Shanghai Telecom and Beijing Telecom are providing the ExpressRoute connectivity service in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers respectively<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>You can contact Shanghai Telecom and Beijing Telecom to establish an ExpressRoute private network connection in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers. ExpressRoute connections don't go over the public internet, and offer more reliability, faster speeds, and lower latencies than internet connections.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/expressroute/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-features-expressroute">ExpressRoute Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/expressroute/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-pricing-expressroute">ExpressRoute Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/expressroute/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-docs-expressroute">ExpressRoute Documentation</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-july-pricing-drop"><span>7/1</span>Data inbound traffic, Virtual Machines, CDN, Cosmos DB, and Storage services discount<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>Since July 1, 2019, data inbound traffic, Virtual Machines, CDN, Cosmos DB, and Storage services have been reduced in price.</p>
								<p>Data inbound traffic is free of charge. To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/pricing/details/bandwidth/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-pricing-bandwidth">Azure Data Transfer Price Details</a> page.</p>
								<p>Azure virtual machine prices lower up to 73%. To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/virtual-machines/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-features-virtual-machines">Azure Virtual Machines Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/virtual-machines/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-pricing-virtual-machines">Azure Virtual Machines Price Details </a>page.</p>
								<p>Content Delivery Network (CDN) prices lower up to 41%. To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/cdn/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-features-cdn">Content Delivery Network (CDN) Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/cdn/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-pricing-cdn">Content Delivery Network (CDN) Price Details</a> page.</p>
								<p>Azure Cosmos DB prices lower up to 38%. To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/cosmos-db/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-features-cosmos-db">Azure Cosmos DB Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/cosmos-db/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-pricing-cosmos-db">Azure Cosmos DB Price Details</a>page.</p>
								<p>Storage prices lower up to 21%. To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/storage/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-features-storage">Storage Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/storage/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-july-pricing-storage">Storage Price Details</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>June 2019</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-media-services"><span>6/28</span>Azure Media Services has now been officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Media Services is a cloud-based media workflow platform that enables developers to build scalable media management and delivery applications. Azure Media Services makes it easy to use high-definition video encoding and streaming services to reach your audiences on today’s most popular devices. You can build end-to-end media workflows, securely upload, store, encode, and package video or audio content for both on-demand and live streaming delivery to various clients (for example, TV, PC, and mobile devices).</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/media-services/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-media-services">Azure Media Services Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/media-services/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-media-services">Azure Media Services Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/media-services/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-media-services">Azure Media Services Documentation</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-data-explorer"><span>6/27</span>Azure Data Explorer officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Data Explorer is a highly scalable and secure data analysis service that can analyze mass data streamed from applications, websites and IoT devices in real time. Ask questions and dynamically browse data in an iterative way to improve products, customer experiences, monitor devices, and support operations. Quickly identify patterns, anomalies, and trends in data, discover new issues and get answers in minutes. Azure Data Explorer makes it simple to ingest this data and enables you to perform complex ad hoc queries on the data in seconds.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/data-explorer/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-data-explorer">Azure Data Explorer Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/data-explorer/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-data-explorer">Azure Data Explorer Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/data-explorer/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-data-explorer">Azure Data Explorer Documentation</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-monitor"><span>6/26</span>Azure Application Insights has now been officially released in the China East 2 data center</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Application Insights, as a part of Azure Monitor, is an extensible Application Performance Management (APM) service for web developers on multiple platforms. It can monitor your live web application and automatically detect performance anomalies. It includes powerful analytics tools to help you diagnose issues and to understand what users actually do with your app. It's designed to help you continuously improve performance and usability. It works for apps on a wide variety of platforms including .NET, Node.js and Java EE, hosted on-premises, hybrid, or any public cloud.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/monitor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-monitor">Azure Application Insights Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/monitor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-monitor">Azure Application Insights Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/azure-monitor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-monitor">Azure Application Insights Documentation</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-security-center"><span>6/25</span>Azure Security Center officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Security Center provides comprehensive security management and advanced threat protection across hybrid cloud workloads, helping customers protect workloads running locally and in Azure from network threats. With Azure’s global threat intelligence and expertise, it automatically collects and analyze security-related events in Azure deployment to identify immediate threats and reduce false positives, providing quick fix solutions.</p>
								
								<p>To understand more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/security-center/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-security-center">Azure Security Center Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/security-center/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-security-center">Azure Security Center Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/security-center/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-security-center">Azure Security Center Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-data-factory"><span>6/25</span>Azure Data Factory officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Data Factory is a cloud-based data integration service that allows you to create data-driven workflows in the cloud for orchestrating and automating data movement and data transformation. Easily construct ETL and ELT processes code-free within the intuitive visual environment, or write your own code. Visually integrate data sources using more than 80 natively built and maintenance-free connectors at no added cost. Focus on your data—the serverless integration service does the rest.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/data-factory/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-language-understanding-intelligent-service">Azure Data Factory Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/data-factory/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-data-factory">Azure Data Factory Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/data-factory/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-data-factory">Azure Data Factory Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-language-understanding-intelligent-service"><span>6/24</span>Azure Cognitive Services Language Understanding API standard officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>The Text Request feature of Azure Cognitive Services Language Understanding API standard has been officially released. Applications can understand a user's conversational, natural language text, predict overall meaning, and pull out relevant, detailed information. A client application for LUIS is any conventional application that communicates with a user in natural language to complete a task. Examples of client applications include social media apps, chat bots, and speech-enabled desktop applications.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/language-understanding-intelligent-service/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-language-understanding-intelligent-service">Language Understanding API Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/cognitive-services/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-language-understanding-intelligent-service">Language Understanding API Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/luis/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-language-understanding-intelligent-service">Language Understanding API Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-hdinsight"><span>6/13</span>Azure HDInsight Av2 Series and Ev3 Series officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure HDInsight is a fully-managed cloud service that makes it easy, fast, and cost-effective to process massive amounts of data. The Av2 Series now officially released runs on the latest Av2 standard virtual machines, with the same CPU performance but faster disk speed. The Ev3 Series runs on Ev3 standard virtual machines and can achieve cache throughout and local disk throughput of up to 128,000 IOPS at 1024MBps (using 32 data disks).</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/hdinsight/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-hdinsight">Azure HDInsight Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/hdinsight/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-hdinsight">Azure HDInsight Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit<a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/hdinsight/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-hdinsight"> Azure HDInsight Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-mariadb"><span>6/12</span>Azure Database for MariaDB has now been officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Database for MariaDB is a relational database service based on the open-source MariaDB Server engine. It is a fully managed community version of MariaDB that can be used by enterprises. The service has characteristics of open-source compatibility, built-in high availability, dynamic scaling and flexible pricing. With MariaDB Community Version, you can create scalable computing and storage resources using popular open-source frameworks, tools and languages. Azure Database for MariaDB makes it easy and fast to build smart applications.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/mariadb/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-mariadb">Azure Database for MariaDB Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/mariadb/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-mariadb">Azure Database for MariaDB Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/mariadb/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-mariadb">Azure Database for MariaDB Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-sql-database"><span>6/11</span>Azure SQL Database Managed Instance preview released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure SQL Database Managed Instance provides the broadest SQL Server engine compatibility and native virtual network support so you can migrate a large number of SQL Server databases from on-premises or virtual machines to SQL Database Managed Instance without changing your apps. Managed Instance combines rich SQL Server interface areas with fully managed service operations. It also retains all PaaS functions (automatic patching, version update, automatic backup, and high availability) and can significantly reduce management overhead and total cost of ownership.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/sql-database/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-sql-database">Azure SQL Database Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/sql-database/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-sql-database">Azure SQL Database Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/sql-database/sql-database-managed-instance-quickstart-guide/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-sql-database-managed-instance-quickstart-guide">Azure SQL Database Managed Instance Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-june-azure-cache-for-redis"><span>6/4</span>Azure Cache for Redis Premium tier P5 officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Cache for Redis is a distributed memory management cache based on open source software Redis. It can improve the system performance and scalability of back-end data storage, and temporarily copy frequently accessed data to fast storage close to applications. With the characteristics of higher cache performance, larger workload supported, and disaster recovery capability, it is specially designed for maximum scale and enterprise integration. The officially released Premium tier P5 has a cache size of 120GB and the customer connections can reach 40,000.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/cache/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-features-azure-cache-for-redis">Azure Cache for Redis Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/cache/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-pricing-azure-cache-for-redis">Azure Cache for Redis Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/azure-cache-for-redis/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-june-docs-azure-cache-for-redis">Azure Cache for Redis Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>May 2019</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-may-30-active-directory-b2c"><span>5/30</span>Azure Active Directory B2C preview released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Active Directory B2C is a cloud identity service built on Azure Active Directory platform. It authenticates with popular social identity providers in China (such as Weibo, WeChat and QQ) through multi-tenant and cloud service support. It is application-oriented, highly available global identity management service that can be extended to hundreds of millions of identities. It can be easily integrated across mobile and Web platforms, and your customers can log in to applications using existing social accounts or creating new authentication information through a fully customizable experience.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/active-directory-b2c/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-30-features-active-directory-b2c">Azure Active Directory B2C Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/active-directory-b2c/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-30-pricing-active-directory-b2c">Azure Active Directory B2C Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/active-directory-b2c/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-30-docs-active-directory-b2c">Azure Active Directory B2C Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-may-27-sql-database"><span>5/27</span>The preview version of Azure SQL Database serverless computing released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure SQL Database serverless computing has optimized its price performance and simplified the performance management of intermittent and unpredictable database. According to the requirement of workload, the auto scaling of single database computing is available and the used computing is charged on a basis of second. During periods of inactivity, the computing is automatically suspended (only storage is charged at this time) and automatically resumed when the activity returns. Users will focus on building applications more quickly and efficiently due to serverless. Like all databases in SQL databases, serverless databases provide high availability and benefit from built-in intelligence for security and performance optimization.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/sql-database/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-27-features-sql-database">Azure SQL Database Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/sql-database/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-27-pricing-sql-database">Azure SQL Database Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/sql-database/sql-database-serverless" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-27-docs-sql-database-serverless">Azure SQL Database Serverless Compute Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-may-aks"><span>5/24</span>21Vianet Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) official version released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) manages your hosted Kubernetes environment, making it quick and easy to deploy and manage containerized applications without container orchestration expertise. It also eliminates the burden of ongoing operations and maintenance by provisioning, upgrading, and scaling resources on demand, without taking your applications offline.</p>
								
								<p>To understand more about this service, please visit<a href="/home/features/kubernetes-service/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-aks"> Azure Kubernetes Feature</a> page. Please contact 21Vianet sales or distributors for technical support and offer plan details of Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) in China. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/aks/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-docs-aks">Azure Kubernetes Service Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-language-understanding-intelligent-service"><span>5/17</span>The free version of Azure Cognitive Services Language Understanding API officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Language Understanding API is one of Azure Cognitive Services. You can build your own self-defined language model to make any program or robot understand your command and execute corresponding operation. Powerful developer tools are combined with customizable pre-built apps and entity dictionaries, such as Calendar, Music, and Devices, so you can build and deploy a solution more quickly. Dictionaries are mined from the collective knowledge of the web and supply billions of entries, helping your model to correctly identify valuable information from user conversations.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/language-understanding-intelligent-service/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-features-language-understanding-intelligent-service">Language Understanding API Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/cognitive-services/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-pricing-language-understanding-intelligent-service">Language Understanding API Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/luis/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-docs-language-understanding-intelligent-service">Language Understanding API Document</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-may-sql-database"><span>5/13</span>The Azure SQL Database hyperscale service tier Gen5 has now been officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
							<section>
								<p>The Azure SQL Database hyperscale service tier is the latest service tier in the vCore-based purchase models, which can be adjusted on demand according to workload requirements. Each database can be quickly and automatically scaled to 100 TB, eliminating the demand for provisioning storage resources, while significantly tapping the potential of application growth to keep it from being limited by the storage size. This new service tier can also scale computing and storage resources independently, giving the flexibility to optimize workload performance. Azure SQL Database is massive and can be used for a single database deployment.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/sql-database/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-features-sql-database">Azure SQL Database Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/sql-database/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-pricing-sql-database">Azure SQL Database Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/sql-database/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-docs-sql-database">Azure SQL Database Document</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-may-ip-addresses"><span>5/9</span>The Azure public IP prefix officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>The public IP prefix is a service in the public IP address. It is a reserved range of IP addresses for your public endpoints in Azure. You can use prefixes to simplify IP address management in Azure. You can change the firewall rules knowing the address range in advance and no longer need to assign IP addresses to new resources. With address prediction, you can dramatically reduce management overhead when scaling in Azure.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and its pricing, please visit <a href="/pricing/details/ip-addresses/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-pricing-ip-addresses">Public IP Address Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-network/virtual-network-public-ip-address" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-docs-virtual-network-public-ip-address">Public IP Address Document</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-may-managed-disks"><span>5/5</span>Azure Managed Disks Large Capacity Disks have now been officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Managed Disks is a service that is designed and controlled by Azure for virtual disk files (VHDs) and storage accounts used by virtual machines.</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Premium Managed Disks are high performance Solid State Drive (SSD) based Storage designed to support I/O intensive workloads with significantly high throughput and low latency. Premium Managed Disks types P60, P70, and P80 (with disk size of 8TB, 16TB, and 32TB respectively) have now been officially released.</li>
									<li>Standard SSD Managed Disks, a low-cost SSD offering, are optimized for test and entry-level production workloads requiring consistent latency. Standard SSD Managed Disks types E60, E70, and E80 (with disk size of 8TB, 16TB, and 32TB respectively) have now been officially released.</li>
									<li>Standard Managed Disks use Hard Disk Drive (HDD) based Storage media. They are best suited for dev/test and other infrequent access workloads that are less sensitive to performance variability. Standard Managed Disks types S60, S70, and S80 (with disk size of 8TB, 16TB, and 32TB respectively) have now been officially released.</li>
								</ul>

								<p>To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/storage/managed-disks/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-features-managed-disks">Azure Managed Disks Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/storage/managed-disks/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-pricing-managed-disks">Azure Managed Disks Price Details </a>page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/linux/managed-disks-overview/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-may-docs-managed-disks-overview">Azure Managed Disks Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
				<h3>April 2019</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-april-virtual-machines"><span>4/23</span>Azure Virtual Machines SUSE Linux Enterprise Server Basic and SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP Priority officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>SUSE Linux Enterprise Server (SLES) is the world's leading modular operating system for secure open source servers and the first supported Enterprise Linux distribution on Azure. Its tuned kernel provides faster access to new and upcoming Azure features, helping users become more agile. SUSE Linux Enterprise Server Basic is the base version, and SUSE Linux Enterprise Server for SAP Priority provides the following key features:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Automatic failover of the SAP HANA database;</li>
									<li>Page cache limits able to maintain SAP application performance;</li>
									<li>Built-in high availability cluster to reduce downtime;</li>
									<li>Full system rollback, including service pack updates, to quickly recover errors;</li>
									<li>Linux container with Docker for automated application deployment</li>
								</ul>

								<p>To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/virtual-machines/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-features-virtual-machines">Azure Virtual Machines Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/virtual-machines/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-pricing-virtual-machines">Price Details </a>page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-docs-virtual-machines">Azure Virtual Machines Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-april-iothub"><span>4/18</span>The Azure IoT Hub Device Provisioning Service officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
							<section>
								<p>The Azure IoT Hub Device Provisioning Service, one of the features of Azure IoT Hub, allows you to make zero-touch device configurations for your Azure IoT Hub. With this feature, you can securely provision and register IoT devices on a large scale. The design of the Azure IoT Hub Device Provisioning Service takes supply chain challenges into full consideration and offers the infrastructure required to configure millions of devices in a secure and scalable manner.</p>

								<p>Azure IoT Hub Device Provisioning Service has now been officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers. To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/zh-cn/home/features/iot-hub/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-features-iot-hub">Azure IoT Hub Feature page</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/iot-hub/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-pricing-iot-hub">Price Details page</a>. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/iot-dps/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-docs-iot-hub">Azure IoT Hub Device Provisioning Service Document page</a>.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-april-hdinsight"><span>4/17</span>Azure HDInsight now officially released in China East 2 data center</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure HDInsight is a fully-managed cloud service that makes it easy, fast, and cost-effective to process massive amounts of data. Use popular open-source frameworks such as Hadoop, Spark, Hive, LLAP, Kafka, Storm, HBase, and more. Azure HDInsight enables a broad range of scenarios such as ETL, Data Warehousing, IoT, and more.</p>

								<p>Azure HDInsight Linux has now been officially released in China East 2 data center. To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/hdinsight/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-features-hdinsight">Azure HDInsight Services Feature page</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/hdinsight/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-pricing-hdinsight">Price Details page</a>. For more details, please visit<a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/hdinsight/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-docs-hdinsight"> Azure HDInsight Document page</a>.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-april-advisor"><span>4/10</span>Azure Advisor officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Advisor is a free, personalized cloud consulting product that helps you follow best practices to optimize your Azure deployments. It analyzes your resource configuration and usage telemetry, and then recommends solutions that help you to increase  cost-effectiveness, performance, and availability of Azure resources. Azure Advisor allows you to obtain the following workable recommendations:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>High availability: Safeguards and improves the continuity of business-critical apps;</li>
									<li>Performance: Increases the speed of apps;</li>
									<li>Cost: Optimizes and reduces overall Azure expenditure.</li>
								</ul>

								<p>Azure Advisor has now been officially released. For more information about this service, please visit the <a href="/home/features/advisor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-features-advisor">Azure Advisor Service Functions</a> page. For more detailed information, visit the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/advisor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-docs-advisor">Azure Advisor Documents</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-april-container-registry"><span>4/5</span>Azure Container Registry officially released in China East and China North data centers</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Container Registry provides a hosted Docker registration service for storing and managing private container images. Azure Container Registry can work along with the existing container development and deployment channels. You can generate a container image in Azure using the Azure Container Registry Build. The source code submission and base image update can be used to generate triggers on demand as needed or fully automatically.</p>
								<p>Azure Container Registry has been officially released in China East and China North data centers. To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/container-registry/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-features-container-registry">Container Registry Service Feature</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/container-registry/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-pricing-container-registry">Container Registry Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/container-registry/"   id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-docs-container-registry">Azure Container Registry Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-april-translator-text-api"><span>4/2</span>Translator Text API officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>The Translator Text API is a neural machine translation service that developers can easily integrate into their applications websites, tools, or any solution requiring multi-language support such as website localization, e-commerce, customer support, messaging applications, internal communication, and more. It can be used to translate text in near real-time through a simple REST API call. It allows you to add multi-language user experiences in <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/translator/language-support/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-docs-language-support">more than 60 languages</a>, and can be used on any hardware platform with any operating system for text-to-text language translation.</p>
								<p>The Translator Text API is part of the <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/"  id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-features-cognitive-services">Azure Cognitive Services API</a> collection, and is readily consumable in your development projects.</p>
								<p>The Translator Text API has now been officially released. To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/translator-text-api/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-features-translator-text-api">Translator Text API Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/cognitive-services/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-pricing-cognitive-services">Translator Text API Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/translator/"   id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-docs-translator">Translator Text API Documentation</a>.</P>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-april-cdn"><span>4/1</span>Azure CDN for China regions with global coverage officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure CDN improves application performance by caching content to the location nearest the customer. CDN stands for content delivery network. Virtually all large-scale websites use the Content Delivery Network technology today, but the technology is by no means exclusive to large websites. The basic purpose of the network is to avoid bottlenecks and other parts of the Internet that could affect data transfer rates and stability, to make content transfers faster and more stable. By placing node servers in different places across the network and building a more intelligent layer of virtual networks by using the Internet as a foundation, Content Delivery Network systems can redirect user requests in real time to the service node closest to the user based on the status of network traffic and node connections and loads, as well as overall information on distance to the user and response times.</p>
								<p>Content Delivery Network Standard Plus for Zone 1 and Standard with global coverage for Zone 2 have now been officially released. To understand more about this service, please visit <a href="/home/features/cdn/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-features-cdn">Content Delivery Network Feature page</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/cdn/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-pricing-cdn">Content Delivery Network Price Details page</a>. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cdn/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-april-docs-cdn">Content Delivery Network Documentation page</a>.</P>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>March 2019</h3>
				
				<ul>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-march-monitor"><span>3/11</span>Alert rules feature of Azure Monitor officially released in China East and China North data centers</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Monitor is a platform function used to monitor and control Azure resources. Azure Monitor allows you to gather detailed performance and usage data, activity and diagnostic logs, and notifications, in a consistent way. You can use Azure portal to view and analyze monitoring data and set up alert-based automated actions. Alerts proactively notify you when important conditions are found in your monitoring data. They allow you to identify and address issues before the users of your system notice them.</p>
								<p>Alert rules are separated from alerts and the action that are taken when an alert fires.</p>
								<P>The alert rule captures the target and criteria for alerting. The alert rule can be in an enabled or a disabled state. Alerts only fire when enabled.</P>
								<P>The key attributes of an alert rule are: target resource, signal, criteria, alert name, alert description, severity, and action.</P>
								<P>To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/monitor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-features-monitor">Azure Monitor Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/monitor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-pricing-monitor">Azure Monitor Price Details </a>page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/azure-monitor/platform/alerts-overview/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-docs-azure-monitor">Azure Monitor Documentation page</a>.</P>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-march-kubernetes-service"><span>3/8</span>21Vianet Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) public preview version released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) manages your hosted Kubernetes environment, making it quick and easy to deploy and manage containerized applications without container orchestration expertise. It also eliminates the burden of ongoing operations and maintenance by provisioning, upgrading, and scaling resources on demand, without taking your applications offline.</p>

								<p>To understand more about this service, please visit<a href="//azure.microsoft.com/zh-cn/services/kubernetes-service/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-features-kubernetes-service"> Azure Kubernetes Feature</a> page. Please contact 21Vianet sales or distributors for technical support and offer plan details of Azure Kubernetes Service (AKS) in China.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-march-virtual-machines"><span>3/4</span>Azure Virtual Machines M-series officially released in China North 2 data center</a>
							<section>
								<p>The Azure Virtual Machines M Series – the VM that offers the highest performance so far – are now officially released in China North 2 data center. Optimized for large in-memory workloads (such as SAP HANA) and provisioned with large RAM and vCPU capabilities, the new M Series VM can cope with the harshest environments. The M Series can support up to 128 virtual CPUs (vCPU) and 1 to 3.8 TiB of RAM. In addition, such VM instances support premium storage and can handle largest enterprise workloads.</p>

								<p>The new M Series are also integrated with accelerated networking and support VM-to-VM data transmission at a speed up to 30 GB/s (Gbps). It is therefore very suitable for ultra-fast real-time database replication and backup, where you no longer have to worry about the issue of rapidly growing space in your cloud environment.</p>

								<p>To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/virtual-machines/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-features-virtual-machines">Azure Virtual Machines Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/virtual-machines/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-pricing-virtual-machines">Price Details </a>page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-docs-virtual-machines">Azure Virtual Machines Documentation</a> page.</p>

							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-march-azure-azure-cognitive-services-text-analytics-api"><span>3/1</span>The standard version of Azure Cognitive Services Text Analytics API officially released</a>
									<section>
										<p>The Text Analytics API is a cloud-based service that provides advanced natural language processing over raw text, and includes four main functions: sentiment analysis, key phrase extraction, language detection, and entity linking.</p>
										<p>The API is backed by resources in Microsoft Cognitive Services, a collection of machine learning and AI algorithms in the cloud, readily consumable in your development projects.</p>
										<p>The standard version of Azure Cognitive Services Text Analytics API has now been officially released. For more information on this feature and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/text-analytics/">Text Analytics API Feature page</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/cognitive-services/">Price Details page</a>. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/Text-Analytics/">Text Analytics API Documentation</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li>
						<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-march-azure-cognitive-services-content-moderator-api"><span>3/1</span>The standard version of Azure Cognitive Services Content Moderator API officially released</a>
									<section>
										<p>The Azure Content Moderator API is a cognitive service that checks text, image, and video content for material that is potentially offensive, risky, or otherwise undesirable. When such material is found, the service applies appropriate labels (flags) to the content. Your app can then handle flagged content in order to comply with regulations or maintain the intended environment for users.</p>
										<p>The standard version of Azure Cognitive Services Content Moderator API has now been officially released. For more information on this feature and its pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/content-moderator/">Content Moderator API Feature page</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/cognitive-services/">Price Details page</a>. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/content-moderator/">Content Moderator API Documentation</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-march-cosmosdb"><span>3/1</span>Azure Cosmos DB Multi-Master support official released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Cosmos DB is a globally distributed, multi-model database service that supports document, key/value pairs, wide-column, and graph databases. With the click of a button, Cosmos DB enables you to elastically and independently scale throughput and storage across any number of Azure's geographic regions and take advantage of fast, single-digit-millisecond data access using your favorite API among SQL, MongoDB, Cassandra, Tables, or Gremlin. With multi-master, Azure Cosmos DB delivers a single digit millisecond write latency at the 99th percentile anywhere in the world, and now offers 99.999 percent write availability (in addition to 99.999 percent read availability) backed by the industry-leading <a href="/support/sla/cosmos-db/">SLAs</a>, providing throughput, latency, availability, and consistency guarantees, something no other database service can offer.</p>
								<p>Azure Cosmos DB Multi-Master support is now official released. To learn more about Azure Cosmos DB, please visit <a href="/home/features/cosmos-db/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-features-cosmos-db">Azure Cosmos DB Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/cosmos-db/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-pricing-cosmos-db">Azure Cosmos DB Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cosmos-db/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-docs-cosmos-db">Azure Cosmos DB Document page</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-march-log-analytics"><span>3/1</span>Log Analytics of Azure Monitor officially released in China East 2 data center</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Log Analytics is part of the Azure Monitor. It collects telemetry from a variety of sources and uses the query language used by Azure Data Explorer to retrieve and analyze data.</p>
								<p>Azure Log Analytics is now officially released in China East 2 data center. To learn more about Log Analytics, please visit <a href="/home/features/monitor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-features_monitor">Azure Monitor Feature </a>page and <a href="/pricing/details/monitor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-pricing-monitor">Azure Monitor Price Details </a>page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/azure-monitor/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-march-docs-monitor">Azure Monitor Document page</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>February 2019</h3>
				<ul>
					<!-- <li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-feb-reids-premium-p5"><span>2/1</span>用于 Redis 的 Azure 缓存高级版P5現已正式发布<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
									<section>
										<p>借助"用于 Redis 的 Azure 缓存"，你将能够使用安全的开源 Redis 缓存。Azure Redis 缓存是由 Azure 托管的专用服务，可通过向你提供对数据的超高速访问来生成高度可扩展且高度可响应的应用程序。你还可以利用 Redis 提供的丰富功能集和生态系统，同时可以从 Azure 获得可靠的承载和监视。</p>
										<p>用于 Redis 的 Azure 缓存高级版 P5 現已正式发布。要了解此功能及定价的信息，请访问用于 Redis 的 Azure 缓存<a href="https://www.azure.cn/home/features/cache/">服务功能页面</a>和<a href="https://www.azure.cn/pricing/details/cache">价格详情页面</a>。更多详细信息请访问<a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/azure-cache-for-redis/">用于 Redis 的 Azure 缓存文档</a>。</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li> -->
						<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
							<div>
								<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-feb-storage-tiers"><span>2/15</span>Azure Archive Storage officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
								<section>
									<p>Azure Storage offers different storage tiers, which allow you to store Blob object data in the most cost-effective manner. The available tiers include Hot storage, Cool storage, and Archive storage. Archive storage has the lowest storage cost and higher data retrieval costs compared to Hot and Cool storage. This tier is intended for data that can tolerate several hours of retrieval latency and will remain in the Archive tier for at least 180 days. Archive storage enables data at rest automatically encrypted, and provides seamless integration with hot and cool storage tiers.</p>
									<p>Azure Archive Storage is officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers. To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/storage/archive">Azure Archive Storage Service Feature </a>page and <a href="/pricing/details/storage/blobs/">Price Details </a>page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/storage/blobs/storage-blob-storage-tiers/">Azure Archive Storage Document page</a>.</p>
								</section>
							</div>
						</li>
						<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
							<div>
								<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-feb-storage"><span>2/14</span>Azure Data Lake Storage Gen2 now officially released</a>
								<section>
									<p>Azure Data Lake Storage Gen2 is an uncompromising data lake platform that combines a wide variety of advanced data lake solution feature sets as well as the economy, global scale and enterprise-level security of Azure Blob Storage.</p>

									<p>ADLS Gen2 has introduced many powerful features to the market:</p>
									<ul>
										<li>It adopts a storage model boasting the same low cost as Azure Blob Storage.</li>
										<li>It is tightly integrated with Azure SQL Data Warehouse to speed up development of end-to-end analysis workflows.</li>
										<li>It will support Azure Blob Storage functions, including object layering, lifecycle policy management and high availability/disaster recovery data redundancy.</li>
										<li>It provides a highly performing HDFS compatible file system, supports atomic operations and can reach a throughput up to 1 TB/s.</li>
										<li>It supports Common Data Service data storage through Power BI or SQL Data Warehouse.</li>
										<li>It features global network support by big data analysis partners and system integrators.</li>
									</ul>
									<p>Azure Data Lake Storage Gen2 is now officially released. To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/storage/data-lake-storage/">Azure Data Lake Storage Gen2 Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/storage/data-lake">Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/storage/blobs/data-lake-storage-introduction">Azure Data Lake Storage Gen2 Documentation</a> page.</p>
								</section>
							</div>
						</li>
					<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-feb-IoT-Hub-GA-in-new-regions"><span>2/1</span> Azure IoT Hub is officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
									<section>
										<p>Azure IoT Hub has now been officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers. The Azure IoT Hub can be used to easily and securely connect IoT assets, add new devices and connect existing devices with open source device SDKs that work on multiple platforms (including Linux, Windows and real-time operating systems), and use standard protocols and custom protocols including HTTP, Advanced Message Queuing Protocol (AMQP) and Message Queuing Telemetry Transport (MQTT). Using Azure IoT Hub’s device management function, administrators can also remotely maintain, update and manage IoT devices on a large scale, eliminating the need to develop and maintain custom device management solutions and expend further resources on maintaining global assets, and delivering savings in terms of both time and costs.</p>
										<p>For more information on services and pricing, please consult the <a href="https://www.azure.cn/home/features/iot-hub">Azure IoT Hub Service Features</a> page and the <a href="https://www.azure.cn/pricing/details/iot-hub/">Azure IoT Hub Pricing Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/iot-hub/">Azure IoT Hub Documentation page</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-feb-virtual-network"><span>2/1</span> Azure Virtual Network Global VNET Peering officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Virtual Network enables many types of Azure resources, such as Azure Virtual Machines (VM), to securely communicate with each other, the internet, and on-premises networks. A virtual network is scoped to a single region. You can build a hybrid infrastructure that you control, bring your own IP addresses and DNS servers, secure your connections with an IPSec VPN or ExpressRoute, and get granular control over traffic between subnets for your private network in the cloud.</p>
								<p>Azure Virtual Network Global VNET Peering is now officially released. To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit Virtual Network <a href="/home/features/virtual-network/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-feb-features-virtual-network">Feature</a> Page and <a href="/pricing/details/virtual-network/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-feb-pricing-virtual-network">Price Details</a> Page. For more details, please visit<a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-network/" id="what-is-new_year_2019-feb-docs-virtual-network"> Azure Virtual Network Documentation</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
				</ul>
				<h3>January 2019</h3>
				<ul>
						<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-jan-azure-azure-cognitive-services-text-analytics-api"><span>1/16</span>The free version of Azure Cognitive Services Text Analytics API officially released</a>
									<section>
										<p>The Text Analytics API is a cloud-based service that provides advanced natural language processing over raw text, and includes four main functions: sentiment analysis, key phrase extraction, language detection, and entity linking.</p>
										<p>The API is backed by resources in Microsoft Cognitive Services, a collection of machine learning and AI algorithms in the cloud, readily consumable in your development projects.</p>
										<p>The free version of Azure Cognitive Services Text Analytics API has now been officially released. For more information on this feature and its pricing, please visit <a href="https://www.azure.cn/home/features/cognitive-services/text-analytics/">Text Analytics API Feature page</a> and <a href="https://www.azure.cn/pricing/details/cognitive-services/">Price Details page</a>. For more details, please visit <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/cognitive-services/Text-Analytics/">Text Analytics API Documentation</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li>
						<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-jan-azure-cognitive-services-content-moderator-api"><span>1/7</span>The free version of Azure Cognitive Services Content Moderator API officially released</a>
									<section>
										<p>The Azure Content Moderator API is a cognitive service that checks text, image, and video content for material that is potentially offensive, risky, or otherwise undesirable. When such material is found, the service applies appropriate labels (flags) to the content. Your app can then handle flagged content in order to comply with regulations or maintain the intended environment for users.</p>
										<p>The free version of Azure Cognitive Services Content Moderator API has now been officially released. For more information on this feature and its pricing, please visit <a href="https://www.azure.cn/home/features/cognitive-services/content-moderator/">Content Moderator API Feature page</a> and <a href="https://www.azure.cn/pricing/details/cognitive-services/">Price Details page</a>. For more details, please visit <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/cognitive-services/content-moderator/">Content Moderator API Documentation</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li>
						<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-jan-azure-cosmos-db"><span>1/1</span>Azure Cosmos DB Cassandra, Table, and Gremlin APIs officially released</a>
									<section>
										<p>Azure Cosmos DB is a globally distributed, multi-model database service that supports document, key/value pairs, wide-column, and graph databases. With the click of a button, Cosmos DB enables you to elastically and independently scale throughput and storage across any number of Azure's geographic regions and take advantage of fast, single-digit-millisecond data access using your favorite APIs among SQL, MongoDB, and newly released Cassandra, Table, or Gremlin.</p>
										<p>Azure Cosmos DB Cassandra, Table, and Gremlin APIs have now been official released. To learn more about Azure Cosmos DB, please visit <a href="/home/features/cosmos-db/">Azure Cosmos DB Feature</a> page and <a href="/pricing/details/cosmos-db/">Azure Cosmos DB Price Details</a> page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cosmos-db/">Azure Cosmos DB Document page</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li>
						<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2019-jan-azure-storage-ssd-e4-e6"><span>1/1</span>Azure Storage E4 and E6 Standard SSD Managed Disks are now officially released</a>
									<section>
										<p>Standard SSD Managed Disks, a low-cost SSD offering, are optimized for test and entry-level production workloads requiring consistent latency. Standard SSD Managed Disks can also be used for big data workloads that require high throughput. Standard SSD Managed Disks deliver lower latency compared to Standard HDDs, while improving reliability and scalability for your applications, and are available with all Azure VM sizes. Standard SSD Managed Disks can be easily upgraded to Premium SSD Managed Disks for more demanding and latency-sensitive enterprise workloads. Offered as a managed disk solution, Standard SSD Managed Disks come with the same industry leading durability and availability that you expect from Premium SSD Managed Disks. E4 and E6 Standard SSD Managed Disks are now officially released.</p>
										<p>To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="https://www.azure.cn/home/features/storage/managed-disks/">Azure Storage Managed Disks feature page</a> and <a href="https://www.azure.cn/pricing/details/storage/managed-disks">pricing details page</a>. For more details please visit <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/storage/">Azure Storage Documentation</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li>
                </ul>

				<h3>December 2018</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-december-service-bus"><span>12/30</span>Service Bus Premium tier officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Service Bus is a multi-tenant cloud messaging service you can use to send information between applications and services. The asynchronous operations give you flexible, brokered messaging, along with structured first-in, first-out (FIFO) messaging, and publish/subscribe capabilities.</p>
								<p>Service Bus Premium runs in dedicated resources to provide higher throughput and more consistent performance.</p>
								<p>Azure Service Bus Premium tier is now officially released. To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit Service Bus <a href="/home/features/service-bus/" id="what-is-new_year_2018-december-features-service-bus">Feature</a> Page and <a href="/pricing/details/service-bus/" id="what-is-new_year_2018-december-pricing-service-bus">Price Details</a> Page. For more details, please visit<a href="//docs.azure.cn/service-bus/" id="what-is-new_year_2018-december-docs-service-bus"> Azure Service Bus Documentation</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
						<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-dec-dns"><span>12/27</span>Azure DNS Now Officially Released</a>
									<section>
										<p>Host your domain in Azure for outstanding performance and availability. You can use Azure DNS to host your Domain Name System (DNS) in Azure. Manage your DNS records using the same credentials, and billing and support contract, as your other Azure services. Seamlessly integrate Azure-based services with corresponding DNS updates and streamline your end-to-end deployment process. Azure DNS is now officially released.</p>
										<p>To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/home/features/dns">Azure DNS feature page</a> and <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/pricing/details/dns">pricing details page</a>. For more details please visit <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/dns/">Azure DNS Documentation page</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
						</li>
						<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
							<div>
								<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-dec-expressroute"><span>12/25</span>ExpressRoute now officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
								<section>
									<p>ExpressRoute is now officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data center. You can contact the local support ExpressRoute connection service provider (GDS Services Ltd.) to create a private network connection. ExpressRoute is a service that enables you to create private connections between Azure datacenters and customer-owned environment. ExpressRoute connections don't go over the public internet, and offer more reliability, faster speeds, and lower latencies than internet connections.</p>
									<p>To understand more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/home/features/expressroute/">ExpressRoute feature</a> page and <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/pricing/details/expressroute/">pricing details</a> page. For more details please visit <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/expressroute/">ExpressRoute</a> Documentation page.</p>
								</section>
							</div>
						</li>
                </ul>

                <h3>November 2018</h3>
                <ul>
					<li>
							<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
								<div>
									<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november-sqldb-vcore-gen5"><span>11/22</span>Single database (Single DB) Gen5 in Azure SQL Database vCore-based purchasing model has been officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 datacenters</a>
									<section>
										<p>Azure SQL database is a fully managed relational database with built-in intelligence supporting self-driving features, such as performance tuning and threat alerts. Microsoft performs all the patching and updating of the code base, and manages the underlying infrastructure for you, so you can save time and resources.With high SQL Server compatibility, you can also migrate your databases to SQL Database Managed Instance without changing your apps.</p>
										<p>If flexible, controllable, and transparent independent resource usage is required, a vCore-based purchasing model is most suitable. This model allows calculation scaling, memory, and storage based on workload requirements and provides a direct way to translate local workload requirements into the cloud. The single DB Gen5 platform has been announced for China East 2 and China North 2 datacenters.</p>
										<p>To understand more about pricing for this service, please visit <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/pricing/details/sql-database/">Azure SQL Database pricing details page</a>. For more details please visit <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/sql-database/">Azure SQL Database Documentation page</a>.</p>
									</section>
								</div>
							</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november-standard-load-balancer"><span>11/20</span>Azure Standard Load Balancer has been officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Standard Load Balancer supports inbound as well as outbound scenarios, provides low latency and high throughput, and scales up to millions of flows for all TCP and UDP applications. You can use load balancing rules with TCP/HTTP/HTTPS health probes, inbound NAT rules for port forwarding, and outbound rules to scale and tune your outbound connectivity.</p>
								<p>For more information about Standard Load Balancer and its pricing, see <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/home/features/load-balancer/">Standard Load Balancer overview page</a> and <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/pricing/details/load-balancer/">Standard Load Balancer Pricing Details page</a>. For more details, please visit the <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/load-balancer/load-balancer-standard-overview">Standard Load Balancer Documentation page</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november-12-customer-engagement-fabric"><span>11/12</span>Azure HDInsight Linux is now officially released in China North 2 datacenter</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure HDInsight is a fully-managed cloud service that makes it easy, fast, and cost-effective to process massive amounts of data. Use popular open-source frameworks such as Hadoop, Spark, Hive, LLAP, Kafka, Storm, HBase, and more. Azure HDInsight enables a broad range of scenarios such as ETL, Data Warehousing, IoT, and more.</p>
								<p>Azure HDInsight Linux is now officially released in China North 2 data center. To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/home/features/hdinsight/">Azure HDInsight Services Feature </a>page and <a href="https://www.azure.cn/zh-cn/pricing/details/hdinsight/">Price Details </a>page. For more details, please visit<a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/hdinsight/"> Azure HDInsight Document </a>page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november-1-customer-engagement-fabric"><span>11/1</span>Azure Customer Engagement Fabric preview version released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Customer Engagement Fabric preview version is announced. Customer Engagement Fabric (CEF) provides a series of basic services that allow interactive connectivity between the app and users, including multi-channel notification service, third-party sign-in and aggregate functions for payment. These services can help the app quickly implement relevant user connectivity functions, improve user engagement and analyze user behavior data to improve app operational efficiency.</p>
								<p>Services formally announced in the preview version include:</p>
								<p>1. Text message notification: provide stable and highly efficient text message services, support text message with verification code, text message notification and marketing text message for members.</p>
								<p>2. Third-party sign-in: Provides unified SDK to help developers implement WeChat, QQ, Weibo Sign-in to implement unified data management.</p>
								<p>To understand more about this service, please visit <a href="/home/features/customer-engagement-fabric/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november_features-customer-engagement-fabric">Customer Engagement Fabric Product Function</a>page and <a href="/pricing/details/customer-engagement-fabric/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november_pricing-customer-engagement-fabric">Pricing</a>page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/customer-engagement-fabric/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november_documentation-customer-engagement-fabric">Customer Engagement Fabric documentation</a>page. For more information about this announcement, please refer to blog<a href="/blog/2018/11/01/Customer-Engagement-Fabric-is-in-public-preview-now/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-november_blog-customer-engagement-fabric">Customer Engagement Fabric preview version announcement</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>October 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-october-24-logic-apps"><span>10/24</span>China regions cloud migration and expansion preview now available</a>
							<section>
								<p>China regions cloud migration and expansion provides customers with assessment services and migration guidance to reduce instances from arising based on the below two scenarios:</p>
								<p>1. For customers migrating your Azure Cloud Services among China regions, please visit <a href="https://aka.ms/ccmechina" id="service-fabric_year_2018-october_features-china-ccme">https://aka.ms/ccmechina</a>;</p>
								<p>2. For customers migrating and expanding your Azure Cloud Services between Azure Global and Azure China, please visit <a href="https://aka.ms/ccme" id="service-fabric_year_2018-october_features-global-ccme">https://aka.ms/ccme</a>.</p>
								<p>This product has two components:</p>
								<p>Online assessment service can assess consistency of services and configurations between original and destination environments, as well as estimate the migration costs. Customers can conduct this assessment through subscription and/or Azure usage reports.</p>
								<p>This migration guide has undergone verification tests by engineers. It provides step-by-step video guides on migrating main workloads. Main workloads include Virtual Machines, Storage, Virtual Network, Database, Web Apps and Azure Cosmos DB.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-october-15-logic-apps"><span>10/15</span>Release of Azure Logic Apps Preview</a>
							<section>
								<p>Logic Apps helps you to quickly generate powerful integration solutions, connecting business-critical apps and services and automating workflows without writing any codes. You can connect apps, data, and devices anywhere - locally or in the cloud - with our large ecosystem of software as a service (SaaS) and cloud-based connectors that includes Salesforce, Office 365, Twitter, Dropbox, Google services, and more.</p>

								<p>To learn more about this capability and pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/logic-apps/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-october_features-logic-apps">Logic Apps Feature</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/logic-apps/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-october_pricing-logic-apps">Logic Apps Pricing</a>page. For more details, please visit the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/logic-apps/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-october_documentation-logic-apps">Azure Logic Apps</a> page.</p></p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="support-chatbot_year_2018-october-support"><span>10/15</span>Azure online customer support preview version announced </a>
							<section>								<p>Effective immediately, you can quickly get answers to the FAQs while using Azure through two channels without the need to wait.</p>
								<p> • Login to <a href="https://support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/" id="support-chatbot_year_2018-october-support-azure">Azure Support Submission </a>Page, click on “<strong>Online Customer Support</strong>”at the lower right corner</p>
								<p> • Follow “Microsoft cloud technologies” WeChat Official Accounts, click on the menu <strong>experience cloud - intelligent customer support (preview version)</strong> (note: WeChat channel provides only intelligent customer support at the moment)</p>
								<p>Azure intelligent customer support “Cloud” uses Azure Cognitive Services, Azure Cosmos DB and machine learning, as well as supporting data and technical knowledge base to help customers get answers to relevant Azure questions. At the same time, through continuing training of machine learning, intelligent customer support can self-evolve as time progresses, giving ever more accurate answers. Users can choose a human operator online on top of the intelligent customer support, which allows users to engage engineers in the same chat. With this “online customer support” model, we hope to provide you with a faster, easier and more intelligent Azure support experience.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>September 2018</h3>
                <ul>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper-azure-stream-analytics"><span>9/28</span>Azure Stream Analytics on IoT Edge preview version released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Stream Analytics on Azure IoT Edge enables developers to deploy near-real-time analytical intelligence closer to IoT devices so that they can unlock the full value of device-generated data. Azure Stream Analytics is designed for low latency, resiliency, efficient use of bandwidth, and compliance. Enterprises can now deploy control logic close to industrial operations and complement big data analytics performed in the cloud. For more information on this feature and its pricing, please visit the <a href="//www.azure.cn/zh-cn/pricing/details/stream-analytics/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_pricing-stream-analytics">Azure Stream Analytics Pricing Page</a>. Please see <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/stream-analytics/stream-analytics-edge" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_documentation-stream-analytics-edge">this documentation</a> for more details.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper-azure-backup"><span>9/18</span>Azure Backup is officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Backup is a reliable, low-cost, and scalable solution, allowing for backup of local data onto the cloud. Without any capital investment, you can protect your key business data with the lowest operating expenses.</p>
								<p>Azure Backup now enables backup of virtual machines on Azure through a few simple steps, and also permits placing the restore points on the cloud storage. Whenever necessary, you can respond from the restore points to meet various demands for protecting Azure Virtual Machines.</p>
								<p>The Azure Backup is now officially released in the new data centers (China East 2 and China North 2). To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/backup/">Azure Backup Service Feature </a>page and <a href="/pricing/details/backup/">Price Details </a>page. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/backup/">Azure Backup Document </a>page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper-azure-site-recovery"><span>9/18</span> Azure Site Recovery is officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers </a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Site Recovery can help protect your major services by coordinating automatic copying and recovery of the private cloud at auxiliary positions. There are two major deployment choices.</p>
								<ul>
									<li>The Virtual Machine operated while Hyper-V and system center are used can be copied between two client sites. Azure Site Recovery can monitor the status and storage recovery plan of the application programs operated at home sites and execute the plan when necessary. When site interruptions happen at the main data center, Virtual Machine recovers as arranged so as to help rapidly recover services. This process can also be used for recovery tests or temporary transmission services.</li>
									<li>Now, Virtual Machine can be copied directly from a home site to Azure instead of your own auxiliary site. When home site interrupt happens, this service can coordinate the recovery of Virtual Machine in Azure.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>The Azure Site Recovery is now officially released in the new data centers (China East 2 and China North 2). To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/site-recovery/">Azure Site Recovery Services Feature </a>page and <a href="/pricing/details/site-recovery/">Price Details </a>page.For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/site-recovery/"> Azure Site Recovery Document </a>page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper-azure-management_groups"><span>9/17</span>Azure Resource Manager Management Groups Feature is officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers</a>
							<section>
								<p>Management Groups is a feature of the Azure Resource Manager (ARM) service. If your organization has many subscriptions, you may need a way to effectively manage the access, policy, and compliance for those subscriptions.  Azure Management Groups provide a higher level of coverage than  subscriptions. You organize subscriptions in a container called a "Management Group" and apply your management conditions to the Management Group. All subscriptions in the Management Group automatically inherit these conditions. Regardless of the type of subscription you use, the management team can provide you with large-scale enterprise-level management. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/azure-resource-manager/management-groups-overview" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_documentation-management_groups">Management Group Documentation</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper-azure-automation"><span>9/13</span>Azure Automation is officially released in China North 2 data center </a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Automation provides cloud-based automation and configuration services which allow for consistent management in both Azure and non-Azure environments. Functions include process automation, update management, and configuration. Azure Automation provides full control during the deployment, operation, and shutdown of workloads and resources. Azure Automation has now officially been released in the China North 2 data center. To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/automation/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_features-automation">Azure Automation Service Feature Page</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/automation/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_pricing-automation">Price Details Page</a>. For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/automation/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_documentation-automation">Azure Automation Documentation Page</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper-azure-batch"><span>9/10</span> Azure Batch is officially released in China East 2 and China North 2 data centers </a>
							<section>
								<p>Using Azure Batch allows users to efficiently run massively parallel and high performance computing (HPC) batch jobs in Azure. Users can use the Batch scheduling function for free, paying only for the underlying virtual machine service consumption. There is no additional cost for using Azure Batch. Developers use Azure Batch to extend parallel workloads, manage the execution of tasks in queues, and offload computing jobs in the cloud through applications. By using Azure Batch, users can run these applications on demand or on a large scale without having to create and manage clusters, virtual machines, or job plans. Azure Batch can manage virtual machine deployment, autoscaling, and failback; be used as a part of your workflow; and deliver applications as a service.</p>
								
								<p>Azure Batch has now officially been released in the new data centers (China East 2 and China North 2). To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit <a href="/home/features/batch/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_features-batch">Azure Batch Service Feature Page</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/batch/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_pricing-batch">Price Details Page</a>.For more details, please visit <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/batch/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-septemper_documentation-batch">Azure Batch Documentation Page</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
				</ul>
                <h3>August 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-august-azure-mysql&postgresql"><span>8/22</span> Azure Container Registry preview version released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Container Registry preview version has been released in China. It provides a hosted Docker registration service for storing and managing private container images. Azure Container Registry can work along with the existing container development and deployment channels. You can generate a container image in Azure using the Azure Container Registry Build. The source code submission and base image update can be used to generate triggers on demand as needed or fully automatically.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/container-registry/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-august_features-container-registry">Container Registry Service Feature</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/container-registry/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-august_pricing-container-registry">Container Registry Price Details</a>page. For more details, please visit the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/container-registry/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-may-10_documentation-container-registry">Azure Container Registry Documentation</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>July 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july-azure-mysql&postgresql"><span>7/23</span> Azure Database for MySQL and Azure Database for PostgreSQL officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Database for MySQL and Azure Database for PostgreSQL have now been officially released. They offer Azure Community edition MySQL and PostgreSQL database engines, built-in high availability, elastic scale for performance, as well as industry-leading security and compliance with 99.99% SLA. They also deliver flexibility for your applications. From framework and language of your choice to a rich tools and service ecosystem, thereby enabling you to build intelligent applications faster and with greater ease.</p>
								
								<p>To learn more about Azure Database for MySQL and its pricing details, please visit<a href="/home/features/mysql/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_features-mysql"> Azure Database for MySQL Service Features</a> page and<a href="/pricing/details/mysql/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_pricing-mysql"> Azure Database for MySQL Pricing Details</a> page. To learn more about Azure Database for PostgreSQL and its pricing details, please visit <a href="/home/features/postgresql/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_features-postgresql">Azure Database for PostgreSQL Service Features</a> page and<a href="/pricing/details/postgresql/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_pricing-postgresql"> Azure Database for PostgreSQL Pricing Details</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july-azure-sql-database"><span>7/2</span> Azure SQL Database Standard Performance Tiers S4, S6, S7, S9, and S12 are officially released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure SQL Database is a managed intelligent relational cloud database service. Using existing SQL Server functions, you can migrate SQL Server databases, speed up app development, and simplify maintenance without changing your app. New performance tiers (S4, S6, S7, S9, and S12) for single databases within SQL database have been officially launched. They provide more CPUs for standard databases, so that you can obtain a significant number of CPUs without having to use the Premium version, thereby reducing costs.</p>
								
								<p>For more information about this service and pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/sql-database/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_features-sql-database">SQL Database Service Features</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/sql-database/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-july_pricing-sql-database">SQL Database Pricing Details</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                
  
            </div>                      
        </div>
        <a id="_whatisnew-linkbutton" href="/what-is-new/archives/2018/" class="single-link h2-link">View Historical Circular<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Latest Azure Cloud Product Announcements - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure’s latest announcements include product updates and important notices. The announcements display the latest dynamics, and allow customers to see updates immediately, quickly locate corresponding content, and see all updates at a glance.]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>whatisnew</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName>Latest Announcements</urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <banner><![CDATA[
      
        <!-- BEGIN: Banner -->
            <div class="common-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#fab300', 'backgroundImage':'//wacndevelop.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/homepage/banner-announcement@2x.png','imageHeight':'180'}" id="banner">            
            <div class="common-banner-image">
                <div class="common-banner-title">
                    <h1>Latest announcements from Azure </h1>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>  
        <!-- End: Banner-->
    
    ]]></banner>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate></pageTemplate>
    <localize>0</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <headerText></headerText>
    <forbidPublish>1</forbidPublish>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
