<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage id="12103" parentID="12095" level="3" writerID="106" creatorID="22" nodeType="1059" template="15" sortOrder="3" createDate="2012-05-29T21:04:52" updateDate="2014-11-07T08:57:21" nodeName="FAQ" urlName="faq" writerName="content" creatorName="Brad" path="-1,11978,12095,12103" isDoc="">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
        <div class="section-component">
                        <h2>Please select the category of FAQs to browse</h2>
                        <!-- BEGIN: TAB-CONTROL -->
                        <div class="tab-control-selector">
                            <a href="#" data-href="#general" id="faq-general" class="active">General issues</a> <a href="#" data-href="#registration" id="faq-registration">Registration issues</a> <a href="#" data-href="#billingAndSubscription" id="faq-billingAndSubscription">Billing, subscriptions and invoice</a> <a href="#" data-href="#implementationAndMaintenance" id="faq-implementationAndMaintenance">Implementation and maintenance</a> <!-- <a href="#" data-href="#ICP" id="faq-icp">ICP 问题</a> --> <!--<a href="#" data-href="#policy" id="faq-policy">Azure 支持概述问题</a>--> <a href="#" id="new_control_bexpend" class="faq-floder"><em>Show all</em></a>
                            <div class="clearfix"></div>
                            <div class="floder-layer">
                                <div class="tab-control-container tab-active" id="general">   
                                    <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                                        <div class="more-detail">
                                            <h2>1 General Issues</h2>
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-1-1" href="#">What is Azure?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Azure is a flexible and open cloud platform that enables you to quickly build, deploy, and manage applications in your data center. Azure supports all major operating systems, languages, or development tools and integrates public cloud applications with the existing IT infrastructure.</p>
                                                            <p>Azure offers international class Service Level Agreements that enable you to build and run highly available applications without having to focus on your infrastructure. It can automatically fix the operating systems and services, and has built-in network load balancing and hardware fault correcting capabilities. It supports the deployment models that allow you to upgrade applications with no downtime.</p>
                                                            <p>Azure enables you to generate applications in any language and by any framework or tool and to utilize the public functions and services of open REST protocol. Azure’s client libraries are available in a variety of programming languages and are published under open source licenses and hosted on GitHub.</p>
                                                            <p>Azure offers a flexible cloud platform that meets the needs of any application.</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_new" href="/what-is-new/">Latest Product Updates</a></li>
                                                                <!--<li><a id="support_faq_sol" href="/solutions/">解决方案</a></li>-->
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_sta" href="/starter-guide/">Guide to Getting Started</a></li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-1-2" href="#">What are the prices of Azure services in China?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>We will continue to update and release more information on prices. You can get the latest information on the <a id="FAQ-1" href="/pricing/overview/">Pricing Page</a>.<!-- 
															：
                                                               <a id="FAQ-1" href="/pricing/overview/">https://www.azure.cn/pricing/overview/</a>
															-->
                                                            </p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-1-3" href="#">Are Azure services in China the same as those in other areas?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>In China, <a id="support_faq_wa" href="//www.azure.cn/">Azure</a> is operated by Shanghai Blue Cloud Technology Co., Ltd., a wholly-owned subsidiary of Beijing 21Vianet Broadband Data Center Co., Ltd. (21Vianet for short). 21Vianet is China’s largest neutral third party Internet infrastructure service telecommunications provider to which Microsoft has authorized technologies. In China, Azure combines Microsoft’s global technologies and 21Vianet’s local operating experience to build an enterprise-level international cloud computing platform for China.</p>
                                                            <p>Outside China, <a id="support_faq_mic" href="//azure.microsoft.com/">Microsoft Azure is operated by Microsoft itself</a>. China’s Azure customers will be able to enjoy entirely the same user experiences and service level as customers in other areas.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-1-4" href="#">What is an SLA (Service Level Agreement)? What kind of SLA does Azure offer in China?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>We provide international class SLAs for each of the official and commercial Azure services. If the corresponding service level is not reached, the customer can enjoy a corresponding service fee deduction. The SLAs provided by Azure in China are listed at :<br><a id="FAQ-2" href="/support/legal/sla/" class="single-link">https://www.azure.cn/support/legal/sla/</a></p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-1-5" href="#">What are some success stories of Azure in China?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>In China, a large number of enterprises like CNTV, GMW.cn, Linekong, Smartisan, China Telecom, Kingdee, PPTV, renren.com, ChinaCache, and Qoros log in to the Azure platform in China. Please go to the <a id="FAQ-3" href="/partnerancasestudy/case-studies/">Success Stories</a> page for information about these cases.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-1-6" href="#">How do I select Azure computing services: Web Apps, Cloud Services and Virtual Machines? If I’m an enterprise level user, what services should I select to migrate the existing enterprise applications to the Azure cloud computing platform when faced with these three different computing capabilities?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>According to the following characteristics, you can select one service that is suitable for your needs:</p>
                                                            <table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%">
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <th align="center">&#160;</th>
                                                                    <th align="center"><strong>Characteristics</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="center"><strong>More Suitable</strong></th>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td><a id="support_faq_web" href="/home/features/web-site/">Web Apps</a></td>
                                                                    <td>
                                                                        <ol>
                                                                            <li>You can easily deploy a highly scalable cloud environment by building a highly scalable website on Azure, which can start at a very small scale.</li>
                                                                            <li>You can use language and open source applications selected by you, such as WordExpress, FTP, Git or TFS, and easily integrate Azure services, such as SQL databases, caches, CDN and storage.</li>
                                                                            <li>The Web applications are characterized by rapid deployment with only basic functions provided, such as Application and Data. It doesn’t support such advanced functions as Startup Task, Native Code and Virtual Network.
                                                                            </li>
                                                                        </ol>
                                                                    </td>
                                                                    <td>
                                                                        <ol>
                                                                            <li>Modern Web applications. Include client scripts, server-side scripts and database applications, and can be scaled horizontally.</li>
                                                                            <li>Continuous development. You can use Git or Team Foundation directly from the source code libraries for deployment.</li>
                                                                            <li>Using open source applications. You can directly use open source applications, such as WordPress.</li>
                                                                        </ol>
                                                                    </td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td><a id="support_faq_clo" href="/home/features/cloud-services/">Cloud Service</a></td>
                                                                    <td>
                                                                        <ol>
                                                                            <li>Expand your enterprise applications on Azure.</li>
                                                                            <li>A rich PaaS environment is utilized to create highly available and scalable applications and services. Advanced multi-layer architecture, automatic deployment and elastic computing are supported.</li>
                                                                            <li>Through a virtual network, you can connect the network of the local LAN to the Azure public cloud network to allow the enterprise network to enjoy the highly elastic computing and interoperability brought by the public cloud, while ensuring network security.</li>
                                                                        </ol>
                                                                    </td>
                                                                    <td>
                                                                        <ol>
                                                                            <li>For multi-layer applications, each layer can expand itself. When using Web Role and Worker Role, the Web Role can respond to the display at the front end, while the complex business is handled at the back end.</li>
                                                                            <li>Advanced management. You can use Cloud Service if your application requires administrator rights, remote desktop access, or upgraded authority to run the code.</li>
                                                                            <li>Private cloud + public cloud. You can use Azure Connect for point-to-point connection with the Azure public cloud, or use the Azure virtual network to connect the enterprise intranet or private network to the public cloud.</li>
                                                                        </ol>
                                                                    </td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td><a id="support_faq_vir" href="/home/features/virtual-machines/">Virtual Machine (VM) </a></td>
                                                                    <td>
                                                                        <ol>
                                                                            <li>Provide IaaS services, support XX and Linux operating system.</li>
                                                                            <li>You can easily deploy and run Windows Server and Linux virtual machine and transfer the operating load in a few minutes, without changing the existing code. For an application based on Windows OS, you can transfer it to Hyper-V and save it as a VHD file and upload it to Azure for deployment and hosting.</li>
                                                                            <li>Virtual network support. You can connect your LAN enterprise application with the public cloud directly and enjoy the convenience of cloud computing.</li>
                                                                        </ol>
                                                                    </td>
                                                                    <td>
                                                                        <ol>
                                                                            <li>Windows or Linux support. You can quickly transfer the existing Windows or Linux applications to Azure.</li>
                                                                            <li>More service applications are supported. You can use SQL Server, MySQL, MongoDB, and SharePoint applications in Azure.</li>
                                                                            <li>Transferring existing applications to the public cloud is supported. You can save persistent non-relational data in Azure VHD.</li>
                                                                        </ol>
                                                                    </td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                            </table>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-1-7" href="#">How can Azure services in China ensure the security of users’ data and services?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The security and stability of cloud services have always been the focus of the industry. As the first international public cloud service launched in China, Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet has gained recognition from many industry users, and provided the majority of users with reliable, flexible and highly valuable public cloud services.</p>
                                                            <p>
                                                                By means of all-round cloud services first realized in China - IaaS, PaaS, SaaS, and reliable localization operation, monthly service-level agreements of international quality with financial security, powerful data security, rich client returns and other advantages, Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet has obtained 6 credible cloud certifications including cloud, cloud engine (cloud service) and the whole network load balancing (Traffic Manager), representing recognition from the industry for the quality of international localized cloud service provided by 21Vianet.
                                                            </p>
                                                            <p>
                                                                Moreover, according to the GBT 22240-2008 Information Security Technology - Guide on Determination of Security Protection Levels for Information Systems, the assessment organization authorized by the Ministry of Public Security has conducted an assessment of Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet as per GB/T 22239-2008 Information Security Technology - Basic Requirements of Security Protection Levels of Information Systems. The Information Security Protection of Azure has been classified as the third Level (Information System Classified Security Protection (DJCP), Level 3 ) and has been issued with record-keeping certificates.
                                                            </p>
                                                            <p>In full compliance with China’s policies and regulations, China’s Azure data service providers provide up to six different backups at different places, which are distributed in 2 data centers (northern China and eastern China). In addition, with decades of experience in providing enterprise customers with online services which are applied in the Azure platform, we strive to keep the leading position in the industry in terms of security, privacy, and control and compliance practices.</p>
                                                            <p>
                                For more details, see the <a id="support_faq7_tru" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/">Data Security</a>, <a id="support_faq7_sec" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/security/">Privacy</a> and<a id="support_faq7_pri" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/privacy/">FAQs</a> pages in the Azure<a id="support_faq7_faq" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/resources/FAQ.html">Trust Center</a>.
                                                            </p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-1-8" href="#">I have an MSDN subscription, and when I enable “Azure Benefit” for my account, can this service be available in Azure China at the same time?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>
                                No. China’s Azure service is operated by 21Vianet. The “Azure Benefit” in your account can only be operated on platforms in other areas of Azure. MSDN accounts cannot be enabled on Azure China’s platform operated by 21Vianet. If you’re interested in applying for a Microsoft Azure service operated by 21Vianet, please fill out the <a id="FAQ-7" href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/">Azure Trial Application Form</a><!--
																<a id="FAQ-7" href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/">http://www.azure.cn/pricing/1rmb-trial/</a> 
																-->. Start your Azure experience with a 1 RMB Trial subscription.
                                                            </p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-1-9" href="#">Does Azure support open-source software in China?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Azure supports a large number of open source applications, frameworks and languages, and the number is still growing. We know that developers want to use the most suitable tools for their own experience, skill, tool and application needs, and our goal is to allow developers to choose tools as needed.</p>
                                                            <p>For the open source code, please visit <a id="FAQ-8" href="//github.com/Azure/azure-sdk-for-net">https://github.com/Azure/azure-sdk-for-net/</a>.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-1-10" href="#">What kind of roles does Microsoft play in Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The Microsoft Azure service operated by 21Vianet is a public cloud platform that is independently operated on the Chinese mainland. It is operated and sold independently by 21Vianet and the Microsoft Azure technology, which serves the whole world and is adopted to provide customers with global uniform quality assurance. As a customer of Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet, the following services are available:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Cloud services are hosted on the Chinese mainland data centers and are operated independently by 21Vianet. 21Vianet is China's leading provider of Internet data centers.</li>
                                                                <li>Based on Microsoft’s decades of rich online service experience in global enterprise customers, Azure, a world-class technology, has been developed to fully serve China’s customers.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-1-11" href="#">Where can I find details on the new features?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>You can browse the following pages:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_new" href="/what-is-new/">Latest Announcements</a> <!-- 
																- <a id="support_faq_new" href="/what-is-new/">http://www.azure.cn/what-is-new/ </a>
																-->
																</li>
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_fun" href="/home/features/what-is-azure/">Learn About Azure</a> <!-- 
																- <a id="support_faq_fun" href="/home/features/what-is-azure/">http://www.azure.cn/home/features/what-is-azure/ </a>
																-->
																</li>
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_pri" href="/pricing/overview/">Pricing Details</a> <!--
																- <a id="support_faq_pri" href="/pricing/overview/">http://www.azure.cn/pricing/overview </a>
																-->
																</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-1-12" href="#">How will 21Vianet use the information I stored in Azure?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>21Vianet will only use your customer data stored in Azure to provide you with Azure services. These services may include the troubleshooting for preventing, detecting, or fixing the issues that affect operation of Azure and the improvement of functions that detect and resist emerging and evolving threats to users (such as malicious software and junk mail). If you want to know more about our promise for your data, please visit the <a id="FAQ-11" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/privacy/">Privacy</a> and <a id="support_faq1_faq" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/resources/FAQ.html">FAQ</a> pages in the Azure Trust Center.
                                                            </p>															
                                                            <!--
															<a id="FAQ-11" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/privacy/">https://www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/privacy/</a><br/>
                                                            <a id="support_faq1_faq" href="//www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/resources/FAQ.html">https://www.trustcenter.cn/zh-cn/resources/FAQ.html</a><br/>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-1-13" href="#">What is StorSimple?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                             <p>StorSimple is a hybrid cloud storage solution that provides IT departments with a new way to manage the rapidly growing data and to simplify the internal environment storage infrastructure while protecting data. The solution includes a set of storage devices deployed in the enterprise’s internal environment and integrated with Microsoft Azure services operated by 21Vianet. It provides you with layered storage.</p>
                                                            <p>StorSimple provides customers with the following core functions:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>5000 and 7000 series devices are provided with hybrid cloud storage</li>
                                                                <li>ISCSI volume access that can be easily integrated with existing applications</li>
                                                                <li>Automatic data hierarchy is adopted to store active data locally and store uncommonly used cold data in the cloud, providing better performance</li>
                                                                <li>Data reduplication and compression</li>
                                                                <li>Data stored in the cloud can be protected by AES-256 bit encryption technology</li>
                                                                <li>Provide local and cloud snapshot capabilities for data protection and disaster recovery</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>Please visit <a id="FAQ_storsimple" href="/solutions/StorSimple/">StorSimple Hybrid Cloud Solutions</a> for details <!--
															<a id="FAQ_storsimple" href="/solutions/StorSimple/">http://www.azure.cn/solutions/StorSimple/</a>
															-->.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-1-14" href="#">I want to learn more about Azure. In addition to the Getting Started Guide, do you have any further study materials?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>You can browse the <a id="support_faq15_docu" href="https://docs.azure.cn/">Documentation Center</a>.</p>																														 
														    <!--
															<a id="support_faq15_docu" href="https://docs.azure.cn/">https://docs.azure.cn/</a>
													        -->																					
                                                            <p>This page contains links and the following content:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Developer center: .NET, Node.js, Java, Python</li>
                                                                <li>Details of various services: computing, data services, application services, networks</li>
                                                                <li>Multiple resources: architectural structure, reference documentation, advice on effective use, performance, and answer to questions, etc.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>Publish and search questions in the Azure forum.</p>
                                        
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                            </ul>   
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="tab-control-container" id="registration">
                                    <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                                        <div class="more-detail">
                                            <h2>Registration Questions</h2>
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-one" href="#">What is the 1 RMB Trial subscription?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>
                                                               This is a promotional activity launched by the Microsoft Azure and operated by 21Vianet. You can register online and pay RMB&#160;1 to activate your 1 RMB Trial subscription and get RMB&#160;1500 in Azure service credits that are valid for one month.
                                                            </p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_offers" href="/offers/ms-mc-azr-44p/">Details of the 1 RMB Trial Subscription Promotion</a></li>
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_1rmb-trial-full" href="/pricing/1rmb-trial-full/?form-type=identityauth/">Apply for Trial Now</a></li>
																<li><a id="support_faq_1rmb-trial-sign-up-guidance" href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-sign-up-azure-account-with-1rmb-trial-subscription/">Trial Program Registration Process</a></li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-two" href="#">What is the standard prepaid subscription? What are the characteristics of such subscription?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>
                                                              Standard prepaid subscription needs to be purchased by Pay-in-Advance. The balance will be deducted according to the actual usage of the user, and overuse is not supported. When the balance is 0, the service will be stopped immediately, and recharge is required to continue using. The minimum prepayment amount of standard prepaid subscription is RMB&#160;1,000 with online payment, and RMB&#160;5,000 with Wire Transfer, which is valid for 12 months after each recharge.
 
                                                            </p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_standard" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">Standard Prepaid Product Details</a></li>
                                                                <li><a id="support_faq_pia-waiting-list" href="/pricing/pia-waiting-list/?form-type=identityauth/">I want to purchase</a></li>
																<li><a id="support_faq_pia-sign-up-guidance" href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-sign-up-azure-account-and-get-a-pia-subscription/">Standard Pay-in-Advance Subscription Process</a></li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                         <a id="faq-register-three" href="#">Is it possible to re-register for a 1 RMB Trial subscription?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Each user can only apply for and get one 1 RMB Trial subscription, and repeated registration is not allowed. If you need more than one subscription, or have already used a 1 RMB Trial subscription, please apply for a <a id="support_faq_ms-mc-arz-33p" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">standard Pay-in-Advance subscription</a>.</p>
															<!--
															详情请参考<a id="support_faq_ms-mc-arz-33p" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p">这里</a>。</p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                         <a id="faq-register-four" href="#">What should I do when a phone validation problem is encountered while registering for the 1 RMB Trial subscription?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Each user can only apply for and get one 1 RMB Trial subscription without repeated registration. If your mobile phone number has been validated before, you cannot apply again. If you need more than one subscription, or have already used a 1 RMB Trial subscription, please apply for a <a id="support_faq_validate" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">standard Pay-in-Advance subscription</a>.</p>
															<!--
															详情请参考<a id="support_faq_validate" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p">这里</a></p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-five" href="#">Do I have to provide identification card information to complete the registration?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Yes, in order to comply with the requirements of relevant laws and regulations and ensure the safety of each subscriber’s account, each registered user needs to provide personal identity information for real-name system certification, so as to obtain secure Azure service.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-six" href="#">Can I use the activation code for a 1 RMB Trial subscription that a friend gives me?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>No. One person can enjoy one opportunity to apply for the promotion. Please go online and get your own activation code. <a id="support_faq_identityauth" href="/pricing/1rmb-trial-full/?form-type=identityauth">Apply for trial</a> now.</p>
															<!--
															请点击<a id="support_faq_identityauth" href="/pricing/1rmb-trial-full/?form-type=identityauth">这里</a>。</p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-seven" href="#">What is OrgID? What does it have to do with trial subscriptions and standard prepaid subscriptions?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>OrgID is a specific user name system for Microsoft’s smart cloud service operated by 21Vianet. It is used to manage Azure subscriptions.</p>
                                                            <p>OrgID is composed of @“domain name”.partner.onmschina.cn. The account is composed of “new user ID”@“domain name”.partner.onmschina.cn, and the user needs to log in with the account name and password. For example, you select the letters ABC similar to your company name as the "domain name" and select XYZ as the "new user ID”. Then your OrgID is @ABC.partner.onmschina.cn, and your account is XYZ@ABC.partner.onmschina.cn.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-eight" href="#"> I have an Office 365 account. Can I use the account information for Azure subscription registration?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>You can only create one of the same type of subscription under each account, and if you have no other subscriptions under your Office 365 account, you can complete the registration by following these steps:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Open the<a id="support_faq_subscriptions" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/subscriptions" target="_blank">account management interface</a></li>
                                                                <li>Log in with your account name</li>
                                                                <li>After you have logged in, you may see the prompt “you haven’t created any subscriptions yet” (if you don’t see the prompt on the page, it means that there are other subscriptions under your account)</li>
                                                                <li>Open a <a id="support_faq_enter-promo-code-form" href="/zh-cn/pricing/enter-promo-code-form/">new page</a> in the same browser</li>
                                                                <li>Enter your activation code and click “Submit”</li>
                                                                <li>When a new page pops up, you can enter the payment information. After completing the steps, you will successfully activate the subscription.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-nine" href="#">After creating the account, if the whole registration process is not completed (the payment is not completed), how can I get back to the registration page and continue to register under the previous account?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>You can only create one of the same type of subscription under each account, and if you have no other subscriptions under your account, you can complete the registration by following these steps:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Details of the 1 RMB Trial subscription promotion - <a id="support_faq_ms" href="/offers/ms-mc-azr-44p/">http://www.azure.cn/offers/ms-mc-azr-44p/</a> </li>
                                                                <ul>
                                                                    <li>Open the<a id="support_faq_account" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/subscriptions" target="_blank">account management interface</a>.</li>
                                                                    <li>Log in with your account name.</li>
                                                                    <li>After you have logged in, you may see the prompt “you haven’t created any subscriptions yet” (if you don’t see the prompt on the page, it means that there are other subscriptions under your account)</li>
                                                                    <li>Open a <a id="support_faq_newpage" href="/zh-cn/pricing/enter-promo-code-form/">new page</a> in the same browser</li>
                                                                    <li>Enter your activation code and click “Submit”</li>
                                                                    <li>When a new page pops up, you can enter the payment information. After completing the steps, you will successfully activate the subscription.</li>
                                                                </ul>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-ten" href="#">Why does the page prompt “1 RMB Trial subscription is not available. The product/service is only provided for Promo members” when registering for the 1 RMB Trial subscription?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>This prompt indicates that you have already used the 1 RMB Trial subscription. Since a user can only apply for and get one 1 RMB Trial subscription without repeated registration, if you need more than one subscription, please apply for a <a id="support_faq_promo" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">standard Pay-in-Advance subscription</a>.</p>
															<!--
															详情请参考<a id="support_faq_promo" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p">这里</a>。</p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <!--
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-eleven" href="#">注册标准预付费订阅时，页面提示“标准预付费服务 不可用，仅为 Promo 成员提供此产品 / 服务” 是为什么？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>此提示说明您在同一账户下想要重复创建多个标准预付费订阅。每个账户下只能创建一个同类型订阅，如果您需要多个订阅，请创建新的账户。详情请参考<a id="support_faq_prepayment" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">标准预付费订阅</a>。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												-->
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-twelve" href="#">How long should I wait for approval after I submitted the Azure 1 RMB Trial subscription application or standard Pay-in-Advance subscription application online? How will you inform me after approval?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>If you apply for a personal account and have submitted an application for the Azure 1 RMB Trial subscription or standard Pay-in-Advance subscription online, you will immediately get feedback about the application results and be guided through completing the registration process;</p>
															<p>If you apply for an enterprise account and have submitted an application for the Azure 1 RMB Trial subscription or standard Pay-in-Advance subscription online, we will email you the review results within one working day and guide you through continuing to complete the registration process;</p>
															<p>When the registration process is interrupted for some reason, you can enter the application page and directly input the mobile phone number that you used for the application, or click the activation link in the email containing the activation code, and then you can continue to complete the registration.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                
												<!-- <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-thirteen" href="#">我找不到系统审核成功发送的激活码怎么办？我的激活码已经过期了，怎么办？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>您可以通过我们的服务热线 400-089-0365、+86-10-84563652 联系我们进行重新激活，并提供申请时所填写的个人信息，我们将协助您完成取回激活码。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li> -->
												
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-mobile" href="#">Why can’t I load the payment information, or there is a prompt indicating that the payment information was not received when I apply for a 1 RMB Trial subscription with a mobile device (mobile phone/tablet)?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>When such a problem occurs, it is recommended that you enable or allow the browser’s Cookie option and then continue the operation from before the interruption. The steps vary depending on the mobile device and the browser. Taking iOS devices as an example, you may follow these steps: [Setup] →[Safari] → [Disable Cookie] →[Always enable].
</p>
															<!--
															详情请参考<a id="support_code_expired " href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p">这里</a>。</p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
													
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-fourteen" href="#">When applying for the 1 RMB Trial subscription, why is there a message showing that payment was successful, but when I return to the Azure registration page, I still see a payment failure message?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Everyone can only enjoy this trial promotion once, so one payment account (including UnionPay and Alipay accounts) can only be used to apply for the 1 RMB Trial subscription once. If you use a payment account that has successfully applied for the 1 RMB Trial subscription to apply for the 1 RMB Trial subscription again, the aforementioned problem will occur, namely: the subscription page shows payment successful, but the Azure registration page shows payment failure. The refund system will automatically return the money to the payment account for the RMB&#160;1 transaction occurred. The specific refund time will be different due to the different operation of each bank and bank card. If you need more than one subscription, or have already tried the 1 RMB Trial subscription, please apply for a <a id="support_code_expired " href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">standard Pay-in-Advance subscription</a>.</p>
															<!--
															详情请参考<a id="support_code_expired " href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p">这里</a>。</p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                
                                                
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-seventeen" href="#">When does the one-month validity of the 1 RMB Trial subscription start?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Validity starts from successful payment and lasts one month.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-eighteen" href="#">In the one-month validity period of the 1 RMB Trial subscription, can the subscription be converted into a standard Pay-in-Advance subscription? How do I do this?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>You can convert the subscription to a standard Pay-in-Advance subscription at any time during the validity of the 1 RMB Trial subscription. Click “Upgrade Now” in the subscription interface and recharge at least RMB&#160;1,000 to your account to turn it into a <a id="support_try_convert " href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">standard Pay-in-Advance subscription</a> and enjoy a richer cloud experience.</p>
															<!--
															详情请参考<a id="support_try_convert " href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">这里</a>。</p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<!--
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-nineteen" href="#">如果订阅账户金额显示为 0，余额不足或使用额度过期，会对用户造成什么影响？账号内的数据是否可以取出？如订阅停用后，数据会保留多少天？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>在使用 1 元试用和标准预付费订阅期间，如果剩余使用额度为 0，或者使用额度过期后，您的订阅将被停用。您的订阅处在停用状态，将无法备份数据，需要重新充值激活激活该订阅。为避免服务中断，请及时充值。</p>
															<p>* 1 元试用订阅：订阅停用后，您的数据将被保留 15 天，在 15 天内进行充值，即可恢复订阅，您需要对相关服务进行重新配置；如订阅被停用 15 天后仍未充值，订阅及订阅内的所有数据将被自动删除。</p>
															<p>* 标准预付费订阅停用后，您的数据将被保存 90 天，在 90 天内进行充值，即可恢复订阅，您需要对相关服务进行重新配置；如订阅被停用 90 天后仍未充值，订阅及订阅内的所有数据将被自动删除。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												-->
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-twenty" href="#"> How should I monitor the balance and the period of validity, in order to avoid any inconvenience caused by the cease of service?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>During the service period of Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet, you will receive a reminder email of the balance and the validity in your contact email every week. You can also log in to the account management interface to check the balance and the validity at any time. It is recommended that you make an assessment based on the actual usage and reserve a sufficient balance. Log in to the <a id="support_faq_inconvenience" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/subscriptions" target="_blank">account management interface</a>.</p>
															<!--
															请点击<a id="support_faq_inconvenience" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions" target="_blank">这里</a>。</p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												  <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-seventeen" href="#">Is payment by wire transfer supported? What should I do?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-pay-for-subscription-via-wire-transfer/" id="faq_registration_azure-wire-transfer-overview2">Introduction to Wire Transfers</a> for details and operating methods.
 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-register-foreign-currency" href="#">Can I use foreign currency for remittance when I choose to pay by wire transfer for my Azure subscription account?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Only the Chinese yuan is accepted as the payment currency for Azure’s service in China.
 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	 	</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                            </ul>   
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="tab-control-container" id="billingAndSubscription">
                                    <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                                        <div class="more-detail">
                                            <h2>Billing, subscription and invoice</h2>
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-11" href="#">What is a “subscription”?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>A subscription is an important concept for Azure. Taking the well-known Dual Sim mobile phone for example, if a customer purchases a China Mobile or China Unicom SIM card (post-pay), he can make calls, send text messages or surf the Internet through the China Mobile or China Unicom SIM card. At the end of each month, China Mobile and China Unicom will express deliver two mobile phone bills separately:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>China Mobile’s mobile phone bill will tell users how many minutes of calls were made this month, how many text messages were sent, and how much data was used to surf the internet. It also shows how much the total cost is.</li>
                                                                <li>China Unicom’s mobile phone account will also tell users the detailed billing and total costs of the monthly mobile phone bill.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>In Azure, a subscription is like a SIM card. For example, users can create two different subscriptions such as ABC and XYZ, in which users can create and use Azure services, such as virtual machine, storage, SQL Database, etc.</p>
                                                            <p>By the end of the month, the Azure system will produce a detailed list of the usage:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>It will tell the users the total costs of the virtual machine, storage and SQL Database.</li>
                                                                <li>It will also display detailed information about costs incurred in the XYZ subscription.</li>
                                                                <li>Finally, it shows the total cost of all subscriptions.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>Note: Only the users of advanced protocol and standard protocol online services can create numerous subscriptions. Other users, such as test users, can only create and use one subscription.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-12" href="#">What is the relationship between an account and a subscription?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>In Azure, the accounts and the subscriptions have a many-to-many relationship. Assuming that there are two subscriptions, ABC and XYZ, the account administrator can create several accounts, with the corresponding relationships as follows:</p>
                                                            <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="60%">
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Serial number</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Subscription</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Account</strong></th>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>1</td>
                                                                    <td>ABC</td>
                                                                    <td>xiaozhang@contoso.partner.onmschina.cn</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>2</td>
                                                                    <td>XYZ</td>
                                                                    <td>mike@contoso.partner.onmschina.cn</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>3</td>
                                                                    <td>XYZ</td>
                                                                    <td>tom@contoso.partner.onmschina.cn</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>4</td>
                                                                    <td>XYZ</td>
                                                                    <td>xiaozhang@contoso.partner.onmschina.cn </td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                            </table>
                                                            <p>In the table above, Mike and Tom can use only one subscription, and they can use subscription XYZ to enjoy Azure cloud services. Xiao Zhang has a different account and can use 2 subscriptions (ABC and XYZ). Xiao Zhang can use these two different subscriptions to enjoy Azure cloud services.</p>
                                                            <p>For enterprise-level customers, internal cost accounting can be easily conducted for the accounts and subscriptions. For example, Contoso Group owns software research and development bases in the three cities of Beijing, Shanghai and Hangzhou in China. In order to utilize the Azure China cloud platform to improve the service level, Contoso Group only needs to sign an Azure business contract with 21Vianet to create an Org ID: Consoto. The account administrator can also create three subscriptions and three accounts. The corresponding relation is as follows:</p>
                                                            <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="60%">
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Serial number</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Subscription</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Account</strong></th>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>1</td>
                                                                    <td>AAA</td>
                                                                    <td>beijing@contoso.partner.onmschina.cn</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>2</td>
                                                                    <td>BBB</td>
                                                                    <td>shanghai@contoso.partner.onmschina.cn</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>3</td>
                                                                    <td>CCC</td>
                                                                    <td>hangzhou@contoso.partner.onmschina.cn</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                            </table>
                                                            <p>Users in Beijing, Shanghai and Hangzhou can use the above three different accounts for their own software development and deployment. At the same time, Contoso Group’s headquarters will receive a bill for Azure sent by 21Vianet at the end of the month, which shows the respective cost of the three different subscriptions (AAA, BBB, CCC) and the total cost of Azure. According to the billing information, Contoso Group can conduct internal cost accounting for the three research and development bases according to the bill provided by Azure.</p>
                                                            <p>
                                                                Note: The information between subscriptions is isolated, that is, the AAA subscription account cannot see the virtual machine, storage, SQL Database, etc. that are created by the BBB subscription account. Similarly, the BBB subscription account also cannot see the same that are created by the CCC account. This ensures that services are isolated and do not interfere with each other in case of malfunction.
                                                            </p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
											
												
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-subscriptions-wire-transfer" href="#">What should I do if I cannot complete the full subscription ID due to the bank’s restrictions?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>If you cannot complete the subscription ID due to the bank’s restrictions, please fill in the remittance information below and send it directly to <a href="mailto:azure_invoice@oe.21vianet.com" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_mail">azure_invoice@oe.21vianet.com</a> so that we can distinguish the remittance sources and recharge your subscription in a timely manner. </l>
                                                                <li>Subscription ID (you can log in to the <a href="//account.windowsazure.cn/subscriptions" id="support_faq_subscriptions-wire-transfer_account" target="_blank">subscription management portal</a>, click the subscription name, and the subscription ID appears on the right side of the page):</li>
                                                                <li>Remittance amount:</li>
																<li>Remittance date:</li>
																<li>Remittance bank account:</li>
																<li>Name of remitter (remitter on the remittance slip) :</li>
																<li>Company name:</li>
																<li>Mobile phone of contact:</li>
                                                            </ol>                                                          
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												
							
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-13" href="#">How are existing subscriptions recharged?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>Log in to the <a id="support_faq3_sub" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions/" target="_blank">account management interface</a>with the Azure account.</li>
																<!--
																<a id="support_faq3_sub" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions" target="_blank">https://account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions</a></li>
																-->
                                                                <li>Click the subscription name to be recharged</li>
                                                                <li>Click on “Upgrade” or “Recharge” on the right side</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                            <p>If you select “Alipay” or “UnionPay Online” and other such methods of online remittance, after clicking on “upgrade” or “recharge”, enter the recharge amount according to the prompt (the minimum amount is RMB&#160;1,000, and the maximum amount shall not exceed RMB&#160;150,000), and then click on the check mark. The payment page will appear and you should follow the instructions to complete the payment. If you select wire transfer, the minimum recharge amount should be RMB&#160;5,000. Please refer to the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-pay-for-subscription-via-wire-transfer/" id="faq_billing and subscription_azure-wire-transfer-overview">wire transfer instructions</a> for details.
</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-2-3" href="#">Can a “1 RMB Trial account” be re-registered?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>If you need more than one subscription, or have already tried a 1 RMB Trial subscription, please use the <a id="support_faq_msmc" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">standard Pay-in-Advance subscription</a>.</p>
															<!--
															详情请见：<a id="support_faq_msmc" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">http://www.windowsazure.cn/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/</a></p>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <!--
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-1" href="#">如何查询我的用量？怎样下载使用量报告？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>您可以登录 <a id="FAQ-15" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions/" target="_blank">Azure 账户管理界面</a> 
															
															<a id="FAQ-15" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions" target="_blank">https://account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions</a>
															
															，点击您的订阅以查询本月实时和以往月份的使用状况。</p>
                                                            <p>如要下载使用量报告,点击要查看的订阅名称, 点击右方的‘下载使用量’。您可以选择想要查看的日期。</p>
                                                            <p>以标准预付费订阅为例，使用 Microsoft Azure 账户登录到<a id="FAQ-15-2" href="//account.windowsazure.cn" target="_blank">https://account.windowsazure.cn</a> ，点击订阅名称，点击右侧的“下载使用率详细信息”。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												-->
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-subscriptions-download-details" href="#">How do I view detailed information about the downloads and usage of a subscription? How do I download and view the usage report? And how do I make pivot tables through bills?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Please follow these steps to see the downloads and usage of a subscription:</p>
															<ol>
																<li>Log in to the <a id="subscriptions-download-details-account" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/" target="_blank">Azure Account Management Interface</a></li>
																<li>Click the subscription name: “1 RMB Trial” or “standard Pay-in-Advance”</li>
																<li>Click “Download usage details” below the “Recharge” button on the right side of the page</li>
																<li>Click “Download Usage” to see the details</li>																
															</ol>
															<p>To download the usage report, click “Download Usage” and you can select the date you want to view. Taking the standard Pay-in-Advance subscription as an example, click the subscription name, and click “Download usage details” on the right side.</p>
															<p>The usage report is divided into three parts:</p>
															<ul>
																<li>Part I: Displays the information and status of the subscription, such as the subscription ID, subscription name and subscription type.</li>
																<li>Part II: Displays the billing sum of each service type in the billing month.</li>
																<li>Part III: Daily usage can be filtered by date or service name to see how much each service costs per day.</li>	
															</ul>
															<p>For example:</p>
															<p>In the daily usage of the virtual machine, the same type, size and usage of the virtual machine under the same cloud service is displayed, and the cloud service name of the virtual machine is displayed under “Component.”</p>
															<p>In the daily storage usage, the storage type, usage amount and name of the storage account are displayed.</p>
															<p>Refer to the online guide video for the pivot table:<a id="subscriptions-download-details-training-video" href="/video-center/">Portal Training for Standard Pay-in-Advance Billing</a>.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-subscriptions-remaining-days" href="#">How are the remaining days and remaining credits viewed?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <ol>
																<li>Log in to the <a id="subscriptions-remaining-days-account" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/" target="_blank">Azure Account Management Interface</a></li>
																<li>Click the subscription name: “1 RMB Trial” or “standard Pay-in-Advance”</li>
																<li>The remaining days and remaining credits are displayed on the right side of the page.</li>
															</ol>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-2" href="#">If the amount of the subscription account is shown as 0, the balance is insufficient or the usage amount is expired, what impact will it have on users? Can the data in the account be taken out? How many days will the data remain if the subscription is disabled?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>During the period of the 1 RMB Trial subscription and standard pay-in-advance subscription, if the remaining usage amount is 0 or when the usage amount is expired, your subscription will be disabled. If your subscription is in an inactive state, you will not be able to back up the data and you need to recharge the subscription to activate it. In order to avoid service interruption, please recharge promptly.</p>
                                                            <p>*1 RMB Trial subscription: After the subscription is disabled, your data will be kept for 15 days, and if you recharge it within 15 days, the subscription can be resumed; you need to reconfigure the related services. All data in the subscription will be automatically deleted if the subscription is not recharged after 15 days.</p>
                                                            <p>*After the Standard Pay-in-Advance subscription is disabled, your data will be kept for 90 days, and if you recharge it within 90 days, the subscription can be resumed; you need to reconfigure the related services. All data in the subscription will be automatically deleted if the subscription is not recharged after 90 days.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-3" href="#">How do I recover it after the service has been suspended?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>If the account is suspended due to insufficient balance, you can log in to the <a id="FAQ-16" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions/" target="_blank">Management Interface</a> of the Azure account <!--
															<a id="FAQ-16" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions" target="_blank">https://account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions</a>
															-->, and resume the service by recharging the corresponding subscription online. If it’s suspended due to other reasons, please contact 21Vianet Customer Service at +86-10-84563652 or 400-089-0365.</p>
                                                            <p>Taking the standard pay-in-advance customer as an example, if the account is suspended due to insufficient balance, you can recharge again to activate the subscription within 90 days of downtime (if you cannot recharge your subscription again within 90 days, all the data will be automatically deleted).</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="faq-subscribe-pay" href="#">What are the payment methods when you subscribe to an account? Can the payment method chosen for the first time be changed in the subsequent recharge?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>For 1 RMB Trial subscription users, the Azure platform offers two payment methods, “Alipay” and “UnionPay Online,” when you prepare to transfer the trial subscription to standard pay-in-advance subscription, you can freely select one from the three payment methods, “Alipay,” “UnionPay Online,” or “wire transfer” according to your needs;</p>
															<p>For standard pay-in-advance users, the Azure platform offers three payment methods, “Alipay”, “UnionPay Online” and “wire transfer”. The user can freely select the subscription payment method, and the subsequent recharge can be changed according to the requirement change each time.</p>
															<p>Please refer to <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-pay-for-subscription-via-wire-transfer/" id="faq_subscribe_azure-wire-transfer-overview1">Introduction to Wire Transfers</a> for details and operating procedures.</p>
                                            
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-pay-interrupt" href="#">How can I deal with an interruption in the process of using Alipay or UnionPay Online when purchasing a standard pay-in-advance account?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            
															<ol>
																<li>Log in to the <a id="pay-interrupt-account" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/" target="_blank">Azure Account Management Interface</a></li>
																<li>Click the subscription name: “Standard Pay-in-Advance”</li>
																<li>Click “Subscribe” on the left side of the page</li>																<li>Then click the yellow bar on the underside of the subscription name and continue to pay</li>				
															</ol>
															<p>Note: Using the UnionPay Online payment, after the order is submitted, the payment should be completed within 15 minutes. If the payment time is over 15 minutes, the payment may not be successfully done and the order should be resubmitted.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-alipay-interrupt" href="#">How do I deal with a payment interruption caused by incorrect input or the payment amount into the Alipay account?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>*If you are upgrading the 1 RMB Trial subscription to a standard pay-in-advance subscription, or are purchasing a standard pay-in-advance subscription for the first time, you will be required to resubmit the order and pay for it after 3 days of the order failure.</p>
                                                            <p>*If you are recharging the standard prepaid subscription again, you can click “Recharge”, submit the order again, and pay.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-virtual-machines-storage-cost" href="#">The virtual machine has displayed the status that the distribution has been canceled. Why does the storage still display the cost generation?</a>
                                                        <section>
															<p>Although the virtual machine has been in the status of the distribution has been canceled, it still consumes storage on the system disk of the virtual machine, so storage costs are generated.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-4" href="#">How do I check if the VM has been stopped correctly and is no longer charging?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>You can log in to the <a id="support_faq_man" href="//portal.azure.cn/">Classic Management Portal</a> <!--
															<a id="support_faq_man" href="//manage.windowsazure.cn">https://manage.windowsazure.cn</a>--> and check the status of the VM in the “Virtual Machines” options tab of the VM instrument board. Charging is still performed if the status of VM is “suspended.” Only when the status is “suspended (de-allocated)” is no cost incurred by the VM. For example, if the power supply option in Windows is used to suspend the VM, a cost will be incurred by the VM; yet, if the virtual machine is suspended from the administration portal, no cost will be incurred by the VM.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-query-virtual-machines-cost" href="#">Can I check the cost of each virtual machine?</a>
                                                        <section>
														<p>You can use the usage report to view the usage of the virtual machine, but you can’t query the cost of each virtual machine at present. That is because if multiple virtual machines of the same size and model are deployed in the same cloud service, they will be displayed as a row in the usage report.</p>
														<p>For example: Three A2 (Windows system) virtual machines are deployed in the same cloud service, so they will be displayed as a row in the usage amount report. The usage time after 24 hours of running will be displayed as 72 hours (i.e. 24*3).</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<!--
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-2-9" href="#">在使用 1 元试用和标准预付费项目期间，在剩余金额为 0，或者金额过期后，会对我有什么影响？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>在使用 1 元试用和标准预付费项目期间，在剩余金额为 0，或者金额过期后：您的订阅将被停用, 1 元试用账号的订阅停用后，您的数据将被保存 15 天，在 15 天内进行充值，您的订阅将被立刻恢复, 您需要重新对相关的服务进行配置。订阅被停用 15 天后，订阅及订阅内的所有数据将被自动删除；标准预付费账号的订阅停用后，您的数据将被保存 90 天，在 90 天内进行充值，您的订阅将被立刻恢复, 您需要重新对相关的服务进行配置。订阅被停用 90 天后，订阅及订阅内的所有数据将被自动删除。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												-->
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-5" href="#">What is the specific process for applying for an invoice? What are the types of invoices? Are there any restrictions on the invoice header?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Log in to the <a id="FAQ-q-3-5-account" href="https://account.windowsazure.cn/" target="_blank">Subscription Management Portal</a>, click “Subscribe,” click “Payment History,” click “Manage Fapiao,” and then register and apply.
															</p>
															<p>Please see the application process on:<a id="FAQ-q-3-5-azure-fapiao-process" href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-get-invoice/">Invoice Application Operations Resolution - Azure Online Business</a>.</p>
                                                            <p>The Azure service in China can provide Chinese tax invoices, including VAT special invoices and VAT ordinary invoices.</p>
                                                            <p>For the invoice title, the customer should fill in the information according to the actual situation.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-6" href="#">When can I apply for an invoice? What is the process of applying for an invoice?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>You can apply for the invoice within 3 business days after the payment is successfully done. For special needs, please contact the 21Vianet Customer Service Center at 86-10-84563652 or 400-089-0365.</p>
                                                            <p>Invoice application process: <a id="FAQ-37" href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-get-invoice/">Invoice Application Operations Resolution - Azure Online Business</a>.</p>
															<!-- 
                                                            <P>第一步：获取定单号</P>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>登陆到 <a id="FAQ-18-1" href="//account.windowsazure.cn" target="_blank">https://account.windowsazure.cn </a></li>
                                                                <li>点击 订阅名称</li>
                                                                <li>页面右侧会显示定单 ID。</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <P>第二步：注册发票账户</P>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>打开链接：<a id="FAQ-18-2" href="http://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/Register">http://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/Register</a></li>
                                                                <li>输入订单 ID，电子邮件地址，密码并确认密码后，点击“注册”</li>
                                                                <li>注册完成后，系统会发送一个激活链接到您注册的邮箱中，点击邮件中的链接激活发票账户。</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <P>第三步：申请发票</P>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>打开发票链接： <a id="FAQ-18-3" href="http://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/LoginView">http://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/LoginView</a></li>
                                                                <li>使用发票账户登录 </li>
                                                                <li>勾选上要申请的账单并点击右侧的“申请账单”</li>
                                                                <li>选择要申请的发票类型并输入相关信息后点击“下一步”</li>
                                                                <li>输入派送方式以及收件人地址等信息后点击 “下一步”。</li>
                                                            </ul>
															-->
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-7" href="#">What is the tax rate?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>According to national regulations, the tax rate of cloud services operated by 21Vianet is 6%.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-8" href="#">How can I register the invoice interface account? What if I can’t apply for the invoice after successfully activating the account?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Click <a id="support_faq_login" href="https://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/LoginView">https://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/LoginView</a> After entering the invoice application interface, you need to click [Register Account] in the upper right corner of the page to register the account, and choose to register the Azure account on the registration information page according to the product you purchased.</p>
                                                            <p>If the invoice cannot be applied for after you successfully activate the account, please contact the 21Vianet Customer Service Center at 86-10-84563652 or 400-089-0365.</p> 
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-9" href="#">How do I obtain the invoice after applying? Do I need to pay extra charges?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The invoice can be sent by express delivery or obtained by yourself, and is printed and delivered by 21Vianet Shanghai Blue Cloud Technology Co., Ltd, and you can select YUNDA or SF Express (for collect payment only).</p>
                                                            <p>If you have chosen to obtain it on your own, you can change it to express delivery. The self pick-up address is: Room 657, Building 3, No.88 Keyuan Road, Pudong District, Shanghai.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-18" href="#">How do I change the registered email of the invoice account?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Log in with an existing invoice account through the following link <a id="FAQ-25" href="https://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/LoginView">https://fapiao.cloud.21vianet.com/EmailAcount/LoginView/</a></li>
                                                                <li>Click the mailbox in the upper right corner, and select “Modify email address” in the drop-down menu. </li>
                                                                <li>After entering the current password and confirming the new email address, click “Modify.”</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>                                           
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-19" href="#">What if I don’t receive the invoice account activation email?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>If you have not received the account activation email within 24 hours after registration, you can click “Resend” on the invoice application interface, and then the system will send the account activation email to your registered email. If you don’t receive the activation email after you try “Resend,” please contact the 21Vianet Customer Service at +86-10-84563652 or 400-089-0365.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-10" href="#">How do I change the subscription name?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Please do the following:</p>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>
																<!--
																点击此链接：<a id="FAQ-20" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions" target="_blank">https://account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions</a>
																-->Log in to the <a id="FAQ-20" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/Subscriptions/" target="_blank">Azure Account Management Interface</a></li>
                                                                <li>Click the subscription name</li>
                                                                <li>Click “Edit subscription details” on the right side of the page</li>
                                                                <li>Enter the subscription name you want to modify in the subscription name field, and then click the in the right corner to complete the operation</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-subscriptions-edit-administrator" href="#">How do I change the service manager and subscription name?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Please do the following:</p>
                                                            <ol>
																<li>Log in to the <a id="subscriptions-edit-administrator" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/" target="_blank">Azure Account Management Interface</a></li>
																<li>Click the subscription name: “1 RMB Trial subscription” or “Standard Pay-in-Advance”</li>
																<li>Click “Edit subscription details” below the “Recharge” button on the right side of the page</li>
																<li>You can change the subscription name and service administrator account after you enter the page</li>
															</ol>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-14" href="#">How do I add a co-administrator?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Step 1: Create a new user</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Log in to the <a id="FAQ-21" href="//portal.azure.cn/">Classic Management Portal</a> with an administrator account</li>
                                                                <li>Click “Active Directory” on the left side</li>
                                                                <li>Click the AD name</li>
                                                                <li>Select “Add user” > Enter the user name and click “Next”</li>
                                                                <li>After entering the relevant information of the new user, click “Next” > “Create” > Record the new password and add the email address, and click the check mark.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>Step 2: Add the new users as co-administrators.</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Log in to the <a id="FAQ-22" href="//portal.azure.cn/">Classic Management Portal</a> with an administrator account</li>
                                                                <li>Click “Settings” on the left side</li>
                                                                <li>Click “Administrator” above > “+” below the page > input co-administrator account and check the subscription, and then click the check mark.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-subscriptions-add-administrator" href="#">How do I manage the administrator role of the subscription account?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%">
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <th align="center">Administrator Roles</th>
                                                                    <th align="center"><strong>Limit</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="center"><strong>Description</strong></th>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>Account Owner</td>
                                                                    <td>Each subscription can only have one account owner</td>
                                                                    <td>The account owner is used to register and purchase subscriptions, through which you can view and subscribe to bills after entering the billing portal. For example: creating a subscription, changing the subscription name and the service administrator.</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>Service Administrator</td>
                                                                    <td>One subscription can only have one service administrator</td>
                                                                    <td>The service administrator can log in to the administration portal, and by default, the account owner is the subscription service administrator.</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>Co-administrator</td>
                                                                    <td>One subscription can have 200 co-administrators at most</td>
                                                                    <td>One subscription can have 200 co-administrators at most who can log in to the management portal and are subscribers without administrative authority over the subscription.</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                            </table>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <!--
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-15" href="#">如何修改个人资料？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>使用 Microsoft Azure 账户登录到 <a id="FAQ-23" href="//account.windowsazure.cn" target="_blank">https://account.windowsazure.cn</a></li>
                                                                <li>点击页面上方的“个人资料” </li>
                                                                <li>点击"编辑详细信息"，在此页面更改个人信息即可。</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												-->
												
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-subscriptions-edit-personal-data" href="#">How do I edit the personal data in the subscription account?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <ol>
																<li>Log in to the <a id="subscriptions-edit-personal-data" href="//account.windowsazure.cn/" target="_blank">Azure Account Management Interface</a></li>
																<li>Click “Profile” at the top of the page</li>
																<li>Click “Edit details” to edit the personal data, and then save</li>
															</ol>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-17" href="#">How do I view auditing, cloud services and storage account quotas?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Log in to the <a id="FAQ-24" href="//portal.azure.cn/">Classic Management Portal</a></li>
                                                                <li>Click “Settings” on the left side </li>
                                                                <li>Click “Usage” to view the auditing quota, cloud services and storage accounts.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-add-quota" href="#">Is it necessary to apply for quotas several days in advance?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>It is recommended that you contact customer service to apply for increasing the quota at least 3-5 business days in advance to avoid delaying your use. If you are a standard pay-in-advance account user, make sure your credit limit is adequate.</p>
															
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                
												<!--
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-20" href="#">订阅停用后，数据会保留多少天？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>1 元试用订阅：订阅停用后，您的数据将被保留 15 天，如 15 天内没有再度充值您的订阅和所有数据将被自动删除。其他在线预付费订阅：订阅停用后，您的数据将被保留 90 天，如 90 天内没有再度充值您的订阅和所有数据将被自动删除。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												--> <!--
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-3-21" href="#">标准预付费账户如何查看使用量报表？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>使用量报表分三部分。</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>第一部分：显示定阅的信息以及状态，例如定阅的 ID，定阅名称以及定阅类型等。</li>
                                                                <li>第二部分：显示的是账单月内每一项服务类型的计费总和。</li>
                                                                <li>第三部分：每天的使用量，可以按照日期或服务名称筛选，来查看每一项服务每天的使用费用。</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>例如：</p>
                                                            <p>在虚拟机的每天的使用量中，会显示同一类型大小并在同一云服务下虚拟机的使用量，并会在“组件”下显示虚拟机所在的云服务名称。</p>
                                                            <p>在存储的每天的使用量中，会显示存储的类型，使用量以及存储账户的名称。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												-->
                                            </ul>   
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <div class="tab-control-container" id="implementationAndMaintenance">
                                    <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                                        <div class="more-detail">
                                            <h2>Implementation and Maintenance</h2>
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="implementation-maintenance-laas-pass" href="#">During the maintenance period, how long should the single IaaS virtual machine or single PaaS role instance be maintained offline?</a> 
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>
                                                        Answer: The single IaaS virtual machine or single PaaS role instance should be maintained offline for 30-45 minutes.
                                                            </p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="implementation-maintenance-point-vm" href="#">If my virtual machine is impacted for a relatively short time, can I define a more accurate time within the 12 hours so that my VM can continue running?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>
                                                                Answer: No. The customer cannot define when the VM will be offline during the maintenance period.
                                                            </p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="implementation-maintenance-choose-maintenance" href="#">Can I opt to have my virtual machine exit this maintenance?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>
                                                                Answer: No. Customers cannot opt out of this maintenance.
                                                            </p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="implementation-maintenance-applications-risks" href="#">What measures should I take to reduce the impact and risk caused by this maintenance on running applications?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>
                                                                Answer: We recommend that you should use the <a id="support_faq_implementation_availability" href="https://docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/virtual-machines-linux-manage-availability">Availability Set</a> in the architecture to prevent pre-planned maintenance downtime. In the availability set, for cloud services and virtual machines, this maintenance updates only one instance of the fault domain (FD). At the same time, we also encourage customers to cooperate with Microsoft contacts (sales field staff, technical support customer managers, etc.) for the availability set. For more information, please visit the <a id="support_faq_documentation_availability" href="https://docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/virtual-machines-linux-manage-availability">Virtual Machine Management Availability</a> web page.
                                                            </p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-15" href="#">Why can’t I access the VIP IP address and port of Azure VM from the local Ping?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>When accessing a virtual machine via an VIP address, the network communication needs to be through Azure Load Balancer. Azure Load Balancer currently does not open the ICMP protocol. Ping belongs to the ICMP protocol group and cannot access the Load Balancer. When customers need to verify the connectivity of virtual machines via VIP, they can use PSping and TCPping through the related tools of TCP protocol, such as Windows operating system and Linux operating system. Within the virtual network, virtual machines can Ping each other when they open the corresponding ports of the firewall.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-16" href="#">Can I create a virtual machine in Azure Virtual Machine?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The Azure data center is composed of tens of thousands of racks, each of which has a Windows Server 2012 operating system that we call Host OS, namely the operating system of the physical server.
                                                            </p>
                                                            <p>These Windows Server 2012 use a special version of Hyper-V virtualization technology which has virtualized several virtual machines and is called Guest OS.</p>
                                                            <p>The Host OS contains Fabric Agent control software to monitor the various information of current virtual machines for the Fabric Controller. The Azure end user can only access the Guest OS and cannot access the Host OS. The user cannot create more virtual machines in the Guest OS.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-17" href="#">Can I select an Oracle virtual machine in Azure?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The Oracle software image based on the Windows platform will be released soon, and users can select the “includes authorization” image. Oracle authorization will not be charged separately, and it will be uniformly charged by Azure. 21V provides Oracle services for the Azure platform, but this will add additional customer costs.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-18" href="#">Can I create a Windows Server 2003 virtual machine in Azure?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The officially supported Windows Server virtual machine template is:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Windows Server 2008 R2</li>
                                                                <li>Windows Server 2012, Windows Server 2012 R2</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>Customers can use local Hyper-V to create a virtual machine template for Server 2003 to Azure cloud, but there’s no way to get Microsoft’s official support if there’s a problem with the virtual machine.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-19" href="#">Do Microsoft Exchange, Lync and SharePoint support deployment in Azure cloud?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The SharePoint virtual machine template can be selected on the Azure virtual machine template and can be officially supported by Microsoft. The users of Exchange Server and Lync Server can customize the upload but cannot get Microsoft official support.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<!--
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-20" href="#">有没有单个实例的服务级别协议（SLA）？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>没有单个实例的服务级别协议（SLA）。举个例子，客户有一个应用部署在传统 IDC 机房中，一台 AD Server，一台 Web Server，一台 SQL Server。</p>
                                                            <p>在 Azure Virtual Machine 中，用户也可以选择使用一台 Azure Virtual Machine 部署 AD Server，一台 Azure Virtual Machine 部署 Web Application，使用另一台 Virtual Machine 部署 SQL Server。但是这样的场景是没有 SLA 保障的。</p>
                                                            <p>Azure Virtual Machine 承诺的 99.95% 的 SLA 是需要2台或者2台以上的 Azure Virtual Machine 同时运行，且所有的 Virtual Machine 都需要在同一个可用性集中。对于上面实例，用户如果想在 Azure 中实现 99.95% 的 SLA，需要同时部署：</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>两台 AD Server，放在同一个可用性集 A 中。</li>
                                                                <li>两台 Virtual Machine 部署 Web Application，且 Web Application 所在的 Virtual Machine 需要放在另外一个可用性集 B 中。</li>
                                                                <li>两台 Virtual Machine 部署 SQL Server，采用 SQL Server 2012 Enterprise 提供的 Always-On 功能，实现 High Availability。且 SQL Server 所在的 Virtual Machine 需要在另外一个可用性集 C 中。</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>补充一点，微软没有单个实例的服务级别协议（SLA）主要原因有以下两点：</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>从基础设施角度来说，无法预测单台物理服务器的硬件在何时发生故障，即单台物理服务器的 CPU 故障、网络故障、电源故障等是无法预测的。</li>
                                                                <li>从物理服务器的维护来说。微软在每个月都会给 Azure Virtual Machine 做升级和维护，维护期一般是在周五凌晨和周六凌晨(北京、上海数据中心分别维护)。维护期窗口一般为 6-8 小时左右，在维护期内的虚拟机实例都会被重启，重启时间一般在10分钟左右。</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>即该维护期是由微软定义的，用户没有办法拒绝维护过程，用户也没办法指定微软在具体哪个时间点，维护哪些虚拟机。在维护期窗口内，任何一台 Azure Virtual Machine 都会被重启。但是只会影响单个实例的 Azure Virtual Machine。</p>
                                                            <p>在 Azure 维护期内，会影响单个实例的 Azure Virtual Machine。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												-->
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-21" href="#">What is the load balancing mechanism?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Azure provides free load-balancing capabilities for Web apps, cloud services and virtual machines. One thing to note about load balancing is its treatment of Sessions. Generally speaking, the traditional load balancer has a Sticky mechanism called Session, which is based on the user’s Session information to transmit the user’s requests to one fixed machine. So, if the application on the server side stores the Session information, then users will smoothly interact with the server. Otherwise, the <strong> user’s Session will be lost and the application logic will be abnormal</strong>.</p>
                                                            <p>On Azure, the load balancers of the cloud service and virtual machines are of a pure network level. The balance mechanism is to take turns sending requests to the back-end server without supporting Session sticking. This requires a stateless back-end server that sends customers’ requests to any server and can get proper treatment. If existing applications have a status, then there are two solutions:</p>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>
                                                                    <p>
                                                                         The Session information is shared among all servers. The specific implementation models include: distributed cache (such as Memcache, Azure Caching), Session persistence (.NET and Java both support storing the Session information with a database, and Azure also supports Cache and Azure storage persistence. NET Session information:<br/><a id="sup_faq4_role" href="http://blogs.msdn.com/b/cie/archive/2013/05/17/session-state-management-in-windows-azure-web-roles.aspx" class="single-link">http://blogs.msdn.com/b/cie/archive/2013/05/17/session-state-management-in-windows-azure-web-roles.aspx</a>)
                                                                    </p>
                                                                    
                                                                </li>
                                                                <li>
                                                                    <p> Configure load-balancing clusters on virtual machines, such as Squid (Linux), IIS ARR (Windows). Microsoft’s MSOpenTech team provides a method to automatically configure the IIS ARR:<br/><a id="sup_faq4_arr" href="//github.com/MSOpenTech/WindowsAzureToolkitForEclipseWithJava/tree/master/Utils/ARRConfigurationAgent" class="single-link">https://github.com/MSOpenTech/WindowsAzureToolkitForEclipseWithJava/tree/master/Utils/ARRConfigurationAgent</a>.<br/>It was originally used to configure Java clusters in the cloud services, or to configure other IIS clusters</p>
                                                                </li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                            <p>The load balancing of Web Apps is slightly different, and its load balancing is implemented by IIS ARR. So it originally supports Session sticking. The implementation principle is to add a ARRAffinity Cookie to each response, so that next time the same user’s request will be identified and sent to the last server. That is, IIS keeps the server binding for each user, regardless of whether the application writes a Cookie or accesses Session.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-22" href="#">How do I perform data backup?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Despite Azure providing the perfect data storage solution, such as three copies of locally stored data and remote data mirroring support, that only solves physical data damage problems, but doesn’t solve the logic data damage problems. For example, the maintainer accidentally deletes the file on Blob or a program Bug, or modifies the data content. In addition, another role of backup is to support disaster recovery. There are two basic concepts for disaster recovery, RTO and RPO. Azure storage provides a remote image mirroring ability that can realize 30 minutes of RPO, but Azure doesn’t promise RTO. That is, if a site from the Azure storage service breaks down, the recovery time may be relatively long, and during this period, although the data is not lost, we don’t have any way to access the data, including image data.</p>
                                                            <p>The following table is the backup and capacity description of various data services in Azure:</p>
                                                            <table cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" width="100%">
                                                    
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Service Name</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Local data redundancy mode</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Local backup</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Remote data mirroring</strong></th>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>Storage service</td>
                                                                    <td>3 copies of Active-Active</td>
                                                                    <td>None</td>
                                                                    <td>Asynchronous replication to the remote location, RPO=30 minutes, without RTO</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>SQL Database</td>
                                                                    <td>3 copies, one master and two backups</td>
                                                                    <td>No (new function development)</td>
                                                                    <td>None</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>IaaS virtual machine system disk and mounted disk</td>
                                                                    <td>Only retention data, same as storage services</td>
                                                                    <td>None</td>
                                                                    <td>Only retention data, same as storage services</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>IaaS virtual machine temporary disk</td>
                                                                    <td>None</td>
                                                                    <td>None</td>
                                                                    <td>None</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>PaaS cloud services, mobile services and Web Apps</td>
                                                                    <td>Only published packages and code are be kept</td>
                                                                    <td>None</td>
                                                                    <td>None</td>
                                                                </tr>
                                                            </table>
                                                            <p>Therefore, <strong>it is necessary to back up the data in the cloud</strong>. In particular, each type of data is backed up differently.</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>SQL database. The Azure portal provides a backup function for the SQL database, and the user clicks the backup button to export the database contents to Blob storage in the Data Tier Application format. The user can download the backup file to the local SQL Server, or restore an SQL database with the file. For SQL databases, it is recommended that automated scripts be used regularly for backups, such as once a day for a 7-day retention. SQL databases do not support regular tasks, but we can run regular scripts with a Windows task plan or a Linux Cron. Refer to the specific commands at <a id="sup_faq4_bp" href="//github.com/richorama/SQLDatabaseBackup"> https://github.com/richorama/SQLDatabaseBackup</a>.</li>
                                                                <li>Blob storage. Blob storage itself does not provide a backup function, only the snapshot function. The snapshot can roll back the files of the previous version, but cannot restore deleted files (Azure does not support the Container snapshot). So, for important files, writing scripts for regular backups is recommended. The destination address of the backup can be another storage account or local account. The tool AzCopy can be used between different storage accounts for file copy and to transfer files between local accounts and Blob <a id="sup_faq4_blob" href="http://blogs.msdn.com/b/windowsazurestorage/archive/2013/04/01/azcopy-using-cross-account-copy-blob.aspx">http://blogs.msdn.com/b/windowsazurestorage/archive/2013/04/01/azcopy-using-cross-account-copy-blob.aspx</a>.</li>
                                                                <li>
                                                                    IaaS virtual machine. The currently available method is to use the virtual machine disk to snapshot the Blob file. Refer to the specific details at<br/><a id="sup_faq4_shaun" href="http://blog.csdn.net/shaunfang/article/details/8933405#t0" class="single-link">http://blog.csdn.net/shaunfang/article/details/8933405#t0</a>.
                                                                </li>
                                                                <li>
IaaS virtual machine files. Various traditional file backup tools can be used. For Windows Server, you can use the Azure cloud backup service<a id="sup_faq4_art" href="http://blog.csdn.net/shaunfang/article/details/8933405#t1"> http://blog.csdn.net/shaunfang/article/details/8933405#t1</a>.
                                                                </li>
                                                                <li>Database in the IaaS virtual machine. You can use various database backup tools or export the database to file backup.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>The backups of all the above data are done on a regular basis, and it is recommended a program or script be written, and to find a special virtual machine to run it.</p>
                                                            <p>Some companies have developed operational tools such as <a style="color:black;">Azure Management Cmdlets </a> provided by Cerebrata.<br/>The tool provides a command line tool that can backup Blob, Table and SQL database. Refer to <a id="sup_faq4_intr" href="http://www.cerebrata.com/products/azure-management-cmdlets/introduction">http://www.cerebrata.com/products/azure-management-cmdlets/introduction</a>.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-23" href="#">Can customers set the location of IP addresses (Beijing/Shanghai, etc.) by themselves?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The IP address is determined according to the selected areas of the customers. If the customer selects China North, the IP address will regard it as Beijing and China East will be regarded as Shanghai. Customers have no means of setting up other regions on their own.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-24" href="#">What is the Azure platform Affinity Group?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The Affinity Group allows users to configure multiple Azure services as a combination to optimize performance. The Affinity Group tells the Azure Fabric Controller that the physical location of the user’s Compute (calculate) and Storage position are very close and altogether, so that the Fabric Controller can search in the Container to place the two as close as possible, thus minimizing the network transmission delay and improving the performance.</p>
                                                            <p>The Affinity Group can provide the following functions:</p>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>Aggregation: the Affinity Group can aggregate Compute and Storage, allowing the Fabric Controller to place the two in a relatively close position in the same data center; </li>
                                                                <li>Reduce delay: Since they’re placed in a relatively close position, when the compute node needs to access storage, it can improve the delay and performance; </li>
                                                                <li>Reduce cost: Using the Affinity Group can prevent the random choice of data center deployment. Since the deployed Compute and Storage are in the same data center, users do not need to pay extra charges for data crossing the data center.</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-4-14" href="#">What should I pay attention to when running a business application with a virtual machine?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Azure will regularly update the environment of the host to ensure that all the operating applications and virtual machines in the platform are always in a secure environment. This updating process may restart your virtual machines. Restarting of the virtual machine will cause the operating applications in the virtual machine to go offline.</p>
                                                            <p>The data may be lost when the virtual machine is migrated. Some reasons for virtual machine migration are as follows:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>Adjusting the size of the virtual machine</li>
                                                                <li>Updating the host</li>
                                                                <li>Hardware failure in the host</li>
                                                                <li>The user configures AutoScale for automatic expansion and contraction</li>
                                                                <li>The user can add instances of multiple machines during high-availability concentration (>5)</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>In order to guarantee high availability of the applications/services hosted in the Azure virtual machine, we recommend:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li><p>1. Using multiple virtual machines during concentration of availability.</p></li>
                                                                <li><p>2. Making all components (front-end interface/application logic/data storage and so on) of applications be of a high-availability structure, and make each component be deployed in multiple virtual machines with availability, where each virtual machine involved in the applications deployment going offline shall not cause the entire system to go offline.</p></li>
                                                                <li><p>3. After the business-critical applications are deployed to the virtual machine, the application is thoroughly tested for the potential impact of virtual machine restarts.</p></li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>Learn more at: <a id="support_faq_more" href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/azure/dn683781.aspx">http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/azure/dn683781.aspx </a></p>
                                                            <p>Website for virtual machines: <a id="support_faq_foc" href="http://blogs.msdn.com/b/azchina/archive/2014/04/18/windows-azure-virtual-machine-restarted-or-shutdown-with-out-any-notification.aspx">http://blogs.msdn.com/b/azchina/archive/2014/04/18/windows-azure-virtual-machine-restarted-or-shutdown-with-out-any-notification.aspx </a></p>
                                                            <p>SLA website: <a id="support_faq_sla" href="/support/legal/sla/">http://www.azure.cn/support/legal/sla/</a></p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-4-1" href="#">Is there anything to note about using virtual machines to store application data?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Azure virtual machine disks contain a temporary disk, the D: disk (Windows) or /dev/sdb1 (Linux). They only provide temporary storage, so there is a risk of data loss, and the data cannot be recovered completely under some conditions. It is recommended that the disk not be used to store data long-term. And the user must bear the sole risk of data loss by this cause. And this case may frequently occur when the virtual machine is migrated to different host machines. The reasons for virtual machine migration include: adjustment of virtual machine size, updating the host machine or failure of the host machine hardware. Time for virtual machine migration cannot be predicted, and it may occur under the circumstance that the user does not conduct any operation. Therefore, we recommend you that the disk not be used to store data long-term. </p>
                                                            <p>Learn more at: <a id="FAQ-29" href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/azure/dn683781.aspx">http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/azure/dn683781.aspx </a></p>
                                                            <p>Virtual machine website: <a id="support_faq_pag" href="http://blogs.msdn.com/b/azchina/archive/2014/04/18/windows-azure-virtual-machine-restarted-or-shutdown-with-out-any-notification.aspx">http://blogs.msdn.com/b/azchina/archive/2014/04/18/windows-azure-virtual-machine-restarted-or-shutdown-with-out-any-notification.aspx </a></p>
                                                            <p>SLA website: <a id="support_faq_leg" href="/support/legal/sla/">http://www.azure.cn/support/legal/sla/</a></p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                            <a id="q-4-2" href="#">How do I add the virtual machine to the virtual network? What is the difference between the virtual machine network adding the virtual machine and the network not building the virtual machine? And how do I put an existing virtual machine into a new virtual network? </a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>For detailed steps, please refer to <a id="FAQ-30" href="/manage/services/networking/add-a-vm-to-a-virtual-network/">How do I Add a Virtual Machine to a Virtual Network? </a>After building the virtual network, establish a new storage account, and input the information, such as a URL. After establishing the storage account, build a new virtual machine, and input the information of the virtual machine, such as name and password.</p>
                                                            <p>After the virtual machine is put into the virtual network, it’s ensured that the virtual machines can communicate with each other via internal networks, and the advanced functions, for instance P2S S2S VPN, can be configured.</p>
                                                            <p>If a virtual machine is not added to the virtual network during construction, it cannot be added to a virtual network later. Currently, this kind of virtual machine only can be deleted (saving the disk for storing data), and a new virtual machine will be established by using the saved data disk, and choose to join an existing virtual network when creating this virtual machine.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-3" href="#"> What Windows and Linux versions defined by the customer are supported by the Azure platform?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>For details, please refer to: <a id="FAQ-31" href="http://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/documentation/articles/virtual-machines-windows-classic-createupload-vhd/">http://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/documentation/articles/virtual-machines-windows-classic-createupload-vhd/ </a><br/>and <a id="FAQ-32" href="http://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/documentation/articles/virtual-machines-linux-endorsed-distros/">http://azure.microsoft.com/en-us/documentation/articles/virtual-machines-linux-endorsed-distros/</a></p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-4" href="#">Support list for local/network equipment of Azure Site to Site VPN customers?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Please refer to <a id="FAQ-33" href="http://msdn.microsoft.com/library/azure/jj156075.aspx">Site to Site VPN</a> for details.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-5" href="#">How does Azure configure a website in which the deployment of the virtual machine is accessible from a public network?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Under default conditions, only the ports corresponding to the VIP address are enabled for remote connection and management. If a new website is required to be accessed through a certain port of the virtual IP address, the Endpoint of this service shall be added in this virtual machine. And this operation can be implemented via the Azure management portal or PowerShell.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-6" href="#"> What is the availability set? And how do I apply the availability set to increase the availability of applications? </a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>There are two extremely important concepts: Fault Domain and Update Domain.</p>
                                                            <p><a id="FAQ-34" href="http://blogs.technet.com/b/yungchou/archive/2011/05/16/window-azure-fault-domain-and-update-domain-explained-for-it-pros.aspx" class="single-link">http://blogs.technet.com/b/yungchou/archive/2011/05/16/window-azure-fault-domain-and-update-domain-explained-for-it-pros.aspx</a></p>
                                                            <p>Let’s talk about Fault Domain first. For example, I have a plug board in my study, which connects my laptop, phone charger, and TV and other appliances. If this patch board is interrupted, all the appliances connected with this patch board will be interrupted. Therefore, this patch board and the appliances connected with it form a Fault Domain.</p>
                                                            <p>The basic facilities of the Azure Data Center are made up of many RACKs, and each RACK is regarded as a Fault Domain. When the hardware on the RACK breaks down, the services on the RACK, whether it is an Azure computing service or a storage service or so on, will crash.</p>
                                                            <p>When the user deploys two Azure Virtual Machines without setting the availability set, Azure may deploy the two Azure Virtual Machines on a RACK, thus a single-point failure may occur. The reason is that if this RACK crashes, the two Azure Virtual Machines operating on it will crash, too. The probability of two Azure Virtual Machines crashing is the same as that of one Azure Virtual Machine crashing.</p>
                                                            <p>However, if an availability set has been established, Azure will deploy the two Azure Virtual Machines on two different RACKs. From the underlying design of the data center, it is guaranteed that these two different racks will not crash at the same time.</p>
                                                            <p>Now, let’s talk about the Update Domain. For instance, I have two Azure Virtual Machines (named VM1 and VM2), which all deploy my Web Application (version: 1.0) and are in different update domains. In the future, if my software is updated to version 2.0, there are two options:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>The user can update the two Azure Virtual Machines simultaneously. But if the customer end initiates a request under this issue, the server end cannot respond.</li>
                                                                <li>The Azure Fabric Controller monitors the two Azure Virtual Machines. Firstly, update the virtual machine software in Update Domain 0, followed by the virtual machine software in Update Domain 1, until the Web Applications in all Azure Virtual Machines are updated. In this way, it can be ensured that at least one Azure Virtual Machine can respond to a request on the customer end at the same time.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-7" href="#">How about the security of the Azure storage service? </a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>The Azure storage service will allocate two access keys to the user: the primary and secondary access keys. This access key is a character string of 256 bytes, and the user can apply it to verify every request for visiting Azure storage service data. Its operating process is as follows:</p>
                                                            <ol>
                                                                <li>The user builds the data access request first, which can be reading the Blob or writing the Entity to the Table or using Queue;</li>
                                                                <li>The user uses the access key to digitally sign the data access request by the encryption algorithm;</li>
                                                                <li>The digital sign is included in the HTML Header of the data access request, and then the data access request will be sent to the Azure storage service.</li>
                                                            </ol>
                                                            <p>It must be noted that two access keys are generated when we apply the storage account: one is the primary access key and another is the secondary access key. And the two access keys have the same function: being able to access data. Setting two access keys is to help the user change over access keys. For instance, usually, the user will have the primary access key, while if the primary access key is disclosed, the user can invalidate the primary access key in the shortest time (a new primary access key will be generated) and then switch over to the secondary access key. Meanwhile, the user does not have to alter the code, and just needs to alter the service configuration file, and there is also no downtime for updating the service configuration file simultaneously. Moreover, another effective way is for the application code to use the primary access key to access data, and if the verification fails, the code will automatically use the secondary access key. In this way, no downtime will be generated when the user changes over the access key.</p>
                                                            <p>In order to further increase flexibility of access control for Blob data, another data access control method is provided by the Azure data storage service called Shared Access Signature. Management personnel can apply the Shared Access Signature to generate a temporary data access request for other users, and the temporary data access request covers the effective digital signature, thus it can pass the data verification. It also includes information such as which information users can access and operation limits, and this temporary data access request will only be valid for a specified time. In this way, the administrator can not only allow other users to access data, but also not reveal the access key.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-8" href="#"> What is the difference between the SQL Azure Database and the traditional SQL Server Database? </a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Sometimes, the SQL Server and Azure SQL Database handle the same application working load. While one is a traditional database server applying the software licensing model, the other one is the service-mode cloud database, which is running in the data center of <span>21Vianet</span>, and is available as a pay-as-you-go model or a commitment rate model. You can easily choose the platform and business model most suitable to your technological requirements through these two products.</p>
                                                            <table cellpadding="0" cellspacing="0" width="100%">
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>SQL Server</strong></th>
                                                                    <th align="left"><strong>Azure SQL Database</strong></th>
                                                                </tr>
                                                                <tr>
                                                                    <td>SQL Server is the enterprise-level database server, which is able to provide “vertical expansion” relational data storage and handle types and scenarios for a group of wide-range on-premises applications. The SQL Server is not a service product and does not use a pay-as-you-go consumption model. The SQL Server is licensed per server or per processor, and is involved in a rich set of server hardware. The SQL Server runs on the hardware in your data center or the data center of the hosting provider.</td>
                                                                    <td>Azure SQL Database is a highly-available distributed “horizontal scaling” database service, hosted in the Cloud by 21Vianet. And the Azure SQL Database can be used to easily set and deploy the relational database capabilities by way of the service. The developers or administrators do not have to install, set up, and patch or manage any software. This service is built in with high availability, backup and recovery, geographical distribution, and disaster recovery.<br><br>In addition to the difference between the vertical and horizontal expansions, there are major differences in operating modes. The Azure SQL Database service covers management of the hardware and operating system, therefore, you can focus on building the solutions instead of purchasing, managing, patching, and licensing the hardware, virtual machines, operating systems and application platform software. While, for the dedicated database server (whether it is installed as traditional server in on-premises deployment, hosted in the virtual machine, or hosted by the third-party service provider), the developers and IT professionals are still be responsible for installing, setting up, updating, and patching the operating system and database software. Furthermore, users of the database server must design their own solutions for high availability, vertical expansion and disaster recovery, resulting in increased overall management costs.<br><br>Azure SQL Database is targeted at designing and optimizing applications with high scalability and high availability at a lower cost than a traditional vertical-scalability structure. As a result, Azure SQL Database is able to provide highly-available vertical-scaling solutions for commercial hardware and provide database functions in the form of services.</td>
                                                                </tr>   
                                                            </table>
                                                            <p>For more details, please refer to the <a id="FAQ-35" href="http://social.technet.microsoft.com/wiki/contents/articles/3536.sql-azure-zh-cn.aspx">SQL Azure</a> web page.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-9" href="#">How is Azure’s data redundancy guaranteed?</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>We provide off-site redundancy. The two data centers in Beijing and Shanghai are connected with exclusive 10G or more bandwidth. For data storage, Azure supports two modes:</p>
                                                            <ul>
                                                                <li>File redundancy in the same data center, that is, triple backups of the files in the same data center;</li>
                                                                <li>Off-site redundancy in different data centers, where the files are also triple redundant in the off-site data centers, so that there are 6 backups in two different data centers.</li>
                                                            </ul>
                                                            <p>For example, I upload a file to the Azure data center in Shanghai, and open off-site redundancy. First, my files will be backed up thrice in the Shanghai data center; at the same time, Azure will asynchronously make triple backups in the data center of Beijing by using the special line between Beijing and Shanghai. Under some extreme conditions, for instance if the Shanghai data center completely crashed due to earthquake, war, flood and so on, my files can still be safely stored in the Beijing data center.</p>
                                                            <p>Thanks to our excellent storage settings, many customers will make Azure their data backup solution.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-10" href="#">Is all data stored in Azure encrypted? </a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Regarding data encryption, Azure provides all kinds of encryption functions including AES-256, helping customers choose the best solutions for their requirements.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-4-11" href="#">What certifications concerning cloud and data security has the Azure obtained in China? </a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>Azure has obtained the following certifications concerning cloud and data security in China:</p>
                                                            <h4>ISO/IEC 27001:2005 auditing and certification</h4>
                                                            <p>The 21Vianet promise to perform the authentication in accordance with the ISO/IEC 27001:2005 (this is a wide range of international information security standards). And the ISO/IEC 27001:2005C Certificate has confirmed that 21Vianet has carried out information security control measures, which is defined in the Standard and recognized internationally, including guidelines and general principles for starting, implementing, maintaining, and improving information security management of organizations.</p>
                                                            <p>ISO scope: the Information Security Management System (ISMS), covering operations, security and management of commercial procedures.</p>
                                                            <p>The certificate is openly issued by the <a id="FAQ-26" href="http://www.cc.cesi.cn/">CEST Certification Co., Ltd. (CESI)</a>.</p>
                                                            <h4>Trust Cloud Services Certification</h4>
                                                            <p>21Vianet has adopted Azure’s leading technology, and with its strong localization operation capabilities, open platform, and high quality SLA (Service Level Agreement), strong data recovery ability and the best customer benefits, the company was successfully certified in the first batch of trusted cloud services for virtual machines and storage services.</p>
                                                            <p>The Trust Cloud certification is the quality assessment system of the cloud services directed by the Ministry of Industry and Information Technology of the People’s Republic of China and organized and implemented by the Cloud Computing Development and Policy Forum - the “Trust Cloud Group”. Certification aims to cultivate the domestic public cloud service market, enhance user confidence in cloud services, protect the formal cloud service providers, and promote the sound development of the market.</p>
                                                            <p>Scope: the following functions are in the current auditing scope: virtual machines and cloud storage, accepting the assessment of 16 indicators in three large categories: data management, business quality, and rights guarantees in the SLA framework. Among which, in terms of the stability of operation, Microsoft Azure virtual cloud hosting and cloud storage services provided by 21Vianet has achieved a 99.9% SLA guarantee.</p>
                                                            <p><a id="FAQ-27" href="http://www.3cpp.org/special/trustedcloud/" class="single-link">The assessment results</a> have been issued on the <a id="FAQ-28" href="http://www.3cpp.org/">Cloud Computing Development and Policy Forum</a> website.</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                            </ul>   
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
                                <!--
								<div class="tab-control-container" id="ICP">
                                    <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                                        <div class="more-detail">
                                            <h2>ICP 问题</h2>
                                            <ul>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-5-1" href="#">ICP 许可证和 ICP 备案是什么？如果我在 Azure 上部署我的服务，我需要 ICP 许可证或者 ICP 备案么？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>ICP 许可证和 ICP 备案相关问题，请参考<a id="FAQ-12" href="/support/legal/subscription-agreement/">世纪互联在线服务标准协议</a>
															中相关内容以及登录<a id="FAQ-13" target="_blank" href="http://icp.cloud.21vianet.com/">上海蓝云网络科技有限公司备案系统</a>
															进行相关备案。</p>
                                                            <p>Chinacloudapp.cn、Chinacloudapi.cn 和 Chinacloudsites.cn 域名由上海蓝云网络科技有限公司备案，仅用于向其客户提供 Azure 服务。 客户如果需要通过 Azure 平台对外提供服务，应使用自有的域名提供服务，并根据相关规定对自有域名做相应的 ICP 备案。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="service-dn" href="#">我可以使用 Chinaclouapp.cn、Chinacloudapi.cn 与 Chinacloudsites.cn 等 Azure 服务域名直接对外提供服务吗？</a>
                                                    <section>
                                                        <p>Chinacloudapp.cn、Chinacloudapi.cn 和 Chinacloudsites.cn 域名由上海蓝云网络科技有限公司备案，仅用于向其客户提供 Azure 服务。 客户如果需要通过 Azure 平台对外提供服务，应使用自有的域名提供服务，并根据相关规定对自有域名做相应的 ICP 备案。ICP 许可证和 ICP 备案相关问题，可参考<a href="https://www.azure.cn/support/legal/subscription-agreement/">世纪互联在线服务标准协议</a>中相关内容，并登录<a href="http://icp.cloud.21vianet.com/">上海蓝云网络科技有限公司备案系统</a>进行相关备案。</p>
                                                    </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-5-2" href="#">备案面签地点？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>北京：朝阳区酒仙桥东路1号   &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;电话：4000890365</p>
                                                            <p>上海：上海浦东区科苑路88号3号楼657室    &nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;&nbsp;电话：021-28986102</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-5-3" href="#">ICP 备案所需材料？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>主办者证件+网站负责人证件+主体负责人证件+网站真实性核验单+网络安全责任书+域名证书。</p>
                                                            <p>注意：以上资料原件在备案系统直接上传（域名证书除外）；</p>
                                                            <p>面签时“网站真实性核验单+网络安全责任书”需要原件，其他资料为复印件（以上资料均需加盖公章，个人需要按手印）</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-5-4" href="#">ICP 备案流程？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>您在<a id="ICP_process_13" target="_blank" href="http://icp.cloud.21vianet.com/">上海蓝云网络科技有限公司备案系统</a>进行注册，并填写、提交相关信息，我们初审通过后会通知贵方网站负责人携带相关核验资料到现场进行核验，通过后我们将信息提交到省管局，若审核通过则备案成功。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-5-5" href="#">ICP 备案周期？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>在您提交信息后，我们会在1-3个工作日进行初审；若审核通过，我们会通知您来我司进行现场核验；面签通过后，我们会在3-5个工作日进行二次审核，并将信息提交到省管局，管局会在20个工作日内下发审核意见。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-5-6" href="#">部分省份管局审核周期预估。（注：最终审核时间以管局为准）</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>2周：北京、四川、湖北</p>
                                                            <p>1周：广东、江苏、浙江、河南、陕西</p>
                                                            <p>3天：重庆</p>
                                                            <p>1天：上海</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-5-7" href="#">备案适用情况？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>新增备案：适合首次备案的用户。</p>
                                                            <p>新增网站：适合已有 ICP 备案，为同一主办单位新开办的网站或此前未进行过备案的网站进行备案。</p>
                                                            <p>新增接入：适合原来在其他服务商处有网站并且已经做过备案的用户，将网站转为我们接入，并且仍使用原来域名的用户。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                            </ul>   
                                        </div>
                                    </div>
                                </div>
								--> <!--<div class="tab-control-container" id="policy">
                                    <div class="pricing-page-section">                      
                                        <div class="more-detail">
                                            <h2>Azure 支持概述</h2>
											<ul>
                                                <li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-1" href="#">什么是故障维修服务？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p> “故障维修服务”是一个行业术语，指“一项技术在其正常功能适用过程中出现故障时所展开的支持工作，需要支持团队介入才能恢复正常运行。”</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-2" href="#">关于咨询服务，专业版 (Pro-Direct) 与企业高级版 (Premier) 相比如何？ </a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>专业版 (Pro-Direct) 咨询服务基于</p>
															<ol>
																<li>公开使用的Azure 的最佳实践文档。</li>
																<li>来自 Azure 论坛的信息 来为您提供支持指导，但它比企业高级版（Premier）支持程度有限。</li>
															</ol>
															<p>Pro-Direct 顾问不提供特定于某个客户的详细咨询帮助，例如设计、架构或代码评审、应用程序具体指导、配置调优（如性能调优）或规范验证。  Pro-Direct 也不提供现场支持或不参与项目实现，如（但不限于）Azure 上客户开发或部署的编码或配置。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-3" href="#">Azure 支持计划是否涵盖预览服务或功能？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>我们仅向“公共预览 (public preview)”服务和功能提供支持，且仅限于故障维修问题。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-4" href="#">我如何联系 Azure 支持？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>您可通过<a id="faq-policy-contact" href="/support/contact/">联系我们</a>轻松访问 Azure 支持。这是获取自助服务或支持工程师反馈的最快方式，他们将准备好开始提供帮助。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-5" href="#">为什么在线提交工单是首选的联系 Azure 支持的方式？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p><a id="faq-policy-support-azure" target="_blank" href="https://support.windowsazure.cn/support/support-azure/">在线提交工单</a>使我们能够以最高效简便的方法快速获得您的服务请求的详细说明，更快地转给最适合的工程师；相比于通过电话提供此类信息，在线提交使您不必额外花时间等待回应。因此，我们强烈推荐您使用网页或云助手在线提交。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-6" href="#">谁可以提交工单？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>您订阅的帐户管理员、服务管理员或协同管理员可以提交工单。此外，任何具有订阅的“写权限”（<a id="faq-policy-role-based-access-control-in-azure-preview-portal" target="_blank" href="/updates/role-based-access-control-in-azure-preview-portal/">所有者/参与者</a>）的用户均可以提交和管理该订阅相关的工单。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-7" href="#">什么是初始响应时间？提交工单后，多久可以获得相关人员的反馈？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>初始响应时间是指从您提交工单到 支持工程师与您联系并开始处理工单之间的这段时间。初始响应时间同时取决于支持计划类别和请求的业务影响（也称为严重级别）。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-8" href="#">你们可以用多快的速度解决我的工单？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>我们承诺会尽快协助您解决问题。有时这意味着在提供完整解决方案之前，我们会优先降低对您业务或者运营的负面影响。因此，我们承诺初始响应时间，及与您协同合作直至问题缓解。由于故障排查和解决工单所需的时间随问题的具体内容不同而大有差异，我们不能承诺解决时间，但尽全力与您协作尽快解决问题。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-9" href="#">我正在 Azure 上运行非微软技术或使用开源软件 (OSS) 构建的自定义应用程序，能否得到支持？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>客户可以在 Azure 平台上运行非 微软技术，包括但不限于 Linux、Oracle、SAP 和 IBM。对于可支持范围内的所有情况，支持团队会帮您辨别问题源自 Azure 服务本身还是自定义的应用程序。</p>
															<p>如果确定该问题是由 Azure 服务或平台导致的，我们将提供全面的技术支持。对于其他所有情况，我们将提供商业上合理的支持，如解决方法不足以解决您的问题，我们可能会向您推荐其他第三方支持渠道。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-10" href="#">我可以在在线提交工单时要求回电吗？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>可以，这是标准版 (Standard) 及以上的客户所享有的一项权益。如果您选择与支持工程师沟通，可以在提交工单时将“电话”选为您的首选联系方式。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-11" href="#">我如何在运行中断或服务中断事件 (SIE) 期间获取支持？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>在 SIE（服务中断）期间，我们会在<a id="faq-policy-shd" href="/support/service-dashboard/">Azure 服务仪表盘</a>发布及时更新, 这是接收最新信息的最佳方式。您也可提交工单，我们会与您协作以确定您的问题是否与当前发生的的 SIE 有关。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-12" href="#">我如何升级到更高级别的 Azure 支持计划？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>根据您购买的 Azure 服务及充值金额或者年度承诺额，您可以升级支持计划，请参考<a id="faq-policy-plans" href="/support/plans/">Azure 支持计划</a>了解具体的标准。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
												<li>
                                                    <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                                                    <div>
                                                        <a id="q-policy-13" href="#">什么是高级云服务依赖关系图 (CSDM)？</a>
                                                        <section>
                                                            <p>云服务依赖关系图 (CSDM) 记录了上游和下游会影响云服务的关键系统依赖关系。这将帮助您的 IT 人员在问题发生前识别潜在问题，同时帮助他们在问题发生时更快速地解决问题。</p>
                                                        </section>
                                                    </div>
                                                </li>
                                            </ul> 
										</div>			
									</div>-->
								</div>
                            </div>
                            
                        </div>
                        <!-- END: TAB-CONTROL -->
                    </div>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Azure FAQs - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Microsoft Azure, service content, FAQ, general questions, registration issues, billing, subscription and maintenance</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Windows Azure Support FAQs summarize some of the common issues when using Azure and classifies these FAQs into four types: general questions, registration, billing and reading, and performing and maintenance, helping you learn more about the Windows Azure through answering questions.]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>support-faq</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName>FAQs</urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
	<banner><![CDATA[
      <!-- BEGIN: Banner -->
          <div class="common-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#002050', 'backgroundImage':'//wacndevelop.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/support/banner-faq@2x.png','imageHeight':'180'}" id="support-contact-banner">      
            <div class="common-banner-image">
              <div class="common-banner-title">
                <h1>FAQs</h1>
              </div>
            </div>
          </div>  
        <!-- End: Banner-->
    ]]></banner>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate></pageTemplate>
    <localize>0</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <headerText>
      <![CDATA[<div class="_faq-banner">
</div>]]>
    </headerText>
    <forbidPublish>0</forbidPublish>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
