<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
    
         <p><tags
            ms.service="icp"
            ms.workload=""
            ms.tgt_pltfrm=""
            ms.devlang="na"
            ms.topic="article"
            ms.date="03/2017"
            wacn.date="03/2017"
            wacn.lang="cn" 
            ms.author=""/></p>
        <h1>ICP registration</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="wacn-date">Final renewal date is March 2017</div></div>
        <h2>Why should you register?</h2>
        <p>According to the Ministry of Industry and Information Technology’s “The Regulation on Internet Information Services” and “Measures for the Archival Administration of Non-operational Internet Information Services”, all who run a website within China’s boundaries (based on domain name resolution) shall execute an ICP registration. Moreover, according to the Communications Authority, you cannot go online if your domain name is not registered. All registered domain names must also resolve to a registered IP.</p>
        <p></br>
        </br></p>
        <h2>Registration process</h2>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/1-1.png" alt="procedure" />
        </br>
        </br>
        Please note:</p>
        <p>According to the “Administrative Measures for the Security Protection of Computer Information Networks Linked to the Internet” (Ministry of Public Security Document No. 33), Article 12, after registering with the Ministry of Industry and Information Technology, the local company or individual responsible for a website must register with a local Public Security Organization within 30 days after the website launches. If the Public Security registration procedures are not carried out, quickly submit a Public Security Registration Application on the <a id="icp_beian" href="http://www.beian.gov.cn/portal/index">National Public Security Internet site Website Security Management Services Platform</a>. If you need to ask questions about Public Security Registration, contact your local Public Security Network Security Department. If your local registration is in Shanghai, immediately complete website Public Security Registration according to the above, but if it is more than 30 days before this is completed, you must take appropriate measures to carry this out according to law and Public Security requirements (including, but not limited to, halting access to services). Thank you for your understanding and cooperation!</p>
        <p>Go to the <a id="icp_public-security-registration" href="/support/announcement/public-security-registration/">Public Security Registration</a>webpage for more details.</p>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>ICP Registration - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
        
            Introduction to ICP registration reasons  and processes
            
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
