<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage id="19341" parentID="11978" level="2" writerID="106" creatorID="94" nodeType="1059" template="16" sortOrder="14" createDate="2013-10-29T16:12:26" updateDate="2014-11-11T02:00:53" nodeName="What Is New" urlName="what-is-new" writerName="content" creatorName="xunfan" path="-1,11978,19341" isDoc="">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
         <div class="section-component">
            <div class="more-detail">
            	 <h1>Important Notice</h1>
            	 <h3>March 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-march_azure-site-recovery"><span>March 20 </span>Before March 31, 2018, please update Azure Site Recovery, which uses Access Control authentication<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Site Recovery helps to coordinate replication and protects running workloads. Access Control authentication services used by older versions of the Site Recovery Provider (also known as DRA) and Recovery Service (also known as MARS) agents are about to be retired. To avoid interruptions, please update these older versions before March 31, 2018.</p>
								<p>Earlier versions of DRA agents (before 5.1.2700) and MARS agents (before 2.0.9096) rely on access control service capabilities for authentication, but this service plan will be completely retired in April 2018. Newer versions of DRA agents (5.1.2700 or later) and MARS agents (2.0.9096 or later) use the latest Azure Active Directory authentication mechanism, which includes role-based control and finer access capabilities. Users who are still using DRA versions before 5.1.2700 and/or MARS agents before 2.0.9096 and replicating servers to one or more recovery service vaults are requested to update your old version to continue using the Site Recovery service and its upcoming features. If you have already performed these updates, no additional action is required. The new version relies on Azure Active Directory instead of access control.</p>
								<p>We recommend that you update DRA instances to version 5.1.2700 or later and MARS agents to version 2.0.9096 or later before March 31, 2018. Please complete all updates by this date to prevent the failure of replication and failover configurations in Azure Site Recovery.</p>
								<p>You can perform updates on the Azure portal:</p>
								<ol>
									<li>Sign in to the <a href="//portal.azure.cn/">Azure portal</a>.</li>
									<li>Open the Recovery Services Vault menu item.</li>
									<li>Select the banner that prompts this update to see the remaining steps.</li>
									<li>Follow these steps to update the Site Recovery Provider and MARS agent to the latest version on the server.</li>
									<li>To complete this process and update the authentication service, please select Update Authentication Service on the Registered Servers page in the portal.</li>
								</ol>
								<p>For more information, please read these <a href="//social.technet.microsoft.com/wiki/contents/articles/50899.upgrade-from-azure-access-control-services-to-azure-active-directory-for-azure-site-recovery.aspx?WT.mc_id=azurebg_email_Trans_33786_1598_CXP_Site_Recovery_upgrade_ACS_deprecation_NoAcct/">detailed steps</a>.</p>
								<p>If you have any questions, you can get support via the following options:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Click on the Azure portal’s <a href="//portal.azure.cn/?l=en.en-us#blade/Microsoft_Azure_Support/HelpAndSupportBlade/overview/">Help and Support</a> page for technical support.</li>
									<li><a href="//support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/">Create a work order</a> online.</li>
									<li>Call the 21Vianet technical support hotline: 400-089-0365.</li>
								</ul>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
               <h3>January 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-jan_cpu"><span>1/6</span>Protecting Azure’s Clients from the Threat of CPU Security Vulnerabilities<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>An update to repair a CPU hardware-based security vulnerability of extensive impact that has been completely deployed in all regions across China. The Azure infrastructure has been updated on the virtualization engine level this time. We advise you to continue to use best security practices when it comes to virtual machine imaging. Maintaining the security of our users is always our primary mission. Thank you very much for your understanding and cooperation during this update!</p>
								<p>For more information, please visit <a href="/blog/2018/01/04/Securing-Azure-customers-from-CPU-vulnerability" id="what-is-new-2018-1-4_blog-Securing-Azure-customers-from-CPU-vulnerability">Azure’s blog articles</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
               <!--  <h3>2016年12月</h3>
				<ul>
				
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="sixteen_year_dec_wire-transfer"><span>12/12</span>电汇支付全新开通</a>
							<section>
								<p>
								即日起，在线直购Azure服务的用户可选择“电汇”进行支付。只要您是新订阅或充值标准预付费账户、或者准备从 1 元试用订阅转为标准预付费订阅，都可以选择此汇款方式进行支付；电汇的最低支付金额为 5,000 元，详细支付操作方式请参考<a id="support_what_new_dec_wire-transfer" href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/billing/billing-pay-for-subscription-via-wire-transfer/">电汇</a>页面。
								</p>							
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="sixteen_year_dec_offer"><span>12/12</span>弹性的支付选择全新上线</a>
							<section>
								<p>
								即日起，在线直购Azure服务的用户可根据每次充值需求，选择不同的支付方式。只要您是准备<strong>从1元试用订阅转为标准预付费订阅</strong>、或是<strong>充值现有的标准预付费账户</strong>，在每次续费时，都可任意选择“支付宝”、“银联在线”或“电汇”进行支付。每种支付方式所要求的最低付款金额不同，详情请参考<a id="support_what_new_dec_offer" href="/offers/ms-mc-arz-33p/">标准预付费产品</a>页面。
								</p>							
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
								
				</ul>
				
				 <h3>2016年8月</h3>
				<ul>
                    <li>
                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                        <div>
                            <a href="#" id="sixteen_year_august_guid"><span>8/1</span>信任中心全新上线</a>
                            <section>
                                <p class="">
                                    全新的<a id="support_na01_safelinks_protection_outlook_com" href="https://www.trustcenter.cn/" target="_blank">信任中心</a>是一个由世纪互联运营的Microsoft Azure和Office 365与您分享承诺，提供信任相关信息的新平台。<a id="support_na01_safelinks_protection_outlook_com" href="https://www.trustcenter.cn/" target="_blank">信任中心</a>以可信为核心，围绕安全性、隐私保护、合规性和透明度四大基本原则传递深度可信云信息，开启全新的用户体检。原<a id="support_trustcenter_cn" href="https://www.trustcenter.cn/" target="_blank;">由世纪互联运营的 Microsoft Azure 信任中心</a>正式关闭切换至新的<a id="support_trustcenter_cn" href="https://www.trustcenter.cn/"  target="_blank">信任中心</a>。<a id="support_na01_safelinks_protection_outlook_com" href="https://www.trustcenter.cn/"  target="_blank">立即查看</a>。
                                </p>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </li>
                    <li>
                        <i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
                        <div>
                            <a href="#" id="sixteen_year_august_guid2"><span>8/8</span>提醒：2016 年 8 月 18 日后未经备案的域名可能会被屏蔽</a>
                            <section>
                                <p>作为可信赖的云服务，Azure 服务需要客户与服务提供商共担责任。世纪互联负责提供基于微软技术的云服务，并努力满足客户对安全性、隐私保护和合规性的需求。在配置服务之后，客户负责维护其环境，包括其自行部署的应用程序、数据内容、虚拟机、访问凭据以及遵守适用于其特定行业和区域的法规。详细信息请访问<a id="support_guid-migration" href="/support/shared-responsibility/">云计算中的共担责任</a>页面。</p>
                            </section>
                        </div>
                    </li>
                    
                    
                </ul> -->
                <h1>Product Update</h1>
                <a href="#" id="new_control_bexpend" class="folded-link"><em>Expand All</em></a>
                <h3>April 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-april_monitor"><span>April 4</span> Official release of Azure Monitor<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>We are very happy to announce that Azure Monitor has now been officially released in China.</p>
								<p>With Azure Monitor, you can use the monitoring metrics and logs within the portal to learn about the status and performance of your resources through the API in near real time. You can use Azure Monitor to configure alert rules to get notifications or automate issues that affect your resources. In addition to enabling multiple product integrations through APIs and data export options, it also enables analysis, troubleshooting, and a unified dashboard experience within the portal. With Azure Monitor, you can:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>View and manage all of your monitoring data easily</li>
									<li>Set up alerts and take automated actions</li>
									<li>Diagnose operational issues quickly</li>
									<li>Integrate with your existing tools</li>
								</ul>
								<p>For details on pricing, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/monitor/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-mar-">Azure Monitor Pricing Details</a> page. For more information about this service and how to deploy it, please visit the <a href="/home/features/monitor/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-mar-">Azure Monitor Features</a> page and the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/monitoring-and-diagnostics/monitoring-overview-azure-monitor/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-mar-monitoring-overview-azure-monitor">Azure Monitor Documentation</a> page. For more information on this release, please refer to the blog <a href="/blog/2018/04/04/azure-monitor-now-available-in-china/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-april-azure-monitor-now-available-in-china">Azure Monitor Officially Released in China</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-April_azure-stack"><span>April 3</span> Commercial launch of Azure Stack<i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Stack is an extension of Microsoft Smart Cloud Azure for local data centers. It brings the flexibility and fast-paced technical innovation of Azure Cloud Computing to a customer's on-premises environment, advancing the digital transformation of corporate business while meeting the diverse needs of hybrid cloud deployment. In China, Azure Stack will help customers build hybrid cloud solutions based on Microsoft Azure operated by 21Vianet. Chinese users can now purchase and deploy hardware integration systems equipped with Azure Stack hybrid cloud solutions through integrated system partners Lenovo, Huawei, and Dell EMC. For more information, please visit the <a href="/overview/azure-stack/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-April_azure-stack-overview">Azure Stack</a> page and the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/azure-stack/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-April_azure-stack-docunment">Azure Stack Technical Documentation</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-april_ccs"><span>April 2</span> Official release of Cloud Connection Service preview version <i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>Customers can use the physical line and network support provided by Cloud Connection Service to easily connect to local data centers and Azure data centers, and deploy flexible, reliable, and secure hybrid cloud scenarios to meet different business needs, including business continuity, disaster recovery, and key business support. For more information about this service and its pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/ccs/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_feature-ccs">Cloud Connection Service Features</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/ccs/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_pricing-ccs">Cloud Connection Service Pricing Details</a> page. For more details, please refer to the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/articles/cloud-connection-service/cloud-connection-service-quick-start/">Cloud Connection Service Introduction</a> documentation page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>March 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_service-health"><span>March 28</span> Official release of Azure Service Health</a>
							<section>
								<p>We are very happy to announce that Azure Service Health (ASH) has been officially released in China. This is a personalized dashboard that provides guidance and support when issues are encountered during Azure services. In contrast to service dashboards that provide basic status information, ASH can provide tailored information for your resources. It can also help you to make planned maintenance preparations and other changes to prevent the availability of your resources from being affected. In the personalized ASH dashboard, you can see:</p>
									<ul style="list-style:none;">
										<li>Service issues - existing issues affecting resources in Azure services.</li>
										<li>Maintenance plans - Maintenance activities that will affect resources in Azure soon.</li>
										<li>Health advisories - Reports and operational recommendations for downtime, stopping Azure functions, and excess quota.</li>
										<li>Health history - Various historical issues that have affected the operation of resources. This includes post mortems after the issues are resolved.</li>
										<li>Health alerts - Proactive notifications on service health.</li>
									</ul>
									<p>For more information, please see the <a href="/features/service-health/">Azure Service Health</a> page and the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/service-health/">Technical Documentation</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_cognitive-emotion-to-face"><span>March 23</span> The Azure Emotion API is being incorporated into the Azure Face API and will be retired on February 15, 2019</a>
							<section>
								<p>For users participating in the Azure Cognitive Services Emotion API preview program, the Azure Emotion API has now been incorporated into the Azure Face API. The Face API has been officially released and has integrated the emotion detection function in the Emotion API (preview version). The Face API can compare faces in pictures, identify previously tagged people, and group photos of the same person. As of February 15, 2019, the Emotion API (preview version) will be retired.</p>
								<p><strong>Recommended Action</strong></p>
								<p>You need to modify any existing code that references the Emotion API. The Face API and Emotion API use a similar REST interface. To access the emotion recognition function in the Face API, please use the <a href="//westus.dev.cognitive.microsoft.com/docs/services/563879b61984550e40cbbe8d/operations/563879b61984550f30395236" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_face-check">face-detect</a> action and set the Face API's "returnFaceAttributes" parameter to "returnFaceAttributes=emotion." For more details, please refer to the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/emotion/home/">Emotion API documentation</a>.</p>
								<p>According to your service tier, please migrate to the Face API before the date listed below:</p>
								<ul>
									<li> If you use the Free, Basic, or Standard version of the Emotion API (preview version) through your existing (previously created) Azure key, please migrate to the Face API before February 15, 2019.</li>
									<li>If you are about to use a brand new key, please use the <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/face/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March-23_face-api">Face API</a>.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>Click <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/face/overview/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_face-api-more">here</a> to learn more about the various features of the Face API, or start a <a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial-full/?form-type=identityauth" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_full-1rmb">free trial</a> now. </p>
								<p>If you have any questions, you can get technical support via the following options:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>You can open the Azure portal’s <a href="//portal.azure.cn/?l=zh-hans.zh-cn#blade/Microsoft_Azure_Support/HelpAndSupportBlade/overview/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_support">Help and Support</a> page for technical support.</li>
									<li>Create a work order online: <a href="//support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_online-support-azure">https://support.azure.cn/support/support-azure/</a>.</li>
									<li>Call the 21Vianet technical support hotline: 400-089-0365.</li>
								</ul>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_cognitive"><span>March 1</span> Azure Cognitive Services Face API Price Reduction Notice</a>
							<section>
								<p>Starting March 1, 2018, the Azure Cognitive Services Face Recognition API enjoys a price reduction. The reduction is as much as 50%. It integrates several improvements, including millions of identifications, to better help clients to realize their vision. For more information about this service and its pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_feature-cognitive-services">Cognitive Services Features</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/cognitive-services/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_pricing-cognitive-services">Cognitive Services Detailed Pricing</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-March_apim"><span>March 1</span> Official release of Azure API Management Public Preview Version</a>
							<section>
								<p>We released the public preview version of Azure API Management on March 1, 2018. Azure API Management is a suite of full life-cycle solutions released to both external and internal clients. Clients will use API Management to rapidly create a consistent, modern API gateway for existing back-end services hosted in any location, helping clients prevent abuse and overuse, as well as gain an in-depth understanding of usage and operations.</p>
								<p>The major application scenarios of Azure API Management include:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>A digital conversion is realized through external and internal usage of API with both efficiency and flexibility;</li>
									<li>Increase market share through provision of existing services and data to partners and the public;</li>
									<li>Attract clients by displaying key systems to the secure application of mobile and web applications, as well as by authentication, ratio limit and quota protection.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>In response to client feedback, we will introduce three important updates to API Management starting March 1, 2018:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Replace the daily charge with an hourly charge to make API Management more accessible and more cost-effective. All existing users will automatically start on the hourly charge model beginning March 1, 2018;</li>
									<li>Introduce a basic pricing layer in addition to development, standard and advanced pricing layers;</li>
									<li>The original standard pricing layer will include Azure AD (Azure Active Directory).</li>
								</ul>
								<p>For details on pricing, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/api-management/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-January_pricing-api-management">Detailed Pricing of API Management</a> web page. For more information on this service and how this service is deployed, please visit the <a href="/home/features/api-management" id="service-fabric_year_2018-January_api-management">API Management’s Service Functions</a> and <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/api-management/ ">API Management Documentation</a> web pages. For more information about this release, please refer to posts on the <a href="/blog/2018/03/01/Api-Management-Public-Preview" id="2018-January_blog-api-management">Release of Azure API Management Preview Version Blog</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>February 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-feb_vm"><span>February 1</span> Official release of new Azure SQL Server mirroring</a>
							<section>
								<p>SQL Server 2017 is the first release of SQL Server available on Linux (excluding Windows). You can now run SQL Server on the Azure Virtual Machine of available releases of Ubuntu Linux in your region. This mirroring applies to stand-alone instances, including all versions available to SQL Server: Developer Edition, Express Edition, Web Edition, Standard Edition and Enterprise Edition.</p>
								<p>Please refer to <a href="//docs.microsoft.com/zh-cn/azure/virtual-machines/linux/sql/provision-sql-server-linux-virtual-machine" id="service-fabric_year_2018-feb_provision-sql-server-linux-virtual-machine">Linux-based SQL Server VM</a> or <a href="//docs.azure.cn/virtual-machines/windows/sql/virtual-machines-windows-portal-sql-server-provision/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-feb_virtual-machines-windows-portal-sql-server-provision">Windows-based SQL Server VM</a> to get started quickly. Please implement the following operations to configure an SQL Server applicable to your scenario:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Select a platform — Windows Server or Linux;</li>
									<li>Select an edition, including the Developer Edition applicable to development and testing scenarios and Express Edition applicable to lightweight workloads;</li>
									<li>Select the Virtual Machine size which is pre-loaded with any edition of SQL Server.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/virtual-machines" id="service-fabric_year_2018-feb_virtual-machines">Virtual Machine Functions</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/virtual-machines/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-feb_pricing-virtual-machines">Virtual Machines Pricing Details</a> web pages.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-feb_HDInsigh"><span>2/1</span>Price Reduction Notice for HDInsight Linux Cluster</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure HDInsight offers Apache Hadoop, Spark, HBase and Storm clusters which are fully administered and supported. HDInsight provides you with the following features:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Create optimized clusters;</li>
									<li>Process and analyze big data;</li>
									<li>Workloads scaling upward and downward in an economical and efficient manner through separation of computation and storage.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>We have made price reductions to various ranges of HDInsight Linux clusters, such as A1, A2, A3, D14 and so on. For more information of this service and its pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/hdinsight" id="service-fabric_year_2018-feb_HDInsight">HDInsight Service Features</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/hdinsight/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-feb_pricing-HDInsight">HDInsight Detailed Pricing</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-jan_apim"><span>2/1</span>Azure API Management Public Preview Version Will Be Released Soon</a>
							<section>
								<p>We will release the public preview version of Azure API Management on March 1, 2018. Azure API Management is a suite of full life-cycle solutions released to both external and internal clients. The clients will use API Management to rapidly create a consistent, modern API gateway for existing back-end services hosted in any location, helping clients prevent abuse and overuse, as well as gain an in-depth understanding of usage and operations.</p>
								<p>The major application scenarios of Azure API Management include:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>A digital conversion is realized through external and internal usage of API with both efficiency and flexibility;</li>
									<li>Increase market share through provision of existing services and data to partners and the public;</li>
									<li>Attract clients by displaying key systems to the secure application of mobile and web applications, as well as by authentication, ratio limit and quota protection.</li>
								</ul>
								<!-- <p>为回应客户反馈，我们将在 2018 年 3 月 1 日起对 API 管理做如下三个重要更新：</p>
								<ul>
									<li>用小时计费率来代替每天计费率，使 API 管理更易访问、更具成本效益。所有当前用户将于 2018 年 3 月 1 日起自动启用每小时计费方式；</li>
									<li>除开发、标准和高级定价层外，引入基本定价层；</li>
									<li>原有的标准定价层将包含 Azure AD（Azure Active Directory）。</li>
								</ul>
								<p>有关定价的详细信息，请访问<a href="/pricing/details/api-management/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-January_pricing-api-management">API 管理价格详情</a>页面。要了解有关该服务以及如何部署该服务的更多信息，请访问<a href="/home/features/api-management" id="service-fabric_year_2018-January_api-management">API 管理服务功能</a>页面和<a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/api-management/ ">API 管理文档</a>页面。关于此次发布的更多信息，请参考博客<a href="/blog/2018/01/31/Api-Management-Public-Preview" id="2018-January_blog-api-management">Azure API 管理预览版发布</a>。</p> -->
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>January 2018</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-jan_network-watcher"><span>1/31</span>Azure Network Watcher Officially Released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Monitoring and diagnosis of your cloud Azure network can be simplified by the application of Azure network monitoring programs (Network Watcher). By using the diagnostics and visualization tools in the Network Watcher, you can:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Capture remote data packets in the virtual machines;</li>
									<li>Use a traffic log to learn about network traffic;</li>
									<li>Carry out diagnosis on the Azure VPN Gateway and connection.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>This service is comprised of data packet capture, connection troubleshooting, next hop address, IP stream verification, security group view and network security group (NSG) traffic log.</p>
								<p>For details on pricing, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/network-watcher/">Detailed Pricing of Network Watcher</a> web page. For more information on this service and how this service is deployed, please visit the <a href="/home/features/network-watcher/">Network Watcher Service Functions</a> and <a href="//docs.azure.cn/network-watcher/">Network Watcher Documents</a> web pages.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					
					<!-- <li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-jan_apim"><span>1/31</span>Azure API 管理将按小时计费并提供基本定价层 <i class="icon icon-update"></i></a>
							<section>
								<p>为回应客户反馈，我们将在 2018 年 3 月 1 日起对 API 管理做如下三个重要更新：</p>
								<ul>
									<li>用小时计费率来代替每天计费率，使 API 管理更易访问、更具成本效益。所有当前用户将于 2018 年 3 月 1 日起自动启用每小时计费方式；</li>
									<li>除开发、标准和高级定价层外，引入基本定价层；</li>
									<li>原有的标准定价层将包含 Azure AD（Azure Active Directory）。</li>
								</ul>
								<p>有关定价的详细信息，请访问<a href="/pricing/details/api-management/" id="service-fabric_year_2018-January_pricing-api-management">API 管理价格详情</a>页面。要了解有关该服务的更多信息，请访问<a href="/home/features/api-management" id="service-fabric_year_2018-January_api-management">API 管理服务功能</a>页面。关于此次发布的更多讯息，请参考博客<a href="/blog/2018/01/31/Api-Management-Public-Preview" id="2018-January_blog-api-management">Azure API 管理预览版发布</a>。</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li> -->
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-jan_vm"><span>1/15</span>Notice about R Server Virtual Machines Being Renamed as the Machine Learning Server</a>
							<section>
								<p>R Server is an enterprise-level server to host and manage the parallel and distributed work load of the R process in servers (Linux and Windows) and clusters (Hadoop and Apache Spark). It provides solutions structured by using R software with execution engines, expands open-source R, supports high-performance analysis, statistical analysis, machine learning scenarios and large-scale data sets. </p>
								<p>This renaming is reflected in the fact that Python is a new advanced analysis language. R Server virtual machines in the existing Azure can be used continuously within a limited period of time. If you obtained your R Server virtual machine through the Azure website, you can continue to visit existing R Server products. As it is only a name change at this time, using the existing application developed for the R Server in the Machine Learning Server will cause no problems. In addition, you will benefit from the Python language.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2018-jan_portal"><span>1/8</span>Notice of Discontinuation of the Azure Classic portal</a>
							<section>
								<p>We have added more functions on a continual basis to <a href="https://portal.azure.cn/" id="what-is-new-2018-1-9_portal">Azure portal</a> ever since its launch. We are also gradually carrying out a service transition from <a href="https://portal.azure.cn/"id="what-is-new-2018-1-9_manage-windowsazure">Azure Classic portal</a> to this portal. Azure portal is currently the core of all Azure services, providing a broad range of management experiences and functions, including the instrument panel for fixed resources, intelligent search to search for resources, Cloud Shell and Azure Resource Manager to achieve automation as well as a labelling function for resource management.</p>
								<p>We will shut down Azure Classic portal on January 8, 2018 to provide users of Azure portal with single and simplified experience. The existing users of Azure Classic portal do not need to perform any operations. We will provide you with all services and resources in the Azure portal. </p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>December 2017</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-dec_mysql"><span>12/31</span>End of MP1 and MP2 Example Sales Promotion for the MySQL Database on Azure Service</a>
							<section>
								<p>The 50% off MP1 and MP2 example promotion from MySQL Database on Azure service will come to an end immediately. Starting on January 1, 2018, the price of MP1 will go back to ￥ 7.64/hour (￥ 5684.16/month), while the price of MP2 will return to ￥ 12.02/hour (￥ 8942.88/month). For detailed information on pricing, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/mysql/" id="what-is-new-12-31_mysql-pricing">Detailed Pricing of MySQL Database on Azure</a> web page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-dec_media-services"><span>12/19</span>Azure Media Service’s “Real-time Channel Using Real-time Coding” Price Cut!</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Media Services’ real-time channel provides audiences with a streaming content transmission using 2 types of nearly real-time methods: an unencoded real-time channel and a real-time channel using real-time coding. All real-time channel types will charge users based on the running-state time of channels instead of charging on data transferred and processed. With the help of this service, you can quickly deploy a real-time coding channel within a few seconds. All mainstream formats (HLS, MPEG - DASH and Smooth Streaming) and top DRM content protection systems (PlayReady, Widevine and Apple Fairplay) are supported. The price of a standard real-time coding channel is now up to 38% off, valid for settlement cycles starting on and after December 19, 2017.</p>
								<p>To learn more about this service and pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/media-services/" id="what-is-new-12-19_features-media-services">Media Services Functions</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/media-services/" id="what-is-new-12-19_pricing-media-services">Detailed Price of Media Services</a> web pages.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-dec_iot-suite"><span>12/18</span>Azure IoT Suite Upgraded Remote Monitoring Solution Officially Released</a>
							<section>
								<p>We are very pleased to announce today that the upgraded remote monitoring solution Azure IoT Suite has been officially released. This solution accelerator is offered in .NET and Java in an open-source format. It has a whole new interface. It is structured for scalability and size.</p>
								<p>The updated remote monitoring pre-configuration solution adopts the optimum functions in existing pre-configuration solutions, including a direct deployment into subscription function taking place within minutes, open-source availability and comprehensive functionality from equipment to business applications.</p>
								<p>For more details, please visit the <a href="/blog/2017/12/18/The-next-generation-ofAzure-IoT-Suite-accelerates-IoT-solutions" id="what-is-new-12-18_The-next-generation-ofAzure-IoT-Suite-accelerates-IoT-solutions">Whole New Azure IoT Suite Blog, Internet of Things Solution Accelerator </a>and<a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/iot-suite/iot-suite-remote-monitoring-sample-walkthrough" id="what-is-new-12-18_iot-suite-remote-monitoring-sample-walkthrough"> Architecture of Remote Monitoring Pre-configuration Solutions</a> web pages.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-dec_MySQL"><span>12/01</span>The MySQL Database on Azure Services example sales promotion of MP1 and MP2 will come to an end soon. The non-public preview plan for Azure Database for MySQL and PostgreSQL is going forward in an orderly manner</a>
							<section>
								<p>The 50% off example promotion of MP1 and MP2 from MySQL Database on Azure service will come to an end on December 31, 2017. Starting January 1, 2018, the price of MP1 will go back to ￥ 7.64/hour (￥ 5684.16/month), while the price of MP2 will return to ￥ 12.02/hour (RMB8942.88/month). For detailed information on pricing, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/mysql/" id="what-is-new-12-01_mysql-pricing">Detailed Prices on MySQL Database on Azure</a> web page.</p>
								<p>In addition, the Azure Database for MySQL and PostgreSQL service which is on global public preview will soon embark into China. The new-generation Azure open-source relationship database service possesses the following new features:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>High availability service guarantee for 99.99% single examples (SLA)</li>
									<li>Obtain corresponding IOPS performance scalability by changing the size of memory</li>
									<li>It adopts the same architecture and service model as Azure services operated abroad by Microsoft. Although it cannot be directly connected with Microsoft’s foreign Azure data center, it is more beneficial for the client’s execution of the seamless transition of 21VIANET’s Azure and Microsoft’s foreign Azure.</li>
									<li>PostgreSQL Database service support</li>
								</ul>
								<p>We sincerely invite MP1 and MP2 users to participate in the free non-public preview. The service team can create free examples in the non-public preview of Azure Database for MySQL for the existing MP users’ database examples. They can be configured as general read-write main base or readable backup subordinate base examples for existing MP examples. During the non-public preview, the use of transited or newly created examples in services will be free. For specific details, please contact your sales representative and product manager from the product services team.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>November 2017</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-nov_event-hubs"><span>11/30</span>New Azure Event Hubs Pricing Layer Officially Released</a>
							<section>
								<p>We have provided Azure Event Hubs with a new pricing layer—dedicated event hubs. This pricing layer will introduce a fixed price based on an hourly rate. It is offered to all clients.</p>
								<p>Azure Event Hubs is an introductory service for super-large scale remote monitoring which can collect, convert and store millions of events. It is a fully hosted service, thus you can focus on capturing values from remote monitoring instead of data collection.</p>
								<p>Dedicated event hubs can provide single-tenant deployment for the most demanding clients. The major advantages of this service include:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Supports messages up to 1 MB</li>
									<li>Guarantees that the capacity meets peak demand</li>
									<li>Messages are kept 7 days without any extra charges</li>
									<li>Single stream can support real-time pipeline and batch-based pipeline by using the Event Hubs capture function.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>These enhanced functions bring more value to price per capacity unit and enable you to pay for more flexible capacity use. For detailed information on pricing, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/event-hubs/" id="what-is-new-11-30_event-hubs">Detailed Pricing of Event Hubs</a> web page.</p>
								<p>If you have any questions, please click <a href="/support/support-azure/" id="what-is-new-11-30_support">here</a> to create online work orders, or call the 21VIANET technical support hotline at 400-089-0365 to receive Azure support.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-nov_storage"><span>11/24</span>Azure Host Disk P15 Now Officially Released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure host disk is used in Azure virtual machines to realize the recommended disk memory products through permanent data storage. Host disk provides secure disk storage and simplified management as well as industry-leading durability and availability. The P15 disk is an advanced 256 GB host disk, providing a speed of 1,100 input/output operations (IOPS)/disk/second and a throughput of 125 MB/second. For more information about this service and its pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/storage/" id="what-is-new-11-24_storage-features">Storage Service Function</a> and <a href="/pricing/details/storage/"  id="what-is-new-11-24_storage-pricing">Host Disk Detailed Pricing</a> web pages.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-nov_cdn"><span>11/02</span>Azure Content Delivery Network (CDN) Price Cut!</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Content Delivery Network (CDN) offers a discount of up to 17%. It provides enterprises with a faster, smoother client experience, helps you structure applications with high scalability and high response speed while reducing investment cost. For detailed pricing information, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/cdn/">CDN Services Detailed Pricing</a> web page.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-Nov_analysis"><span>11/01</span>Azure Analysis Services Officially Released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Analysis Services can convert complex data into operable insights. Azure Analysis Services is based on the verified analysis engines from Microsoft SQL Server 2016 analysis services. It can provide enterprise-level data modeling according to the size and advantages of the cloud. In addition, your team can capture more benefits from existing investments by using current technology, tools and data.</p>
								<p>You can use Azure Analysis Services to:</p>
								<ul>
									<li style="list-type-style:disc;">Simulate and structure any data of any size;</li>
									<li style="list-type-style:disc;">Quick start-up without any need for management infrastructure;</li>
									<li style="list-type-style:disc;">Provide a secure visit any time, anywhere;</li>
									<li style="list-type-style:disc;">View data by using your favorite data visualization tools;</li>
									<li style="list-type-style:disc;">Manage, deploy, test and deliver BI solutions with confidence.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>For detailed pricing information, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/analysis-services/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-October_pricing-analysis-services">Azure Analysis Services Pricing Details</a> page. For more information on this service and how this service is deployed, please visit the <a href="/home/features/analysis-services" id="service-fabric_year_2017-October_analysis-services">Azure Analysis Services Features</a> page and the <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/analysis-services/tutorials/aas-adventure-works-tutorial">Azure Analysis Services - Adventure Works Tutorial</a> documentation page. For more information about this release, please refer to the <a href="/blog/2017/11/01/analysis-services">Azure Analysis Services Official Release</a> blog.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>October 2017</h3>
                <ul>
                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-October_apim"><span>10/31</span>Cognitive Services: Computer Visual API and Face Recognition Officially Released</a>
							<section>
								<p>Computer Visual API &amp; Face API have been officially launched in Azure portal. Cognitive Services is a set of APIs that have been developed over several decades to allow developers to build intelligent applications by mining high-quality visual, speech, language, and search technologies. For more information about this product, please visit the <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/face/">Face API</a> and <a href="/home/features/cognitive-services/computer-vision/">Computer Vision API</a> web pages. For detailed information on pricing, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/cognitive-services/">Cognitive Services Pricing</a> web page. For more documentation information, please visit the <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/face/">Face API Documentation</a> and <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/cognitive-services/computer-vision/">Computer Vision Documentation</a> web pages.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-september_apim"><span>10/20</span>New Azure Virtual Machine Models Officially Released</a>
							<section>
								<p>The DS13-2_v2, DS13-4_v2, DS14-4_v2, and DS14-8_v2 Azure Virtual Machines DS series have been officially released. It limits the number of vCPU to half or one quarter of the original number of Virtual Machine while maintaining the same memory, storage and I/O bandwidth. The new range limits the number of vCPU and reduces the cost of software licensing compared with previous series, thus increasing its cost effectiveness. For more details, please visit the <a href="/blog/2017/10/20/virtual-machine-newrelease" id="service-fabric_year_2017-October_VM-blog">New Models of Azure Virtual Machine Released — More Cost-effective Database Workloads</a> blog.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>September 2017</h3>
                <ul>
                	<!-- <li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-september_apim"><span>9/19</span>Azure API 管理预览版上线</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure API 管理是一个可立即使用的、生命周期完整的解决方案，用户可用其发布 API。使用 API 管理可以快速创建一致、现代的 API 网关，随时随地托管现有的后端服务，避免过度使用，并深入了解 API 的使用状态。API 不再是技术资产，而是新业务模式、数字战略和生态系统的驱动力。有关定价的详细信息，请访问<a href="/pricing/details/api-management/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-September_pricing-api-management">API 管理价格详情</a>页面。要了解有关该服务的更多信息，请访问<a href="/home/features/api-management" id="service-fabric_year_2017-September_api-management">API 管理服务功能</a>页面。</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li> -->
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-september_standard-managed-disks"><span>9/30</span>Azure Storage Standard Managed Disk Promotion Ends</a>
							<section>
								<p>Standard Managed Disk employs an HDD-based storage medium. It is most suitable for development/testing not sensitive to performance changes and other non-frequent access workloads.The total cost of the Standard Managed Disk storage depends on the size and quantity of disks, quantity of transactions and transition volume of outbound data. For IOPS and throughput, there is no difference between the various sizes of Standard Managed Disk. The offer is over effective immediately, and resumes its regular price on October 1, 2017. For more information on this service and its pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/storage" id="service-fabric_year_2017-september_standard-managed-disks">Storage Service Features</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/storage#tabContent3-1" id="service-fabric_year_2017-september_standard-managed-disks">Managed Disk Pricing Details</a> page.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-september_blog-data-science-vm-images"><span>9/8</span>Data Science Virtual Machine Mirror Formally Launched</a>
							<section>
								<p>The Data Science Virtual Machine (DSVM) is an Azure Virtual Machine mirror customized for data science. It integrates many popular data sciences, preliminary installation tools and preliminary configuration tools that can quickly build smart applications for advanced analysis on both Windows Server and Linux servers. The design and configuration of DSVM applies to a broad range of usage scenarios. You can zoom in and out of the environment based on changes in project requirements and use your favorite languages to program for data sciences. You can also install other customary systems based on your specific requirements. For more details, please visit this <a href="/blog/2017/09/08/data-science-vm-images/">blog</a>.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>

                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-september_blog-visual-studio2017-vm-images"><span>9/7</span>Azure Visual Studio 2017 Virtual Machine Mirror Formally Launched</a>
							<section>
								<p>VS 2017 makes the development of Azure applications a seamless integration experience. It includes all features required for Azure development and provides all features that allow the user to easily build, manage and deploy cloud applications on a large scale on the Azure platform. After launch of the Azure Virtual Machine mirror in China, the user now can easily build a development environment on Azure, and use the Visual Studio to build and test applications. For more details, please visit this <a href="/blog/2017/09/07/visual-studio2017-vm-images/">blog</a>.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>

                	<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-september_apim"><span>9/7</span>Azure Launches New Performance Level of SQL Database and Additional Storage Preview Version</a>
							<section>
								<p>S4, S6, S7, S9 and S12 are five new standard performance levels recently launched. At present, they remain at the previous status, and are very suitable for the CPU-intensive workloads that don’t require IO performance (provided by the higher level).</p>
								<p>The new additional storage allows the user to purchase the additional storage without adding DTU or eDTU. Now, the user can purchase S3-S12, P1-P6 and PRS1-PRS6 databases with a size of up to 1TB, a standard elastic pool with a size of up to 4TB, and a small eDTU advanced pool with a size of up to 1TB.</p>
								<p>For more information about new performance levels and additional storage, please visit the <a href="/home/features/sql-database/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-September_sql-database">SQL Database Features</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/sql-database/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-September_pricing-sql-database">SQL Database Pricing Details</a> page.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_vpn-gateway"><span>9/7</span>Azure Media Redactor Formally Launched</a>
							<section>
								<p>The Azure Media Redactor is a powerful cloud video processing service that can automatically detect and dim human faces in the video and is well suited for public security, news media and other scenarios. It is based on the AI technology developed by Microsoft and used to improve efficiency of manual video editing. For detailed price information, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/media-services/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-September_pricing-media-services">Media Services Detailed Pricing Information</a> page. For more information about the service and how to deploy it, please visit the <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/media-services/media-services-face-redaction" id="service-fabric_year_2017-September_media-services-face-redaction">Using Azure Media Analytics for Facial Modifications</a> documentation and the <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/media-services/media-services-redactor-walkthrough" id="service-fabric_year_2017-September_media-services-redactor-walkthrough">Using Azure Media Analytics for Facial Modification Exercises</a> documentation.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
                </ul>
                <h3>August 2017</h3>
				<ul>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_standard-managed-disks"><span>8/30</span>Azure to End Standard Hosting Disk Service Marketing Campaign Soon</a>
							<section>
								<p>Standard Managed Disk employs an HDD-based storage medium. It is most suitable for development/testing not sensitive to performance changes and other non-frequent access workloads. The total cost of Standard Managed Disk storage depends on the size and quantity of disks, quantity of transactions and transition volume of outbound data. For IOPS and throughput, there is no difference between various sizes of Standard Managed Disk. The current price is a promotional price, and the offer will continue until September 30, 2017. Its regular price will be resumed on October 1, 2017. For more information on this service and its pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/storage" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_standard-managed-disks">Storage Services Features</a>page and the <a href="/pricing/details/storage#tabContent3-1" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_standard-managed-disks">Managed Disk Pricing Details</a> page.</p>
								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_hdinsight"><span>8/30</span>HDInsight Kafka Preview Version Launched</a>
							<section>
								<p>Now, a user can save the trouble of signing up and directly deploy Kafka Cluster and Managed Disk through the Azure portal. The service will provide strong scalability and reduce the cost with the expansion of the workload. With the pre-built system on the Azure Resource Manager template, the user can take only a few minutes to deploy a manageable, safe streaming channel (Kafka, Storm or Spark Stream) integration experience. For pricing details, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/hdinsight/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_pricing-hdinsight">HDInsight Pricing Details</a> page. To learn more information on the service and how to deploy it, please visit the <a href="/home/features/hdinsight/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_features-hdinsight">HDInsight Features</a> page and the <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/hdinsight/hdinsight-apache-kafka-get-started">Apache Kafka on HDInsight Introduction</a> documentation page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
						
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_vpn-gateway"><span>8/30</span>New-generation Azure VPN Gateway Formally Launched</a>
							<section>
								<p>We recently introduced three all-new VPN gateways (VpnGw1, VpnGw2 and VpnGw3) for the Azure VPN gateway service to considerably improve the bandwidth and the service level agreement (SLA).</p>
								<ol>
									<li style="list-style:disc;">The Basic level will stay unchanged under the current architecture. Standard and High-performance levels will be replaced with VpnGw1, VpnGw2 and VpnGw3.</li>
									<li style="list-style:disc;">VPN Gateways already deployed so far will not be automatically upgraded to the new level, but will maintain the current performance and pricing. Even so, we still suggest you migrate current gateways to a new level. Given no price change, the new gateways will enhance the performance by as much as 7 times. For pricing details, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/vpn-gateway/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_pricing-vpn-gateway">VPN Gateway Pricing Details</a> page. To get more information on the service and how to deploy it, please visit the <a href="/home/features/vpn-gateway/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_features-vpn-gateway">VPN Gateway Services</a> page and <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/vpn-gateway/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_docs-vpn-gateway">VPN Gateway Documentation</a> page.</li>
								</ol>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>

					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_storage_store"><span>8/18</span> Azure Storage Disk Hosting Service Now Formally Launched</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure has formally launched the Managed Disk Service in the China region. Azure Managed Disk manages the <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/storage/storage-introduction" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_storage-introduction">Storage accounts</a> associated with the Virtual Machine disk to simplify the disk management of Azure IaaS Virtual Machines. You only need to designate the type and size of the required disk, and Azure will create and manage the disk for you. You can use more than one Managed Disk for every Virtual Machine. The Managed Disk Service provides two persistent storage options: Premium Managed Disk and Standard Managed Disk.</p>
								<p>Disk Storage provides high-security persistent disk options to support Virtual Machines. Premium Disk Storage (SSD) is the most suitable for I/O-intensive applications, and low latency and high throughput are key features of the application. Now, in the China region, Azure has introduced two large-volume disks with the sizes of P40 (2TB) and P50 (4TB) for the Managed and Non-managed Premium Disks. Premium Disk has increased the maximum IPOS to 7,500 and the bandwidth to 250MBps.</p>

								<p>As far as testing is concerned, Standard Disk Storage (HDD) helps you cut down on costs during rapid vertical scaling. In the China region, we also provide two new options, S40 (2TB) and S50 (4TB), for the Standard Managed Disk service. For the Standard Non-managed Disk, we can create a disk with a maximum size of 4.095TB. Standard disks of all sizes will provide an IOPS as high as 500 and a bandwidth of 60MBps.</p>

								<p>When you only have a small disk, such as the operating system disk of a Linux Virtual Machine, but need to obtain consistent disk performance, you can use these new disks of varying sizes to reduce costs. The P4 Premium Managed Disk provides an IOPS of up to 120 and a disk throughput of 25MBps, while these figures for the P6 Premium Managed Disk are 240 and 50MBps respectively.</p>
								<p>For more details, please visit <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/migrate-to-managed-disks">Migrate Azure VM to Azure Managed Disks</a>. To learn more about the services and pricing, please visit the <a href="/home/features/storage" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_storage">Storage Disk Features</a> page and the <a href="/pricing/details/storage#tabContent3-1" id="service-fabric_year_2017-august_storage-detail">Hosting Disk Pricing</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-August_ade"><span>8/18</span>Azure Has Launched Disk Encryption Service in China</a>
							<section>
								<p>Today, we are announcing Azure’s release of Disk Encryption Services for Windows and Linux IaaS Virtual Machines in the China region. This signifies that Azure has released Disk Encryption Services for all users of Windows and Linux IaaS Standard Virtual Machines (Standard A, D, DS, F and other series), and customers now can employ encryption technologies based on industrial standards to protect their static operating systems and data disks.</p>
								<p>The Azure Disk Encryption feature allows you to encrypt the disks of Windows and Linux IaaS Virtual Machines. Azure Disk Encryption technology employs the <a href="https://technet.microsoft.com/zh-cn/library/cc732774.aspx" id="service-fabric_year_2017-june_ade_BitLocker" target="_blank" rel="nofollow">BitLocker</a> feature of Windows as the industrial standard and Linux’s DM-Crypt feature to encrypt operating system and data disks and protect your data. Moreover, the technology also helps you deliver on your organization’s commitment to security and compliance. This solution, integrated with the <a href="/documentation/services/key-vault/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-june_ade_documentation-key-vault">Azure Key Vault</a>, helps you protect, control and manage disk encryption keys for key vault subscriptions. At the same time, the solution ensures all data in the disks of Virtual Machines realize static encryption in your Azure Storage.</p>
								<p>For more details, please see the document <a href="https://docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/security/azure-security-disk-encryption/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-june_ade_documentation">Azure Disk Encryption Applicable to Windows and Linux IaaS VM</a> page.</p>								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
				</ul>
                <h3>July 2017</h3>
				<ul>	
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_cosmos-db"><span>7/19</span>Your Current DocumentDB Resource Has Become Part of the Azure Cosmos DB Resources on the Azure portal.</a>
							<section>
								<p>As announced at the Microsoft Build conference in 2017, Azure Cosmos DB is the first multimodal database service spreading across the entire world, and provides universal SLAs that can be used to forge global applications. You have possibly noticed that your current DocumentDB resource has become part of the Azure Cosmos DB resources on the Azure portal. Azure Cosmos DB provides the same SLA and pricing as those of DocumentDB, but offers more features and functions. Please note: As part of the recent evolution, the indicator and SKU names will be changed after August 1, 2017, and indicator GUID and pricing will remain unchanged. For more information on the recent evolution, please visit the <a href="/blog/2017/07/19/WelcometoAzureCosmosDB/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_cosmos-db_blog">Dear DocumentDB User, Welcome to Azure Cosmos DB!</a> blog. For product information, please visit the <a href="/home/features/cosmos-db/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_cosmos-db_production">Cosmos DB Features</a> page. For pricing information, please visit <a href="/pricing/details/cosmos-db/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_cosmos-db_pricing">Cosmos DB Pricing Details</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_event-hubs"><span>7/11</span>Azure Event Center has Formally Released the Capture Function</a>
							<section>
								<p>Azure Event Center is a data stream intake service that features real time, high scalability and full management. It can take in millions of events per second and generate a data stream with multiple applications. This enables you to process and analyze mass data generated by connected appliances and applications.</p>
								<p>The Capture feature of Event Hubs (namely, the Event Hubs documentation in the earlier public preview version) has been formally released. This feature allows you to directly access data of the Event Hubs based on the time and size you define, and send these data to your destination, thereby specifically addressing your demand for long-term data saving and processing of downstream small batch data:</p>
								<ul>
									<li>Enable simple settings;</li>
									<li>Reduce the overall ownership cost;</li>
									<li>Realize seamless integration with Azure Storage (which will soon add more data storage).</li>
									<li>Realize quasi real-time batch analysis.</li>
								</ul>
								<p>For more information, please visit the <a href="/blog/2017/07/10/EventHubCapturePublishing/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_event-hubs_blog">Event Hubs Capture Formally Launched</a> blog. For relevant product information, please visit the <a href="/home/features/event-hubs/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_event-hubs_production">Event Hubs Features</a> page. For relevant pricing information, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/event-hubs/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_event-hubs_pricing">Event Hubs Pricing Details</a> page.</p>
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_messaging"><span>7/11</span>Azure Relay Hybrid Connection in Azure Server Bus Formally Launched</a>
							<section>
								<p>The Azure Relay hybrid connection in the Azure Server Bus has been formally launched. For pricing details, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/service-bus/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_messaging_pricing">Server Bus Pricing Details</a> page. With the hybrid connection, you can use HTTPS, WebSockets and other open standards to realize safe connection with resources behind the local firewall and other cloud-based services or resources. To learn details about the service, please visit the <a href="/home/features/service-bus/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_messaging_production">Server Bus Features</a> page.</p>								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_traffic-manager"><span>7/11</span>Azure Traffic Manager’s Rapid Failover Formally Released</a>
							<section>
								<p>When using Azure Traffic Manager, you can employ the Rapid Failover service to realize more features and optimize and customize failover behaviors. The Rapid Failover feature has now been formally released. You can choose to redirect users even faster to keep yourself away from abnormal terminals. Specifically now you can:</p>
								<ol>
									<li>Define a 10s interval for the flow manager to check the working status of the terminal (the interval is shorter than the present 30s);</li>
									<li>Configure the continuous failure counter (which falls between 1 and 10) before the terminal is marked as abnormal;</li>
									<li>Configure the timeout interval for every detection attempt (if the detection interval is 10s, the timeout interval will fall between 5s and 9s, and if the detection interval is 30s, the timeout interval will fall between 5s to 10s);</li>
									<li>Set the time-to-live (TTL) response.</li>
								</ol>
								<p>When the aforementioned configurable settings are used together, Traffic Manager can divert traffic from a degraded terminal at a faster speed than the standard settings by 90%. You can use Azure portal, PowerShell, CLI, REST API or SDK to set the Rapid Failover.</p>
								<p>For more pricing information, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/traffic-manager/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_traffic-manager_pricing">Traffic Manager Pricing Details</a> page. To learn how to use the Rapid Failover feature, please visit the <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/traffic-manager/traffic-manager-monitoring?WT.mc_id=azurebg_email_Trans_33675_1421_Release_MOSP_Tier2_June26_CORRECTION/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_traffic-manager_document">Traffic Manager Terminal Monitoring and Failover</a> documentation.</p>								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>
					
					<li>
						<i class="icon icon-plus"></i>
						<div>
							<a href="#" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_documentdb"><span>7/7</span>Azure DocumentDB Launches Corporate Preview Version of Minute Preliminary Configuration</a>
							<section>
								<p>Now, you can employ the throughput configuration mode with a lower cost to supplement the seconds-based normal throughput (RU/s) in minute. For more pricing information, please visit the <a href="/pricing/details/documentdb/" id="service-fabric_year_2017-july_documentdb_pricing">DocumentDB Pricing Details</a> page.</p>								
							</section>
						</div>
					</li>					
				</ul>
		  
                </ul>
  
            </div>                      
        </div>
        <a id="_whatisnew-linkbutton" href="/what-is-new/archives/2017/" class="single-link h2-link">View Historical Circular<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Latest Circular on Azure Cloud Product - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure’s latest announcements include product updates and important notices. The announcements display the latest dynamics, and allow customers to see updates the first time, quickly locate corresponding content, and see all updates at a glance.]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>whatisnew</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName>Latest Circular</urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <banner><![CDATA[
      
        <!-- BEGIN: Banner -->
            <div class="common-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#fab300', 'backgroundImage':'//wacndevelop.blob.core.chinacloudapi.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/homepage/banner-announcement@2x.png','imageHeight':'180'}" id="banner">            
            <div class="common-banner-image">
                <div class="common-banner-title">
                    <h1>Latest circular from Azure </h1>
                </div>
            </div>
        </div>  
        <!-- End: Banner-->
    
    ]]></banner>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate></pageTemplate>
    <localize>0</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <headerText></headerText>
    <forbidPublish>1</forbidPublish>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
