<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
    
        <p><tags
            ms.service="icp"
            ms.workload=""
            ms.tgt_pltfrm=""
            ms.devlang="na"
            ms.topic="article"
            ms.date="07/2017"
            wacn.date="07/2017"
            wacn.lang="cn" 
            ms.author="will"/></p>
        <h1>ICP filing operation analysis</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="wacn-date">Final renewal date: July 2017</div></div>
        <h2>Filing type</h2>
        <p>Initial filing</br>
        Original filing in Blue Cloud: Add a website, filing changes, filing sign-off</br>
        Original filing not in Blue Cloud: newly added website, newly added access
        </br>
        </br></p>
        <h2>Filing of specific operations</h2>
        <p>1. Filing requirements for each province</br>
        Before registering, first know your own local administration’s filing requirements. This will make your audit by the local administration go smoothly.</br>
        <a id="icp-cancel_special-request" href="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/备案信息填写要求20180115.doc">Download all provincial administration special requirements</a>
        </br></p>
        <p>2. Filing of specific operations</br>
        2.1 Sign into account</br>
        Sign in to <a id="icp-cancel_cloud.21vianet" href="https://icp.cloud.21vianet.com">https://icp.cloud.21vianet.com</a>, download account number and click Sign in.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/5-1.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>2.2 Cancel filing</br>
        If you have already registered and need to delete information, you can cancel filing operations. Go to the home page and select “cancel filing.”</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/5-2.png" alt="Procedure" /></p>
        <p>To skip to the page, select the corresponding cancelation page</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/5-3.png" alt="Procedure" /></p>
        <p>After confirming cancellation, fill in the relevant information and “save”</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/5-4.png" alt="Procedure" /></p>
        <p>Return to the homepage of the “Cancel filing information” tab to submit the record.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/5-5.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>2.3 Filing actions after submitting filing information</br></p>
        <ol>
        <li>After submitting filing, we will conduct an audit within 2 business days and will let you know by mail or phone if there are any problems. Please make sure your phone is available and check your mail.</br></li>
        <li>
        After filing is completed, the administration will notify the host’s responsible person by mail and SMS.</br>
        Attached: the estimated audit period of some provincial administrations. (Note: the audit period is ultimately up to the administration)</br>
        3 Weeks：Gansu, Yunnan</br>
        2 Weeks: Beijing, Zhejiang, Hubei, Tianjin, Jiangxi, Guangxi, Hebei, Heilongjiang, Inner Mongolia</br>
        1 Week: Guangdong, Jiangsu, Sichuan, Henan, Shanxi, Anhui, Fujian, Guizhou, Liaoning, Hainan, Hunan, Xinjiang, Shanxi, Ningxia, Chongqing</br>
        3 Days: Shanghai</br>
        </li>
        <li>After the filing information is submitted: you can check on the progress of filing through the filing module.</li>
        </ol>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/5-6.png" alt="Procedure" /> </br>
         4. If the administrative audit is not passed, we will call and mail you to inform you of the reason and assist you in submitting additional information. Please ensure your phone is available and check your mail.</p>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>ICP Filing Cancellation ICP Filing Operating Procedure Analysis - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords>ICP Filing Cancellation ICP Filing Operating Procedure Analysis</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
        According to the Chinese Ministry of Industry and Information Technology’s “The Regulation on Internet Information Services” and “Measures for the Archival Administration of Non-operational Internet Information Services,” anyone who runs a website within China’s boundaries (based on domain name resolution) must carry out ICP filing. Moreover, according to the Communications Authority, you cannot go online if your domain name is not registered. All registered domain names must also resolve to a registered IP.    
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
