<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
    
        <p><tags
            ms.service="icp"
            ms.workload=""
            ms.tgt_pltfrm=""
            ms.devlang="na"
            ms.topic="article"
            ms.date="07/2017"
            wacn.date="07/2017"
            wacn.lang="cn" 
            ms.author="will"/></p>
        <h1>ICP filing operation analysis</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="wacn-date">Final renewal date: July 2017</div></div>
        <h2>Filing type</h2>
        <p>Initial filing</br>
        Original filing in Blue Cloud: Add a website, filing changes, filing sign off</br>
        Original filing not in Blue Cloud: newly added website, newly added access
        </br>
        </br></p>
        <h2>Filing of specific operations</h2>
        <p>1. Filing requirements for each province</br>
        Before registering, first know your own local administration’s filing requirements. This will make your audit by the local administration go smoothly.</br>
        <a id="icp-change_special-request" href="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/备案信息填写要求20180115.doc">Download all provincial administration special requirements</a>
        </br></p>
        <p>2. Filing of specific operations</br>
        2.1 Log into account</br>
        Login website<a id="icp-change_cloud.21vianet" href="https://icp.cloud.21vianet.com">https://icp.cloud.21vianet.com</a>, download account number and click Login.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/4-1.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>2.2 Change filing</br>
        A client can change a filing that has already been through an administrative audit, but the change must be re-submitted for the audit to take effect. Click “change filing” to skip to “change filing information,” select the corresponding area that needs to be amended, then click “submit filing” to continue.</br>
        To make a filing change, please note: when making a filing, the effective date of the signature of the person responsible for the website is 24 months, if the change is after that period, it must be re-signed in-person.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/4-2.png" alt="Procedure" /> <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/4-3.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>2.3 Filing actions after submitting filing information</br></p>
        <ol>
        <li>After submitting filing, we will conduct an audit within 2 business days and will let you know by mail or phone if there are any problems. Please make sure your phone is available and check your mail.</br></li>
        <li>After the initial audit, we will mail you with the next steps. According to the mail, take a picture and the original website authentication list + network security responsibility agreement to the Blue Cloud in-person signing address, or take your own picture and mail the materials.</br></li>
        <li>
        In-person signing address:</br>
        Beijing (this is also the address to mail material to): No. 1, Jiuxianqiao East Road, Chaoyang District, Beijing  Telephone: 4000890365</br>
        Shanghai: Room 657, Building 3, No. 88, Keyuan Road, Pudong District, Shanghai  Telephone: 4000890365</br>
        </li>
        <li>After we have received the paper documents and photographs, we will carry out an audit within 1.5 working days. If there are any problems during the audit period, we will call or email you about the materials that have problems. Please ensure that your telephone is available and check your mail. Once your information is found to be accurate and is verified, we will immediately report it to the administration.</br></li>
        <li>
        After filing is completed, the administration will notify the host’s responsible person by mail and text.</br>
        Attached: the estimated audit period of some provincial administrations. (Note: the audit period is ultimately up to the administration)</br>
        3 Weeks：Gansu, Yunnan</br>
        2 Weeks: Beijing, Zhejiang, Hubei, Tianjin, Jiangxi, Guangxi, Hebei, Heilongjiang, Inner Mongolia</br>
        1 Week: Guangdong, Jiangsu, Sichuan, Henan, Shanxi, Anhui, Fujian, Guizhou, Liaoning, Hainan, Hunan, Xinjiang, Shanxi, Ningxia, Chongqing</br>
        3 Days: Shanghai</br>
        </li>
        <li>After the filing information is submitted, you can check on the progress of filing through the filing module. <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/4-4.png" alt="Procedure" /> </br></li>
        <li>If the administrative audit is not passed, we will call and mail you to inform you of the reason and assist you with submitting additional information. Please ensure your phone is available and check your mail.</li>
        </ol>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Original filing in Blue Cloud - Change filing | Azure</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
        
            The ICP filing type is the filing change process for an original filing in Blue Cloud
            
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
