<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
    
         <p><tags
            ms.service="icp"
            ms.workload=""
            ms.tgt_pltfrm=""
            ms.devlang="na"
            ms.topic="article"
            ms.date="07/2017"
            wacn.date="07/2017"
            wacn.lang="cn" 
            ms.author="will"/></p>
        <h1>ICP filing operation analysis</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="wacn-date">Last updated: Wednesday April 4, 2018</div></div>
        <h2>Filing type</h2>
        <p>Initial filing</br>
        Original filing in Blue Cloud: Add a website, filing changes, filing sign off</br>
        Original filing not in Blue Cloud: newly added website, newly added access
        </br>
        </br></p>
        <h2>Filing of specific operations</h2>
        <p>1. ICP filing procedures</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-1.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>2. Filing requirements for each province</br>
        Before registering, first know your own local administration’s filing requirements. This will make your audit by the local administration go smoothly.</br>
        <a id="icp-newinsert_special-request" href="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/备案信息填写要求20180115.doc">Download all provincial administration special requirements</a>
        </br></p>
        <p>3. Filing of specific operations</br>
        3.1 Sign up to account</br>
        3.1.1 Sign in to filing account</br>
        Login website <a id="icp-newinsert_cloud.21vianet" href="https://icp.cloud.21vianet.com">https://icp.cloud.21vianet.com</a></p>
        <p>1) Click on “Registered users”</br>
        2) Enter sign up email. The system can default to using your sign up email as your login account. If the email has already been registered, then please switch to another email</br>
        3) Read and agree to the service agreement</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-2.png" alt="Procedure" /> <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-3.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.1.2 Fill in account information</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-4.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.2 Enter filing information</br>
        3.2.1 Log into filing system, click on “New filing”, and enter the verification page</br>
        Fill in filing domain name and host certification information. The system can, based on the domain and host certification number, check whether a filing record already exists. If the document number and domain name have records, they are recognized as new access.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-5.png" alt="Procedure" /> <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-6.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.2.2 If it is a newly added access, you will be prompted to enter the access information</br>
        1) Website IP address: must be filled out as part of your company’s network segment IP address.</br>
        2) Website access method: Cloud access.</br>
        3) Server location: Select “Beijing” or “Shanghai”.</br>
        4) When an access is newly added, we suggest that the agent information be examined first. If the agent information and actual conditions are not the same, the agent information should be amended and the filing should be changed. After the filing has undergone administrative approval, re-add the access (Note: when amending main information, you can’t carry out new-add operations).</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-7.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.3 Upload filing materials</br>
        Attention:</br></p>
        <p>1) All appended documents must be “original color-scanned” or an “original photograph” in jpg format.</br>
        2) Mainland identity cards must be valid for 3 months. Both sides of the identity card must appear in one image.</br>
        3) On the “Website filing verification checklist” it is only necessary to fill in the “Website host name” (registering host name) and “Website domain” (www. is not needed). Moreover, the “Person responsible for the website signature” must include a seal (each person registering must provide a seal). Please do not fill any information in the section marked “Signature and unit seal of the examiner”.</br>
         <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-8.png" alt="Procedure" /> </br>
         6. If you have not yet gone to the audit and approval page, then click directly on “return to homepage”</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-9.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.4 Submit a filing information note</br>
        1) After information is validated, click “Submit filing” and wait for an initial check.</br>
        2) If you need to submit multiple access requests, return to the verification page and open a new filing workflow. In addition, if you submit multiple access requests, only 3 can be submitted each time. Once administrative approval is passed, additional accesses can be submitted.</br>
        3) To ensure that the audit passes, do not turn on privacy protection during the audit period.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-10.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.5 Filing tasks after filing information is submitted</br></p>
        <ol>
        <li>After submitting filing, we will conduct an audit within 2 business days and will let you know by mail or phone if there are any problems. Please make sure your phone is available and check your mail.</br></li>
        <li>After the initial audit, we will email you with the next steps. Follow the email’s requests to take a picture and bring the “Website Authenticity Audit Checklist + Network Security Certificate” originals to Blue Cloud in-person signing or take your own picture and mail the materials.</br></li>
        <li>
        In-person signing address:</br>
        Beijing (this is also the address to mail materials to): No. 1, Jiuxianqiao East Road, Chaoyang District, Beijing  Telephone: 4000890365 </br>
        Shanghai: Room 657, Building 3, No. 88, Keyuan Road, Pudong District, Shanghai  Telephone: 4000890365 </br>
        </li>
        <li>After we have received the paper documents and photographs, we will carry out an audit within 1.5 working days. If there are any problems during the audit period, we will call or email you about the materials that have problems. Please ensure that your telephone is available and check your mail. Once your information is found to be accurate and is verified, we will immediately report it to the administration.</br></li>
        <li>
        After filing is completed, the administration will notify the host’s responsible person by mail and text.</br>
        Attached: the estimated audit period of some provincial administrations. (Note: the audit period is ultimately up to the administration)</br>
        3 Weeks：Gansu, Yunnan</br>
        2 Weeks: Beijing, Zhejiang, Hubei, Tianjin, Jiangxi, Guangxi, Hebei, Heilongjiang, Inner Mongolia</br>
        1 Week: Guangdong, Jiangsu, Sichuan, Henan, Shanxi, Anhui, Fujian, Guizhou, Liaoning, Hainan, Hunan, Xinjiang, Shanxi, Ningxia, Chongqing</br>
        3 Days: Shanghai</br>
        </li>
        <li>After the filing information is submitted, you can check on the progress of filing through the filing module. <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/7-11.png" alt="Procedure" /> </br></li>
        <li>If the administrative audit is not passed, we will call and mail you to inform you of the reason and assist you with submitting additional information. Please ensure your phone is available and check your mail.</li>
        </ol>
        <p></br>
        </br></p>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Original filings not in Blue Cloud - newly added access | Azure</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
        
            The ICP filing form for new filing of a newly-added access process not in Blue Cloud
            
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
