<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
    
         <p><tags
            ms.service="icp"
            ms.workload=""
            ms.tgt_pltfrm=""
            ms.devlang="na"
            ms.topic="article"
            ms.date="07/2017"
            wacn.date="07/2017"
            wacn.lang="cn" 
            ms.author="will"/></p>
        <h1>ICP filing operation analysis</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="wacn-date">Last updated: Wednesday April 4, 2018</div></div>
        <h2>Filing type</h2>
        <p>Initial filing</br>
        Original filing in Blue Cloud: Add a website, filing changes, filing sign off</br>
        Original filing not in Blue Cloud: newly added website, newly added access
        </br>
        </br></p>
        <h2>Filing of specific operations</h2>
        <p>1. ICP filing procedures</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-1.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>2. Filing requirements for each province</p>
        <p>Before registering, first know your own local administration’s filing requirements. This will make your audit by the local administration go smoothly.</br>
        <a id="icp-new_special-request" href="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/备案信息填写要求20180115.doc">Download all provincial administration special requirements</a>
        </br></p>
        <p>3. Filing of specific operations</br>
        3.1 Sign up to account</br>
        3.1.1 Sign up to register account Log into website<a id="icp-new_cloud.21vianet" href="https://icp.cloud.21vianet.com">https://icp.cloud.21vianet.com</a></p>
        <p>1) Click on “User sign up”.</br>
        2) Enter signup email. the system can default to using your signup email as your login account. If the email has already been signed up, then please change to another email.</br>
        3) Read and agree to the service agreement.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-2.png" alt="Procedure" /> <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-3.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.1.2 Fill in account information</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-4.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.2 Enter filing information</p>
        <p>3.2.1 Log into filing system, click on New Filing, and verify the page</p>
        <p>Fill in filing domain name and host certification information. The system can, based on the domain and host certification number, check whether a filing record already exists. If there isn’t a filing record, then it is a first-time filing.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-5.png" alt="Procedure" /> <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-6.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.2.2 For first time filing, skip to filling in the agent information</p>
        <p>When filling in the agent information, pay attention to the following points:</p>
        <p>1) The business license number acquired after integrating the business license, the organization code certificate, and the certificate of taxation filing into one document should be filled in as the “Unified Social Credit Code”.</br>
        2) For the host contact address, fill it in accurately and in detail, for example the specific street and building number. For rural village units, fill in the details regarding the village and town including the street number or email number.</br>
        3) For the investor or the higher-level unit in charge, if there isn’t a specific investor or unit in charge, fill in the host name to continue.</br>
        4) For the host’s responsible person, we recommend filling in the principal person responsible for the company that is hosting the filing, and filling in the business license and legal representative information.</br>
        5) For the office telephone and mobile number, it should correspond with the host location.</br>
        6) If the certificate number of the person in charge ends in “X”, write it in capital letters.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-7.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br>
        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-8.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.2.3 Fill in website information</br>
        1) Website name: you cannot use the domain or URL as the website name. If the host is not a national-level website, it cannot use “China” in the name.</br>
        2) Webpage URL: Fill in the top level domain corresponding to the web address (for example www.abc.com). Based on current administrative regulations, register the main top level domain, and if the top level domain is an already registered second level domain, it can usually be used.</br>
        3) If the person responsible for the website and the person responsible for the host are not the same person, fill in separate mobile numbers and email addresses to distinguish them, as the two cannot be the same.</br>
        4) From January 1, 2018, domain names engaged in the use of Internet information should be registered to comply with laws and regulations. The domain name registrant for an individual registration should be the individual themselves. The domain name registrant for an organization registration should be the organization (including company shareholders), the main person in charge of the organization, or senior management personnel. Domain names must also be top-level domain names that have been approved by the state, that have been registered through a state-approved domain name registration service.</p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-9.png" alt="Procedures" />
        </br>
        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-10.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br>
        </p>
        <p>3.2.4 Website access information</br>
        1) Website IP address: must be filled out as part of your company’s network segment IP address.</br>
        2) Website access method: Cloud access.</br>
        3) Server location: Select “Beijing” or “Shanghai”.</br></p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-11.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.3 Upload filing materials</br>
        Attention:</br></p>
        <p>1) All appended documents must be “original color-scanned” or an “original photograph” in jpg format.</br>
        2) Mainland identity cards must be valid for 3 months. Both sides of the identity card must appear in one image.</br>
        3) On the “Website Filing Verification Checklist” it is only necessary to fill in the “Website Host Name” (registering host name) and “Website Domain” (www. is not needed). Moreover, the “Person responsible for the website signature” must include a seal (each person registering must provide a seal). Please do not fill any information in the section marked “Signature and unit seal of examiner”.</br>
          <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-12.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br>
        5) The registrant of the domain certificate must be the host or legal representative.</br></p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-13.png" alt="Procedure" />
        </br></p>
        <p>3.4 Submit a filing information note</br>
        1) if you need to submit multiple websites, return to the home page, click on “Website information” and on that page click on “Newly added website”, where you can continue to input websites.</br>
        2) If there are no more websites to register, click “Submit filing” and wait for verification.</br>
        3) To ensure that the audit passes, do not turn on privacy protection during the audit period.</br></p>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-14.png" alt="Procedure" /></br>
        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-15.png" alt="Procedure" /></br>
        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-16.png" alt="Procedure" /></br>
        </br></p>
        <p>3.5 Filing tasks after filing information is submitted</br></p>
        <ol>
        <li>After submitting filing, we will conduct an audit within 2 business days and will let you know by mail or phone if there are any problems. Please make sure your phone is available and check your mail.</br></li>
        <li>After the initial audit, we will mail you with the next steps. According to the mail, take a picture and the original website authentication list + network security responsibility agreement to the Blue Cloud in-person signing address, or take your own picture and mail the materials.</br></li>
        <li>
        In-person signing address:</br>
        Beijing (this is also the address to mail material to): No. 1, Jiuxianqiao East Road, Chaoyang District, Beijing  Telephone: 4000890365  </br>
        Shanghai: Room 657, Building 3, No. 88, Keyuan Road, Pudong District, Shanghai  Telephone: 4000890365 </br>
        </li>
        <li>After we have received the paper documents and photographs, we will carry out an audit within 1.5 working days. If there are any problems during the audit period, we will call or email you about the materials that have problems. Please ensure that your telephone is available and check your mail. Once your information is found to be accurate and is verified, we will immediately report it to the administration.</br></li>
        <li>
        After filing is completed, the administration will notify the host’s responsible person by mail and text.</br>
        Attached: the estimated audit period of some provincial administrations. (Note: the audit period is ultimately up to the administration)</br>
        3 Weeks：Gansu, Yunnan</br>
        2 Weeks: Beijing, Zhejiang, Hubei, Tianjin, Jiangxi, Guangxi, Hebei, Heilongjiang, Inner Mongolia</br>
        1 Week: Guangdong, Jiangsu, Sichuan, Henan, Shanxi, Anhui, Fujian, Guizhou, Liaoning, Hainan, Hunan, Xinjiang, Shanxi, Ningxia, Chongqing</br>
        3 Days: Shanghai</br>
        </li>
        <li>After the filing information is submitted: you can check on the progress of filing through the filing module.</li>
        </ol>
        <p><img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/icp/2-17.png" alt="Procedure" /> </br>
         7. If the administrative audit is not passed, we will call and mail you to inform you of the reason and assist you in submitting additional information. Please ensure your phone is available and check your mail.</br></p>
        <p></br>
        </br></p>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>First-Time Filing | Azure</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
        
            ICP first-time filing process
            
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
