<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="2" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-07-04T10:41:59" urlName="iot-gateway-sdk" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
           <tags ms.service="iot-hub" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/azure-Iot-hub.jpg','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/azure-iot-hub80.png" />
                        <h2>Azure IoT Gateway SDK</h2>
                        <h4>Built-in Edge Logic in hybrid solutions</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_iot-gateway-sdk_trial">1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_iot-gateway-sdk_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner --> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <!-- <h1>连接、监视并控制数百万 IoT 资产</h1> -->
                <ul>
                    <li>Assists new and old devices to connect to the cloud</li>
                    <li>Carries out edge computation and analysis</li>
                    <li>Geared toward time sensitive scenarios</li>
                    <li>Reliably runs solutions</li>
                    <li>Promotes Internet of Things security solutions</li>
					<li>Lowers bandwidth costs</li>
                </ul>
                <h2>Uses Edge Smart Ecology Systems to strengthen performance</h2>
                <p>No matter whether you choose to connect to old devices, lower bandwidth costs, strengthen execution security and privacy policies, or handle any data, cross-platform Azure IoT Gateway SDK can confidently handle common tasks and allow you concentrate on solving important problems. Generate others’ open source, then use a familiar language (node.js, Java, C#, or C) to extend the SDK from the platform of your choice to implement the logic specific to your scenario.</p>

                <h2>Connected manufacturing</h2>
                <p>One car manufacturer hoped for real time monitoring of its global car component production and to raise global factory process efficiency. The solution was based on Azure IoT Gateway SDK at the factory gateway to analyze production cycles and send data to the cloud. Moreover, by comparing large amounts of factory data, it detected and identified production defects. Even with no connection to the Internet, the local gateway can use assembly line sensors to create gigabytes of data to integrate concise information into related production cycles.</p>

                <h2>Intelligent Building</h2>
                <p>Swedish partner Eniga used Azure IoT Gateway SDK to construct the LoRa Gateway to connect a Stockholm residential building to the cloud. This was used to perform advanced analysis on a large amount of building data so that the owner could use smart metering and advanced billing to optimize water, electricity, and heating energy resources. They were able to use building consumption data to make future maintenance and care decisions. Short- and long-term savings improved profits and made for a better tenant experience.</p>

                <h2>Innovative Retail</h2>
                <p>Checkpoint Retail used Azure IoT Gateway SDK to achieve new delivery and in-store shopping experiences. With RFID tagging products to connect to the cloud, Checkpoint used real time inventory tracking to provide clients with efficient delivery options. For example, purchasing online/in-store pickup or in-store purchase/delivery. In addition, data from in-store transactions combined with e-commerce and social media behavior provided valuable insights into loyalty program implementation.</p>

            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content --> <!-- BEGIN: Read-More -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section link-group-container">
			<h1>More</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li><a id="iot-gateway-sdk_articles_iot-hub-linux-gateway-sdk-get-started" href="https://docs.azure.cn/iot-hub/iot-hub-linux-gateway-sdk-get-started/" target="_blank">Azure IoT Gateway SDK - Start using Linux<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></li>
					<li><a id="iot-gateway-sdk_articles_iot-hub-windows-gateway-sdk-get-started" href="https://docs.azure.cn/iot-hub/iot-hub-windows-gateway-sdk-get-started/" target="_blank">Azure IoT Gateway SDK - Start using Windows<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></li>
					<li><a id="iot-gateway-sdk_articles_iot-hub-linux-gateway-sdk-simulated-device" href="https://docs.azure.cn/iot-hub/iot-hub-linux-gateway-sdk-simulated-device/" target="_blank">Azure IoT Gateway SDK - Using Linux to send device information to the cloud through simulated devices<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></li>
					<li><a id="iot-gateway-sdk_articles_iot-hub-windows-gateway-sdk-simulated-device" href="https://docs.azure.cn/iot-hub/iot-hub-windows-gateway-sdk-simulated-device/" target="_blank">Azure IoT Gateway SDK - Using Windows to send device information to the cloud through simulated devices<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></li>
					<li><a id="iot-gateway-sdk_articles_iot-hub-gateway-sdk-physical-device" href="https://docs.azure.cn/iot-hub/iot-hub-gateway-sdk-physical-device/" target="_blank">Azure IoT Gateway SDK - Using Linux to send device information to the cloud through physical devices<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></li>
                </ul>
            </div>

            <!-- END: Read-More --> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->              
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure IoT Gateway SDK Product Overview - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>home-features-iot-gateway-sdk</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Azure IoT Center, Azure IoT Gateway SDK, Built-In Edge Logic, Features, Hybrid Solutions</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Use Azure IoT Gateway SDK (Azure IoT Gateway SDK) to provide a stronger framework to create, configure, and deploy edge logic, allowing you to use Azure IoT for even more things]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Product Overview - Azure IoT Gateway SDK</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
