<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="5" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2014-10-20T09:41:59" urlName="ccs" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
           <tags ms.service="ccs" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/web_banner_cloud-connection-service.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <svg version="1.1" id="Layer_1" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2000/svg" xmlns:xlink="http://www.w3.org/1999/xlink" x="0px" y="0px" width="48px" height="48px" viewBox="0 0 48 48" style="enable-background:new 0 0 48 48;float:left;margin-right:10px;" xml:space="preserve">
                            <style type="text/css">
                                .cloud-connection-service0{fill:#D1D1D1;}
                                .cloud-connection-service1{clip-path:url(#SVGID_2_);}
                                .cloud-connection-service2{fill:#33A2E5;}
                                .cloud-connection-service3{fill:#71C2EA;}
                                .cloud-connection-service4{fill:#005091;}
                                .cloud-connection-service5{clip-path:url(#SVGID_4_);}
                                .cloud-connection-service6{fill:#ACD64D;}
                            </style>
                            <polygon class="cloud-connection-service0" points="0,46 10,46 10,42 4,42 4,6 10,6 10,2 0,2 "/> <polygon class="cloud-connection-service0" points="48,2 38,2 38,6 44,6 44,42 38,42 38,46 48,46 "/> <g> <defs> <path id="SVGID_1_" d="M38.7,8.1c10.8,10.8-16.4,29.7-18,31.4c-1.6,1.6-5.9-0.1-9.6-3.8c-3.7-3.7-5.4-8-3.8-9.6
                                        C9,24.5,28.8-1.9,38.7,8.1z"/> </defs> <clipPath id="SVGID_2_"> <use xlink:href="#SVGID_1_"  style="overflow:visible;"/> </clipPath> <g class="cloud-connection-service1"> <rect x="-1.7" y="22" transform="matrix(-0.7071 0.7071 -0.7071 -0.7071 48.5298 42.6871)" class="cloud-connection-service2" width="34.2" height="18.9"/> <ellipse transform="matrix(0.7071 -0.7071 0.7071 0.7071 -5.6215 25.0969)" class="cloud-connection-service3" cx="27.5" cy="19.3" rx="4.1" ry="9.4"/> <ellipse transform="matrix(0.7071 -0.7071 0.7071 0.7071 -5.6215 25.0969)" class="cloud-connection-service3" cx="27.5" cy="19.3" rx="4.1" ry="9.4"/> <ellipse transform="matrix(0.7071 -0.7071 0.7071 0.7071 -5.6213 25.0977)" class="cloud-connection-service4" cx="27.5" cy="19.3" rx="2.4" ry="7.1"/> <g> <defs> <path id="SVGID_3_" d="M42.2,7.9c5.2,5.2-8.8,15.5-9.7,16.4c-0.9,0.9-3.9-0.6-6.7-3.3c-2.8-2.8-4.3-5.8-3.3-6.7
                                                C23.4,13.4,35.6,1.3,42.2,7.9z"/> </defs> <clipPath id="SVGID_4_"> <use xlink:href="#SVGID_3_"  style="overflow:visible;"/> </clipPath> <g class="cloud-connection-service5"> <path class="cloud-connection-service6" d="M40.2,13.6c-0.5-0.5-1.4-0.5-2,0c0,0,0,0,0,0l0,0L24.4,27.4l2,2l13.8-13.8l0,0c0,0,0,0,0,0
                                                C40.7,15,40.7,14.1,40.2,13.6z"/> <path class="cloud-connection-service6" d="M34.2,12.6c-0.5-0.5-1.4-0.5-2,0c0,0,0,0,0,0l0,0L18.4,26.4l2,2l13.8-13.8l0,0c0,0,0,0,0,0
                                                C34.8,14,34.8,13.1,34.2,12.6z"/> <path class="cloud-connection-service6" d="M28.8,11.3c-0.5-0.5-1.4-0.5-2,0c0,0,0,0,0,0l0,0L13,25.1l2,2l13.8-13.8l0,0c0,0,0,0,0,0
                                                C29.4,12.7,29.4,11.9,28.8,11.3z"/> </g> </g> </g> </g> </svg>
                        <h2>Cloud Connection Service<span style="color: #4d4d4d;font-family: '微软雅黑',regular;font-size: 20px;top: -6px;position: relative;display: inline;"> (Preview) </span></h2>
                        <h4>Customers can use the physical line and network support provided by Cloud Connection Service to easily connect to local data centers and Azure data centers, and deploy flexible, reliable, and secure hybrid cloud scenarios to meet different business needs.</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_ccs_trial">Apply for 1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_ccs_trial">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                        
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner --> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <p>Cloud Connection Service is a one-stop hybrid cloud solution (includes physical line deployment + network support) that provides dedicated lines and support. Customers can easily connect to Azure data centers and local data centers to deploy fast, reliable, and secure hybrid cloud scenarios.</p>
                
                <h2>Advantages</h2>
                <p><strong>A one-stop hybrid cloud solution</strong></p>
                <p>Connect local customer data centers to Azure data centers operated by 21Vianet via Cloud Connection Service and ExpressRoute to implement hybrid architecture and meet different business needs.</p>

                <p><strong>Predictable, secure, and stable bandwidth and latency</strong></p>
                <p>Cloud Connection Service offers a high availability service level agreement of more than 99.9%, allowing customers to enjoy exclusive network bandwidth. It is more stable and has more predictable bandwidth and latency and higher security than a connection via the public Internet.</p>

                <p><strong>Multiple options are offered</strong></p>
                <p>Transfer rates ranging from 1 Mbps to 2.5 GBps are supported, along with four access ports: 100BASE-T, 1000BASE-T, 1000BASE-LX, and 10 GBASE-LR.</p>

                <p><strong>Two-line access</strong></p>
                <p>In order to meet the requirements for highly reliable network access, Cloud Connection Service supports two lines to implement access redundancy and supports high availability scenarios including load balancing, mutual backup, and active/standby switchover.</p>
            </div>
            <div class="pricing-page-section">

                <h2>Application scenarios</h2>

                <p><strong>Make connections stable, reliable and safe, and provide support for key services</strong></p>
                <p>With ExpressRoute, you can create a proprietary connection between an Azure data center and your on-premises data center. Cloud Connection Service connects through a private network and is more stable, with more predictable bandwidth and latency and higher security than a connection via a public network. It can provide support for critical business (for example, SAP systems).</p>

                <p><strong>Storage, backup, and recovery</strong></p>
                <p>Cloud Connection Service provides you with a fast and reliable connection to Azure, which is suitable for the following scenarios: periodic data migration, replication for business continuity, disaster recovery, and other high availability strategies. It can also be a cost-effective option for transferring large amounts of data (such as datasets for high-performance computing applications), or moving large virtual machines between your development/test environment in Azure and your on-premises production environment.</p>

                <p><strong>Expand your data center</strong></p>
                <p>It allows you to securely add compute and storage capacity to your existing data center. The high throughput and low latency provided by Cloud Connection Service’s dedicated line services make an Azure data center operated by 21Vianet feel like a natural extension of your own data center, so you can enjoy the scalability and economy of the public cloud while enjoying high throughput, low latency network performance.</p>

                <p><strong>Build hybrid applications</strong></p>
                <p>Cloud Connection Service provides a predictable, reliable, and secure way to connect an Azure data center operated by 21Vianet with a customer’s on-premises data center. Users can build applications that span both on-premises infrastructure and Azure applications operated by 21Vianet, without compromising security or performance and enabling flexible and reliable hybrid cloud deployments. There are two ways of setting up backups for Cloud Connection Service:</p>

                <ul>
                    <li>Two-line access backup for master-failover configuration.</li>
                    <li>To configure a VPN connection as a failover path for ExpressRoute, please refer to<a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/expressroute/expressroute-howto-coexist-resource-manager"> Setting Up ExpressRoute and Site-to-site Concurrent Connections</a>.</li>
                </ul>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content --> <!-- BEGIN: Read-More --> <!-- END: Read-More --> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->                
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Cloud Connection Service (CCS) Product Overview - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>tour-features-ccs</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Cloud Connection Service, CCS</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Cloud Connection Service (CCS) is a one-stop hybrid cloud solution (includes physical line deployment + network support). Customers can connect to Azure data centers and local customer data centers via dedicated lines to deploy fast, reliable, and secure hybrid cloud scenarios.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Product Overview - Cloud Connection Service (CCS)</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
