<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="2" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-07-04T15:41:59" urlName="event-hubs" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
           <tags ms.service="event-hubs" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/event-hubs.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/event-hubs@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Event Hubs<span>Event Hubs</span></h2>
                        <h4>Cloud-scale telemetry ingestion from websites, apps, and any streams of data</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_event_trial">Apply for trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_event_pia">Buy now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner --> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h1>Collect cloud-scale telemetry data from websites, applications, and devices</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li>Log millions of events per second in near real time</li>
                    <li>Automatically send telemetry data to storage</li>
                    <li>Use time-based event buffering</li>
                    <li>Get a managed service with elastic scale</li>
                    <li>Access a series of platforms using native client libraries</li>
                    <li>Seamlessly integrate with other Azure services</li>
                </ul>
                <h2>Stream millions of events per second</h2>
                <p>Event Hubs is a hyper-scale telemetry ingestion service that collects, transfers, and stores millions of events. As a distributed streaming platform, it offers users low latency and configurable time retention, which enables users to ingest large amounts of telemetry data into the cloud and read the data from multiple applications using publish-subscribe semantics.</p>

                <h2>Handle real-time and batch processing in the same data stream</h2>
                <p>Use the Event Hubs Capture feature, which enables a single stream to support real-time and batch-based pipelines, and reduces the complexity of solutions. Build for today’s batch processing on a platform that supports tomorrow’s real-time analytics and processing. Event Hubs Capture is the easiest way to load data into Azure.</p>

                <h2>Take advantage of a fully managed platform as a service</h2>
                <p>Event Hubs is a fully managed service; there are no servers to maintain and no software licenses to get. Pricing is simple and easy. Event Hubs enables users to focus on getting value from their telemetry data instead of gathering the data.</p>
                
                <h2>Handle volume, variety, and velocity</h2>
                <p>Big data originates from many sources with different load distributions. For example, thermostats that produce telemetry data every few minutes, application performance counters that generate events every second, and mobile apps that capture telemetry data for every customer’s action. Event Hubs is a fully managed service that ingests events with elastic scale based on different load distributions and spikes.</p>

                <h2>Develop across platforms with multi-language support</h2>
                <p>Event Hubs uses Advanced Message Queuing Protocol (AMQP) to enable interoperability and binary compatibility across platforms, while also supporting HTTPS for data ingress. With native clients in Java and .NET, it’s easy to get started with Event Hubs. You can also integrate with Azure Services (including Stream Analytics and Virtual Machines), while building rich serverless workflows. There is also a strong Event Hubs open-source community that’s continually creating new adapters and connectors for popular platforms such as Apache NiFi and Elastic Stack.</p>

            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content --> <!-- BEGIN: Read-More -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section link-group-container">
                <h1>Find out more</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li><a id="home_event_hubs_sta" href="http://channel9.msdn.com/posts/Service-Bus-Introduction/" style="color: #00a8d9;" target="_blank">Service Bus introduction</a></li>
                    <li><a id="home_event_hubs_document" href="https://docs.azure.cn/event-hubs/" style="color: #00a8d9;" target="_blank">Event Hubs documentation</a></li>
                </ul>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Read-More --> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> &lt;?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->               
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Event Hubs Internet of Things - Azure cloud computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>home-features-event-hubs</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Microsoft Cloud, Internet of Things, Event Hubs, Azure Event Hubs, data processing, hosting services, functions</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure Event Hubs is a hosting service that can capture and process massive data streams from websites, applications, and devices. It can capture millions of events per second and has flexible scale. It also has dockable adapters to interface with other cloud services.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Event Hubs</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
