<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="2" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-06-28T11:31:22" urlName="service-fabric" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
           <tags ms.service="service-fabric" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/media,images,production,service-fabric_background.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/documents/service-fabrics@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Service Fabric</h2>
                        <h4>Service Fabric is an application platform that can be used to build microservice-based applications.</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_service-fabric_trial">Apply for a 1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_service-fabric_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner --> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h1>Build and run always-on, scalable, distributed apps</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li>Simplified app deployment and lifecycle management based on microservices</li>
                    <li>Provides low-latency performance and productivity on a large scale</li>
                    <li>Proven platforms used by Azure and other Microsoft Services</li>
                    <li>Runs on Azure, locally or in the cloud</li>
                </ul>

                <h2>Simplified app deployment and lifecycle management based on microservices</h2>
                <ul>
                    <li><strong>Quick time-to-market: </strong>Using Service Fabric, developers can focus on creating functions that add commercial value to apps and avoid the everyday costs generated by designing and writing extra code to deal with reliability, scalability or latency issues in the infrastructure.</li>
                    <li><strong>Choose your preferred architecture:</strong> Create stateless or stateful microservices (in this architecture method, complex apps are composed of small, standalone versions of services) to support the most complex, low latency, data-dense solutions and extend them into the cloud.</li>
                    <li><strong>Microservice flexibility:</strong> Building refined microservice apps can implement continuous integration and continuous development practice, as well as speeding up the delivery of new functions to apps.</li>
                    <li><strong>Visual Studio integration:</strong> Includes support for Visual Studio tools and the command line, so that developers can quickly and easily create, test, shakedown, deploy and update their Service Fabric apps for standalone deployment, test deployment and production deployment.</li>
                </ul>
                
                <h2>Provides low-latency performance and productivity on a large scale</h2>
                <p>Implements rapid in-place upgrades and has advantages including zero downtime, autoscaling, integrated health monitoring and service self-healing. Microservice business flows and automation provide a new level of application awareness and insight, so that rollback and autoscaling functions can be used to implement automatic real-time upgrades.</p>
                <p>It also resolves difficult issues with distributed systems (such as failover, leader election, state management) and provides app lifecycle management functions that mean developers no longer need to rebuild apps because of usage increases. This includes multi-tenant SaaS applications, IoT data collection and processing, and game and media services.</p>

                <h2>Proven platforms used by Azure and other Microsoft Services</h2>
                <p>We created Service Fabric based on many years of experience implementing mission-critical cloud services. Our core Azure infrastructure operates based on this infrastructure technology, and has enhanced the following services: Skype for Business, Intune, Azure Event Hubs, Azure Data Factory, Azure DocumentDB, Azure SQL Database, and Cortana. Based on this experience, we were able to design a platform with an inherent understanding of available infrastructure resources and app needs, thereby implementing automatic updates and self-healing behavior that provides highly available and persistent services on a very large scale.</p>

                <h2>Runs on Azure, locally or in the cloud</h2>
                <p>Platform services that consistently span Azure, local and managed service centers and identical app modes enable you to flexibly deploy identical app code in public clouds, managed clouds or private clouds. As we are committed to providing choice and flexibility, Service Fabric apps can run on Azure, locally and in other clouds, and you can also choose to use Windows Server or Linux as the host operating system (Service Fabric on Linux is currently only available as a preview version).</p>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content --> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />

    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure Service Fabric - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>home-features-service-fabric</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Microsoft Cloud, Azure Service Fabric, platform, app</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure Service Fabric is an app platform that can be used to build apps based on Microsoft Services. It simplifies deployment and lifecycle management for Microsoft Services-based apps, and provides low-latency performance and productivity on a large scale. It is a proven platform that is used by Azure and other Microsoft services, and can run on Azure, locally, or in other clouds.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Service Fabric</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
