<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="2" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-06-30T15:41:59" urlName="storage" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
           <tags ms.service="storage" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/storage.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/css/storage@2x.png" />
                        <h2>Storage</h2>
                        <h4>Durable, highly available, and massively scalable cloud storage</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_storage_trial">Apply for 1RMB Trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_storage_pia">Buy Now<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner --> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h1>Suitable for different scales of data, economical and reliable cloud storage</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li>Manage PB level storage</li>
                    <li>Crosses hundreds of kilometers of regional redundant storage</li>
                    <li>Industry’s highest functionality</li>
                    <li>Conforms with industry standards for file-sharing across virtual machines</li>
                    <li>Competitive pricing, controls consumption costs</li>
                    <li>Supports REST, .NET, Java, C++, node.js, PowerShell, etc.</li>
                </ul>
                <h2>Blob, Table, Queue and File</h2>
                <p>Azure Storage Service possess a high degree of flexibility when it comes to data storage and retrieval. It can store large amounts of unstructured data, for example you can use Azure Blob to store documents and media files, or use Azure Storage Table to form NoSQL data, or use Azure Queue Storage for reliable information. And, based on SMB <a id="home-files_storage" class="link-btn_one" href="/home/features/storage/files/" style="color:#00a8d9" target="_blank">Azure File</a>service, sequence local apps for migration to the cloud.</p>
                
                <h2>Premium Storage</h2>
                <p>Azure Advanced Storage is a Azure virtual machine running an I/O-intensive workload to provide high performance and low-latency disk support. You can add several advanced storage disks to a virtual machine (VM). With the help of advanced storage and apps, each VM can hold up to 32 TB of storage and achieve 50,000 IOPS (input/output operations per-second). Read operation latency is also very low. Currently, Advanced Storage can only store data on Azure Virtual Machine disks.</p>
                <p><a id="home_advanceStoMore" href="/home/features/xio-storage/" target="_blank">Find out more</a></p>

                <h2>High flexibility</h2>
                <p>Azure Storage Services can always satisfy your continuously growing data needs and provide a maximum of 500 TB of storage per account. Each subscription includes 20 individual accounts, providing PB-level storage, which you can use to achieve large-scale deployment plans. No matter if you are building a consumer product website or TB-level big data apps, Azure can handle it with ease.</p>

                <h2>Durable and highly useful</h2>
                <p>Azure Storage Services automatically duplicates your data and assists in overcoming transient hardware failures, ensuring data is always available. We maintain 3 copies in each zone. With geo-redundancy you can choose to create 3 copies hundreds of kilometers outside a region to further increase reliability and achieve disaster recovery. Geo-redundancy backup can have the option of being read access, which can further raise data availability to 99.99%.</p>

                <h2>Focused on developer planning</h2>
                <p>With the help of support to common client libraries like ,NET, Java, Android, C++ and Node.js, you have freedom in building apps. Data in Azure Storage Services can still access through REST API and any language that can invoke HTTP/HTTPS can use the API. Azure Storage Services provide reliable, consistent safeguards, simplify development of cloud apps, and provide a predictable experience building apps on Azure.</p>

                <!--<h2>全球覆盖</h2>
                <pAzure 存储服务已在全球建立19个数据中心，其中包括中国东部以及中国北部。你可以将文件放置在对业务最有利的区域，还可以根据需要扩展存储服务或跨数据中心部署，并将数据保留在靠近客户的地理位置，让用户实现快速高性能访问。</p>
                -->
				
                <h2>Highly cost effective</h2>
                <p>Only pay for the services you use and there is a lower price if you have your own local storage solutions. We have competitive set price matching plans, which means that you can get help with cloud storage to maximize profits.</p>
               
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content --> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> <?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->
                           
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Storage Product Overview - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>home-features-storage</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Azure Storage, Features</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure Storage (Storage) is economic and reliable, suitable for different scales of data and is highly cost effective. It can automatically backup data, help guard against unexpected hardware failure, and ensure data is always available. Azure Storage always satisfies users’ continuously growing data needs, and with the support of common client libraries you can build your own apps.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Product Overview - Storage</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
