<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="2" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2014-10-20T09:41:59" urlName="virtual-machines" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
           <tags ms.service="virtual-machines" ms.date="09/30/2015" wacn.date="11/27/2015"></tags> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-TopBanner -->
            <div class="common-banner col-top-banner" data-config="{'backgroundColor':'#e3f4ff', 'backgroundImage':'//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/virtual_machine.png','imageHeight':'auto'}">
                <div class="common-banner-image">
                    <div class="common-banner-title">
                        <img src="//resource.cdn.azure.cn/marketing-resource/media/images/production/icon-virtual-machines.png" />
                        <h2><span>Virtual Machines</span></h2>
                        <h4>You only need minutes to start a Windows Server and Linux Server and can completely control servers in the cloud and perform maintenance based on your business needs.</h4>
                        <em><a href="/pricing/1rmb-trial/" id="home_vm_trial">Apply for a trial<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a></em> <a href="/pricing/pia/" id="home_vm_pia">Purchase immediately<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                    </div>
                </div>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-TopBanner --> <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h1>You only need minutes to start a Windows Server and Linux</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li>Very large scale is going from one to thousands of virtual machine instances</li>
                    <li>Built-in virtual networks and load balancing</li>
                    <li>Achieve a consistent mixed environment with a local environment</li>
                    <li>Supports Linux, Windows Server, SQL Server, Oracle, IBM and SAP</li>
                    <li>Charging by the minute to economize costs</li>
                </ul>
                <p>You can use Azure virtual machines to image a Windows Server, Linux, or third-party software to Azure. You can choose from a warehouse of images or use your own custom image.</p>
                <p>Azure image warehouse provides the following versions of Windows Server: Windows Server 2008 R2, Windows Server 2012 and Windows Server 2012 R2.</p>
                <p>Azure image warehouse provides the following versions of SQL Server: all versions of SQL Server2014, SQL Server 2012, and SQL Server 2008 R2.</p>
                <p><strong>Warning:</strong></p>
                <p>Azure Virtual Machine Disk includes a temporary disk, D: disk (Windows) or /dev/sdb1 (Linux). They only provide temporary storage, so that there is the risk of lost data and data is not backed up. The common reason this situation occurs is when virtual machines migrate onto different mainframes. Causes of virtual machine migration include adjusting the size of a virtual machine, replacing a mainframe, or a hardware failure.</p>
                <a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/linux/classic/faq/" id="home_vm_overview_info" class="single-link">Find out more<i class="icon icon-arrow-right-thin"></i></a>
                <h2>SQL Server</h2>
                <p>Using an image built by the SQL Server Team, you can effortlessly set up a SQL Server in a few minutes. You can use the free MSDN licensed virtual machine environment to focus on rapid development/testing. You can also use SQL Server AlwaysOn across multiple Azure regions to deploy complicated apps you have created.</p>

                <h2>Open, to provide more choices</h2>
                <p>You can deploy fully open and community driven operating systems and software solutions on Azure. With the help of Azure, yo can choose Ubuntu and SUSE type Linux released versions. Azure is open, providing you more choices.</p>

                <h2>Save money, get above average flexibility</h2>
                <p>When deploying a virtual machine into Azure, you pay by the minute for fast computer mode workloads, rapid development and testing environments, and frequent stop and start scenarios. It includes Windows, Linux, and SQL Server all charged by the minute. You even can automatically scale your entire platform based on planned or instance CPU use rates. We can provide a charge plan to satisfy your infrastructure and software needs, not our needs!</p>

                <h2>Hybrid Connections</h2>
                <p>Using virtual networks, you can control and configure all aspects of your network, define a subnetwork, and preferred DNS IP. You can, through the Internet, use a secure path through a VPN into Azure to reach your virtual machine.</p>
                <p>This service includes load balancing across instances and ease of configuration. You can set up Load Balancer and add secure ACL to control access. Moreover, you can define specific instrumentation to help you monitor running applications. All of this can be done through an easy-to-use portal.</p>

                <h2>Faster, bigger, and better D series virtual machines</h2>
                <p>You can now deploy an even bigger D series virtual machine to satisfy you load balancing requirements. This size of virtual machine runs faster and stronger and handles faster device speeds. Internal storage is greater and provides easier virtual machine extremely fast temporary storage based on a temporary disk supported by SSD storage. You have to try it out to see how fast it is! Experience it yourself today.</p>

                <h2>It uses Dv2 and DSv2 series virtual machine functionality</h2>
                <p>The Dv2 series virtual machine is an improvement over the D series virtual machine and provides an even stronger CPU<!--，即在相同的内存和磁盘配置的情况下，CPU 的平均速度更快 35%-->. The Dv2 series is based on the newest generation 2.4 GHz Intel Xeon E5-2673 v3 (Haswell) processor and uses Intel Turbo Boost technology 2.0, which can exceed a speed of 3.2 GHz. The DSv2 is based on the Dv2 adding <a href="/home/features/xio-storage/" id="home_vm_overview_xio-storage" class="single-link">Azure Advanced Storage</a> to provide high-performance permanent disk. Speaking of the need for an even faster CPU, better local disk performance, or higher enterprise-level storage apps, the DSv2, Dv2 and D series combined can provide even stronger functionality.</p>

                <h2>Through software assurance get Microsoft license mobility</h2>
                <p>Using software assurance get Microsoft license mobility you can:</p>
                <p>From the Azure Data Center, you can allocate to some servers use of licensed programs based on purchasing a volume licensing agreement. Locally or in the cloud allocate server use of licensed programs to extend value.</p>
                <p>Use low cost calculations of infrastructure to change business priorities.</p>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content --> <!-- BEGIN: Read-More -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section link-group-container">
                <h1>Find out more</h1>
                <ul>
                    <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/linux/endorsed-distros?toc=%2fvirtual-machines%2flinux%2ftoc.json" id="home_virtual_documention_list">Azure supports virtual machine mirror imaging</a></li>
                    <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/classic/tutorial/" id="home_virtual_tutorial-classic-portal">Creating and running a Windows Server virtual machine</a></li>
                    <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/linux/quick-create-portal/" id="home_virtual_linux-tutorial-portal-rm">Creating and running a Linux virtual machine</a></li>
                    <li><a href="/home/features/networking/" id="home_virtual-machines_networking">Virtual network</a></li>
                    <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/classic/capture-image/" id="home_virtual_cap">Capture a Windows Server image</a></li>
                    <li><a href="//docs.azure.cn/zh-cn/virtual-machines/windows/sqlclassic/virtual-machines-windows-classic-ps-sql-create/" id="home_virtual_sqlserver">Find out details about SQL Server on Azure</a></li>
                </ul>
            </div>
            <!-- END: Read-More --> <!--BEGIN: Support and service code chunk--> &lt;?UMBRACO_MACRO chunkpath="production" chunkname="production-bottom-banner" macroAlias="blankCodeChunk" />  <!--END: Support and service code chunk-->               
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>Azure Virtual Machine_Windows/Linux Virtual Machine - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>home-features-virtual-machines</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Virtual Machines,Features, SQL Server, Virtual Machine Instances</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure Virtual Machines (Virtual Machines) can rapidly set up scalable Linux or Windows servers and allocate virtual machine resources locally or from the cloud. Built-in virtual networks and load balancing achieve a consistent hybrid environment with a local environment that supports Microsoft SQL Server and SharePoint Server. You can use Azure virtual machines to deploy Windows Server, Linux, or third party software images to Azure and choose from a warehouse of images or use your own.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Virtual Machines</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
