<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
    
         <p><tags
            ms.service="public-security-registration"
            ms.workload=""
            ms.tgt_pltfrm=""
            ms.devlang="na"
            ms.topic="article"
            ms.date="03/2017"
            wacn.date="03/2017"
            wacn.lang="cn" 
            ms.author="will"/></p>
        <h1>Website filing process</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="wacn-date">Last updated: March 2017</div></div>
        <h3>1. Initial online review</h3>
        <p>Initial review materials for website filing need to be submitted on the national public security system (apply after the 5th of every month). Review materials may only be submitted to the branch after the initial review has been passed and “in-person verification” has been displayed (refer to the message left by the system for details of the specific in-person verification time and requirements).</p>
        <p>Filing website: <a href="http://www.beian.gov.cn">http://www.beian.gov.cn</a></p>
        <p>Note:</p>
        <ol>
        <li>
        <p>Website filing applications must be submitted in the district or county where the office of the public institution, company, or social organization is located.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
        <p>Personal websites need to be filed at the household filing location.</p>
        </li>
        </ol>
        <h3>2. Onsite verification</h3>
        <p>After the website being filed passes its initial review, please bring the following materials to the Internet Security reception room at 2F, 800 Lingshan Road for in-person verification:</p>
        <ol>
        <li>
        <p>International Online Organization Filing Form, filed International Online User Information and Internet Usage Form, Online Information Security Protection Group (these three forms can be downloaded from<a href="http://www.pdxa.cn">http://www.pdxa.cn</a>).</p>
        </li>
        <li>
        <p>Main qualification documents: Communist Party organizations, government organizations, and public institutions are to submit copies of their Organization Code Certificate and Public Institution Legal Person Certificate. Companies are to submit copies of their Organization Code Certificate, Business License, and Corporate Tax Filing Certificate.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
        <p>Website-related materials: Copy of website ownership certificate (i.e., domain name certificate) and network topology map.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
        <p>Information on website owner: Copy of identification card (people not from this city are requested to provide proof of residence).</p>
        </li>
        <li>
        <p>Industry certification: Those engaged in online services that require prior approval are requested to submit a copy of an approval document, such as a payment business license, pharmaceutical industry qualification certificate, food industry qualification certificate, audiovisual program qualification certificate, or online cultural operations qualification certificate.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
        <p>Website security status: Website security vulnerability scan report (needs to have the seal of the testing organization affixed).</p>
        </li>
        <li>
        <p>Proof of operating location: A copy of the rental contract, etc.</p>
        </li>
        <li>
        <p>Website security management system: Interactive websites are to establish a security management system in accordance with Information Security Technology: Security Requirements for Interactive Internet Services (see Appendix for further details of the specific content).</p>
        </li>
        </ol>
        <p>Note: The above materials must all have official seals affixed. Please call 22047852 if you have any questions.</p>
        <h3>3. Logo display</h3>
        <p>After you have passed your filing audit, sign in to <a href="http://www.beian.gov.cn">www.beian.gov.cn</a>.</p>
        <p>In the filed Website menu on the platform homepage, click on Public Security Bureau Filing Number Details to view and download filing icon code which you can copy into the code on your website’s homepage.</p>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Public security website filing process | Azure</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
        
            Public security website filing process
            
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
