<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
    
        <p><tags ms.service="public-security-registration"
            ms.workload=""
            ms.tgt_pltfrm=""
            ms.devlang="na"
            ms.topic="article"
            ms.date="03/2017"
            wacn.date="03/2017"
            wacn.lang="cn" 
            ms.author="will"/></p>
        <h1>Notification for Network Security Responsibilities for the Service Institutions of Internet Information</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="wacn-date">Last updated: March 2017</div></div>
        <h2>Dear users, hello!</h2>
        <p>We recently received notice from the public security department on the website’s public security filing. It is requested that you log into the <a href="http://www.beian.gov.cn">National Public Security Internet Websites Security Management Services Platform</a> as soon as possible, and submit an application to file with public security. If the formalities are not handled for more than 30 days after the date the network is officially connected, the connection will be suspended in accordance with the laws. The contents of the notice are as follows:
        </br>
        </br>
        In order to protect the security of network information, guarantee the legitimate rights and interests of citizens, legal persons and other organizations, and safeguard national security and public interests, in accordance with the regulations of applicable laws and rules, such as the Regulations of the People's Republic of China for Computer Information Systems Security Protection and Computer Information Network International Network Security Protection Management Measures, the network security responsibilities that your institution shall fulfill according to law are given below:</p>
        <p>I. Possess related qualifications that are required by the laws and regulations;</p>
        <p>The providers for Internet information services shall be the entities that solely bear the legal responsibilities. Related licenses and qualifications shall be obtained for engaging in Internet information services which require approval of the relevant departments, in accordance with laws and regulations and related decisions of the State Council.</p>
        <p>II. Accept the supervision, inspection and guidance of public security organizations according to law;</p>
        <p>III. Assist public security organizations in investigating and punishing illegal criminal activities related to the Internet in accordance with laws;</p>
        <p>IV. Be in accordance with applicable laws and regulations and standards for security management, such as the <a href="http://www.gov.cn/flfg/2005-08/06/content_20928.htm">Regulations of the People's Republic of China for Computer Information Systems Security Protections</a>, <a href="http://www.gov.cn/gongbao/content/2011/content_1860856.htm"> Computer Information Network International Network Security Protection Management Measures</a>, <a href="http://www.gov.cn/gongbao/content/2006/content_421771.htm"> Provisions on Technical Measures for the Protection of Internet Security</a>, <a href="http://www.beian.gov.cn/portal/index"> Security Protection Requirements for Internet Interactive Services</a>, and <a href="http://www.beian.gov.cn/portal/index">Basic Procedures and Requirements for Internet Service Security Evaluation</a>, and perform other security protection obligations, for instance, filtration of illegal information, inspection of public information and users’ qualifications, retention of log information, rapid disposal, and implementation of safety management responsibilities and related technical measures for security protection;</p>
        <p>V. Post a filing icon issued by public security organizations in a prominent position on the home page of the website;</p>
        <p>VI. When the filing information of the website changes, it is requested that you log in to the platform to submit the changed information within 30 days after the information was changed. If you fail to go through the formalities in line with the regulated requirements and time limits, the public security organization will notify the access provider to suspend website access according to law;</p>
        <p>VII. When the website is no longer opened, you are requested to log in to the National Public Security Internet Sites Security Management Services Platform within 5 working days and submit an application for cancellation to the network security department of the local public security organization.</p>
        <p>No fees are charged for filing with public security. In case of any problems related to records in the public security organization, you can consult the local network police department, or visit the <a href="http://www.beian.gov.cn">National Public Security Internet Sites Security Management Services Platform</a> for more details.
         </br>
         </br>
        21Vianet’s Microsoft Azure Team on April 21, 2016</p>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Notification for Network Security Responsibilities for the Service Institutions of Internet Information - Azure Cloud Computing</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
        
            Notification of Network Security Responsibilities for Internet Information Service Institutions
            
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
