<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <umbTextpage template="21" createDate="2017-12-04T11:20:07" updateDate="2017-12-04T11:34:25">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
    
        <p><tags
            ms.service="public-security-registration"
            ms.workload=""
            ms.tgt_pltfrm=""
            ms.devlang="na"
            ms.topic="article"
            ms.date="03/2017"
            wacn.date="03/2017"
            wacn.lang="cn" 
            ms.author="will"/></p>
        <h1>Public Security Filing</h1><div class="tags-date"><div class="wacn-date">Last updated: March 2017</div></div>
        <h2>Why we have to register</h2>
        <p>“Administrative Measures for the Security Protection of Computer Information Networks Linked to the Internet” (Ministry of Public Security Decree 33) approved and issued by the State Council stipulates that:
        </br>
        </br>
        Article 11 A Users shall fill in the user registration form when going through the formalities of accessing the network at the receiving institution. The user registration form shall be prepared under the supervision of the Ministry of Public Security.
        </br>
        </br>
        Article 12 interconnected and access units, legal persons and other organizations that use the international network of computer information networks (including cross-province, cross-autonomous region and cross-municipality directly under Central Government interconnected units and their branches) should go through the formalities of registering at the processing agencies designated by the public security organs of the governments of the provinces, autonomous regions and municipalities directly under the Central Government wherein the units are located within 30 days starting from the date of formal connection of the network.
        </br>
        </br>
        The institutions listed in the preceding article shall be responsible for registering information on the access units and users connecting to the network to local public security organizations and report changes in the access units and users connecting to this network in a timely manner.</p>
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <umbracoNaviHide>0</umbracoNaviHide>
    <pageTitle>Public Security Filing | Azure</pageTitle>
    <metaKeywords></metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[
        
            Reasons for Public Security Filing
            
    ]]></metaDescription>
    <linkid>0</linkid>
    <urlDisplayName></urlDisplayName>
    <headerExpose></headerExpose>
    <footerExpose></footerExpose>
    <disqusComments>0</disqusComments>
    <metaCanonical></metaCanonical>
    <isHeader>0</isHeader>
    <pageTemplate>0</pageTemplate>
    <localize>1</localize>
    <localizePartial>0</localizePartial>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <banner>
    </banner>
  </umbTextpage>
</localize>
