<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<localize>
  <TextpageLeftNav template="2" createDate="2014-08-05T07:49:24" updateDate="2016-07-07T10:41:59" urlName="storage_files" writerName="content" creatorName="content">
    <bodyText><![CDATA[
      
            <style type="text/css">
                .container .pure-content .pricing-page-section{
                    margin-top: -40px!important;
                }
                @media only screen and (max-width: 769px){
                    .container .pure-content .pricing-page-section{
                        margin-top: 0px!important;
                    }
                }
            </style>
            <!-- BEGIN: Product-Detail-Content -->
            <div class="pricing-page-section">
                <h3 style="font-weight:400;"><a id="storage-economic_highStorage" class="anchor"></a> <a id="xio_storage_sto" href="/home/features/storage/" style="color:#00a8d9" target="_blank">Storage</a><span>></span><a id="xio_storage_advantagesto" style="color:#00a8d9" href="javascript:void(0)">Azure Files</a></h2>
                <h1>File Storage</h1>
                <p>Use standard SMB 3.0 protocol apps shared storage</p>
                <p>Key Scenarios:</p>
                <ul>
                    <li>Migrate existing apps to the cloud</li>
                    <li>No need to alter code to use cloud storage</li>
                    <li>Share tools and logs between virtual machines</li>
                </ul>
                <h2>No need for complex rewrites to easily migrate apps</h2>
                <p>With no need to rewrite code, or rewrite only a limited amount of code, easily use reliable shared storage apps to migrate to the cloud. You only need to use internally deployed servers to transfer into Azure virtual machines and use Azure file services to handle file storage. Azure provides a useful and reliable service level agreement, freeing you from administering file servers.</p>

                <h2>Cloud storage with no need to rewrite code</h2>
                <p>Azure file storage uses Windows and other operating systems standard SMB 3.0 protocol. Because of this, apps can us familiar document system interfaces to open, access, and administer file storage. Azure file storage looks like familiar apps used for internally configured file storage and because of this existing code can often be used.</p>

                <h2>Shared public files and data</h2>
                <p>Azure file storage provides simple and convenient public storage solutions - server data, diagnostic tools, and troubleshooting logs - even when app servers crash, it can ensure data availability.</p>
                
            
            </div>
            <!-- END: Product-Detail-Content -->
                          
    
    ]]></bodyText>
    <pageTitle>File Storage |Azure</pageTitle>
    <sitemapHide>0</sitemapHide>
    <linkid>home-features-storage-files</linkid>
    <metaKeywords>Azure, Storage Services, File Storage</metaKeywords>
    <metaDescription><![CDATA[Azure file storage provides simple and convenient public storage solutions - server data, diagnostic tools, and troubleshooting logs - even when app servers crash, it can ensure data availability.]]></metaDescription>
    <urlDisplayName>Virtual Machines</urlDisplayName>
  </TextpageLeftNav>
</localize>
